Hi everyone
Babe what hi Miley, I'm sorry Mikey
Babe
How are you here? Okay? Hey tricks I come cuddle I'm cuddle with me
Hi, it was quite a night last night. We'll recap it. Oh my god
Just those crazy night
One of the more
Have weird nights was last night and you know, I happen at I don't know. It was just weird. It was just
one after another
People I like really like
Maybe people that are kind of controversial on the show sometimes says
Yeah, thank you. Oh
Yeah, the people I like there's three people like, you know
Yeah, I like I like all I like all the people but you know
said I'm there
Nice nice intense, but I just remember like three people, you know, there's a lot of people out there a lot of people were meaning at me and stuff but
You know
Alex actually, oh my god, so many people attacked me good times Alex
It's a big pipe. We missed some big pipes now. I expected that from him. I was like, oh my god,
this is just terrible last night. He was just,
I don't know, this is lack of self-awareness. Maybe I said something to irritate. I just,
I mean, I just, I got annoyed to put him backstage. Finishingly, I brought him back up.
Is it after your fucking show and then he starts saying the n-word over you know, it's not another person. It's like
What that are we with level of intelligence of of human being in my way. What is this?
I
Say
These people are demented
Well, not I mean not you know, I love Joker. I think I don't think Joker was trying to like pick on me
He was like, oh, I'm just trolling you
Isn't it aren't you gonna laugh well not many people like laugh when they're being troll it's like kind of like
trolling is kind of like design for everyone else to like laugh at the person or make the person look stupid and not
Hi Z
Yeah, trolling is like so we went into Joker's like oh, I'm just I was just trolling you and he's telling me
Oh, you need to meditate you need to take you know you're telling me what I need to do and stuff
You know, I don't like to be told what I need to do or
what i'm doing i guess so of course i didn't you know i get a little annoying oh you got triggered
i guess she doesn't have a does it have a um you can't take a joke
let's say about me you're not trolling i mean i mean i don't know if you were here last night
you know it was just you know it was a weird night um i don't know if you heard about what
You know, I I have nothing personal against you or anybody. It's just like I don't like
When it's like I'm just kind of being mocked mocked outright like oh, yeah, we're taking over your channel or you're you know
You're done. You're you know
We I don't know yeah
What happened there's like a there's this couple is anyone know the name of the couple that came on there's a couple
And you know a lot of stuff happened like a lot of stuff happened, you know Alex got banned
You have to early I was got banned last night. Has he turned on me?
Joker kind of was being mean to me
Mr.. Big Pipes and were bombs show
Everyone was fighting in the chat. Oh my god. It was just bad. I had to start I had to restart the stream like so many times
It was not it was just like
just like one after the other
porn bombing and
Or is he ever just like I just felt like hated it's like because it's like you know people I like I love we're like
Hating on me. So I
Don't know what I was doing was that this is all last night. It was like or until this morning
I was up, you know, I did that I eventually ended I kept restarting until finally mr. Big Pipe's
Um and we're bombed the show and I was like, okay fuck it
I just went to bed. Hi Sam and how are you? Yeah, I just think everyone's just on my ass and it's like and
I mean, I do have there are people in the chat
looking out for me. Thank God. I like sassy scarlet and
Like a few and thing that is like there's some good mods and stuff
It was just it was a lot. Hey Sam, man
You let it rock too much
Hmm well and I say I'm there you go. It's like you that's what I you're telling me what I'm doing wrong, okay?
Yeah, what happened last night it was just I
Mean say I mean you understand like when you think you're doing a show and then you're like a hundred people
And it's like so you have a crowd right and so it's like, you know, he's like you
There's like how we're like working in a crowd you want to like have the crowd like you know getting a long happy
It's just like but people are keep trying to turn everyone against me Alex is like
St. I was saying like the worst day. I didn't do anything to Alex. Oh, I
Was I fucking sit up for Alex many times
At my expense like you know, I look stupid a lot of people left because they just and I was like, you know
I like the guy. I'll keep the guy around
His termines were no reason
So like they're really really nasty. It was yeah, who's nasty?
Yeah
And plus I had to end the show like twice because he kept saying at pay GGOT
Crystal kept saying it. I kept saying you know what I
Personally, I don't care. I used to have I used to tell out I was to call me that now. I'm like, okay. Well
You know, it's kind of like and I'm being flagged for every stupid little thing
So people are gonna look for any kind of like they can label his hate speech and say, you know
So I'm just trying to say hey don't say that on my channel. You know, and then they argue with me. Why what can I?
Or they keep saying it. I said promise not to say it out
I just just they don't say that one word he said it within a minute after I let him back on and then he fucking went on the attack on me
saying this really horrible things that's not that it's like
But maybe it's something to do astrologically because
Is it was just happening so many people
Expected from the thrills right I think it from the trolls or some people have always they always do that but
Now it's like now everyone's doing it to me so
Anyway
Yeah, so I do have some stuff to do put in the book today. So I have this book
Let's call this the notebook. This will be called a notebook. So let me see
To go in and cross the names out. Okay, so
Okay. Okay, so I
Mean I don't like to cross names out
See
That's fine or fuck it, uh, Mr. Big Pipe's his name crossed out
He's a band
Okay, I think that's the only one I have
but
Members are
Oh, Doug, please.
DC, OK, are known to kill streamers
who come along for their pleasure.
So that's what I get.
I mean, that's what.
That's the story. That's the storyline I keep hearing. It's like I just don't know why it's really a pleasure
It's just it's just fun to like watch somebody suffer. I don't know. It's fun. Just watch somebody
In a state of in a state of stress and sadness. I don't know. It's kind of kind of stick to me
Hi flirty good to see you. Yeah flirty, you know Alice's band now
You know Joker turned on me
Crystal was crystal was actually making saying that I was what a crystal say I said about her. She said I said
Just things I don't even say she said I said I called her CR ACK
WHore, which I've never done. She said I said I said that she looked like
Him like like Joe's friend. She was like you said I look like yeah, I was like what?
Obviously either like I don't remember saying that it doesn't sound like it's obviously doesn't make sense
you don't look anything I like and
So it's obviously a joke and she's oh, and she was so mad. Hi
Biggie you track and record shows you hooked up with and then try to kill like you leave. Yeah
Yeah, what happened was
You know, there's all these people and then your guys they're laughing say oh, he's like I did this I did this
Yeah, this channel done blah blah. Yeah, we're just like like laughing at me like
And then like and there's nobody hardly anybody in the chat like yesterday that one of the one of the first chess
Like everyone was from somewhere else and no one was even acknowledging me
They're always talking about this weird shit in the chat. I was like, what's going on? Yeah. Oh, yeah
And then it's just like then they do like the because they think I don't
See or something right?
All right, I don't understand
so
But
It's like when it's like in my face and it's like, okay, like I do like
Sometimes I play dumb like when you know Alex is bringing up. Oh the discord Brigade. I kind of was saying oh
It's a yeah, I was making a big joke of it. No, I mean there might be some truth to it, but I'm not gonna let on that
I
Know that or knew that
Until it was like, you know, right?
and so
Yeah, and so then
There's some people this I was dumb. I didn't get it and
openly mock me and as I when they do that they're like they don't think I
understand I do you don't try hard all you just drink the leader of those f'd up
okay okay thank you I appreciate people that actually because it's hard to
sort out friend and friend and foe sometimes because people seem to be just
Some people will just
You know, it's it's the people typing in a chat. You can type anything you can say anything
It's like I can't really see your expression or face. They can't see you like I
Can't take to the look of the stain or hate in your eyes to know that this person doesn't
But now it's kind of like it's too obvious what happens if people get too cocky about it
Damn it is meant
It means to me because he hates
Some people you like okay, Sam was saying in Tony's
He's going to use you
as his little cow
Someone was saying some or Sam and Sam and you were saying that okay
Sam and we have to say I mean, I know I say man. I know maybe it's not true, but
You can be sure I am and people are people do say that even my even pie who I love by she's my cause
She was trying to call me that because it's kind of insulting
You don't know guys a little cow is just like a streamer. And so did you say that you do you say that?
The ones that you said that you wanted to turn me into your little cow. I'm telling you server
I'm not in the server. So I know I know it's this it's a math that it says that I know I know I can't really
Believe everything I hear from people about it, but yeah, no, I've heard it before I've seen it before
Okay, you didn't say that
It's just like I mean all it is is it's one of the stupid new derogatory things is just basically
Kind of like along the IP2 audience by the locale, you know, even at least it gets called to get called a whore cow
H-O-R-R-O our cow and the other people people that are just streamers. It's basically
People wanting to laugh at people
Don't you see once JT and on where it always came around it's the vibe has changed even JT
Rain yesterday gotty yesterday. Don't you see they always turn it against you and they think you're dumb. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, I said that's what I was exactly what I'm saying. It's like I was reading it
I know I love
In the chat, it was going crazy in the chat. I'm not watching it and the models was
I was reading everything that I was just I was just observing I was watch I was reading the entire chat
So I saw everything that was said, okay?
I was I was off panel most of time so and I was kind of like not acting like I was reading it
But you know, I do see the chat and I was seeing what they were saying and I was like, okay
Well, they're just like now there's
Ruby in my face laughing at me, and it was like, you know, and then it wasn't only them because then it was Alex turn on me and
Yeah, you weren't there. I didn't leave all the screens because you know, mr.. Big
So you that that you let Alex do whatever you want. I've been so you don't like to be on panel with Alex because
It's not even content is dumb
Yeah, sometimes I'll be here with you by myself with you. I'm chilling. I don't like to I just not always a cook all the time
I could chill a lot. Yeah, I'm always honest. I'm gonna tell you how it is. I'm not
Psych I don't need to use you psych. I just be killing. Yeah. Yeah, I mean
I know I mean, I really like at the end of the day
I don't care if people what people want to call me when I call me if they call me a little cow or like
I'm a joke or whatever
People know I have a note people coming in I'll have people that support me and love me and will look out for me
I don't care. I don't care. It's like you would laugh at me laugh laugh with me
I don't I don't feel feel the hate or the love really
So yesterday I was getting called PDF in your shit or non-stop yesterday. No, I'm sorry. I mean, it's a everyone was I mean
That's the same group. Yeah, that's what they started getting the status scarlet started timing them all out and say stop saying that because they kept
saying it all in different ways and then and then you know, then they would be playing and I'd be like
Well, I have exactly been my like a top mod like she knows what she's doing
She's enforcing the rules and so it just like stops saying that.
And all it was is time out.
Hey, Ziggy.
Hey, what's up, man?
Need the other word, though.
Ziggy comes from our community.
He got pushed over.
I don't come from your community.
I do not come from your community.
You fuck around.
You orbit.
Now, I want you to say mine's from my community.
Oh, man, you come from fucking.
No, we invaded you with fucking ETC.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah.
You with fucking
And I'm the one that got Q running nigga, you couldn't do nothing to you
You hang with
Man, he wanted fucking
15 you hang with
You love it. You love it. You don't like it. You don't mark him out.
You don't mark him out.
He knows what I'm saying is you want my cue, but you don't mark out the 15 out.
Man, shut up. What are you doing?
What are you doing? Talking about them up here?
Whenever fucking they care.
Dude, I've talked to you or nobody used to argue with him all the time.
I said, I remember you.
You so are you an emperor? I'm talking to Psyche right now. Come on, man
Psyche. What's up?
This motherfucker dude, he came up at ETC and he fucking thinks that he's on a branch off and fucking take over your shit
That's what he's doing fucking long story short
He's putting down Gotti and fucking JT in them
They'll say shit about anyone, but they really on the backside of things man. They fucking
told me
You dig suck and grow men again. No, that's what happened. No
Only weirdos only weirdos called people pds with no paperwork JT Gotti
rain
Don't worry. I'm getting them one by one ziggie one by one. I already got ready
Already got ready already got ready already got ready
Imagine imagine saying I
Need psych for cloud nigga. You bet you haven't been watching me nigga. Have you been watching me lately?
I'm good
You're popular you're popular streamer
I'm on my second channel chilly nigga
Second channel you got you already got that busted the first one Jesus. No my friend my main one is still good
I need to support my second channel
Busted they got my main channel still lit over 2,000 subs
Well, that's good man
Is that is that how you treat somebody whenever fucking they say congratulations
Hey, man, you just dig suck nigga used to argue with Amber
Oh, you're big as out. She was your biggest out. Look look how I got you running. That is kid. It never do that
There you go
No
You even scared to be G would you like your channel now? I don't need a look it's like when I ever
You know me if I use for psych only drop my second channel one time because
I stopped stop using my main channel site when I ever dropped my channel like that when
No, just when you started last night when you started using it again. I mean, I don't mind
When I started using my second channel, I said say I'll drop my second channel and your chat
That's the only time I did it
Like before I left you before she got crazy you fucking dropped the day
Yeah, okay
Shinnin's community war diggy. Oopsie. No, no
You hang with weirdo so you weirdo too don't fuck. I'm not a weirdo
JT's a weirdo
So JT do the JT I banned last night because I just remember like, you know
He said let me remember he said that you're a weak channel owner psyche like it
Consulting me like to share my face. I'm just your and then the body was saying. Oh, you have no spy your week
And then they're just saying all this stuff
They call you weak because you don't set them down calling people PDFs
That's gonna rule my chat to the beginning is like
It was all that that all that was a body rain rain
And they're calling everybody in the chat it there's everyone's name
They're like why would he find out and sassy wore them she's like stop saying that and I kept they kept doing it
Like I got it I got to be honest rain don't even talk
Most of the time she said it
She's seen it. I chose like look at the chat. She called she said it on panel. She called people PDF on panel
What the fuck you talk about? I got the clip
I told you it's facts nigga. I got the clip
Stupid fuck man. They got it for people. You don't even know them
Crystal Marie shit, shut the fuck up. I know I mean Crystal Marie was coming up with like
She was saying I called her a crack W. H. O. R. E. And I was
These people weirdo just doing it just for like for a cloud
I don't know it's weird
GT GT and I'm on weirdos. I'll be telling you that I looked at his community wall
I looked at his people been talking about him. These people like to bring that weirdo shit around
I don't know what it is. Pam Goddy rain
Okay, it's weird shit as in like, you know, like, you know, JT. There's a thumbnail of a disabled
like minor on
Posting other YouTube streamers with a minor JT. That's the miners. Yes, it is
I wouldn't hear
Go check his community wall you dumb maggot go check his community right now you go see the minor right now go
Go ahead. Go leave don't leave the panel right now and go check his community you all I don't have to leave
You've got a look all right there. All right. Thank you. Shut the fuck up. You just want to protect the weirdo
You just want to protect the weirdos now. We got it
Post-it miners we got it is fucking crazy, man. How can you do that? I said I wasn't here
I got some content. I like to expose the weirdos like yeah
Like although I didn't lead all the streams last night. And so, you know, I don't know if anyone's up to anything
But it was it was like it was crazy like the way it started out like there's nobody in the chat that I knew it was like everybody with
God he had brought everybody here or something and they're just saying weird stuff and like you're kind of not talking to me
Which is I was talking to the panel
And then they started to like say, oh, well, we're taking over the chat. Look what I did is he's like I did I claim as well
Well, you're laughing. Oh your channel's done and I was and they're just like blade and then everyone else was kind of like
It just kind of poisoned the atmosphere. It kind of and I just it was all night. It was a kind of fight, but
Um
What I'm saying is the same man doesn't understand. I'm sorry to cut you off man
What I'm saying though is to show same man like that's out of their character. I had already left. I know I didn't see
That's all I don't love it. It turns out that there's a noble. Yeah noble noble song, right? Noble's watching
Yeah
It's funny that he's trying to like try to erase what JT and God he does
Ziggy knows what God is
Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don't talk to people. Don
I said, can you play as I can you play and I had to ask that's why JT kept the modded because
he kept doing that and I kept saying stop doing it.
Imagine bullying a catcher patient and pull and post in her
cancer scars. OK, all right.
Say, man, my point is real quick, I don't fucking do that stuff.
But
Right now
You forgot your lame nigga, I don't know who hiked you up
I'm not the one and you can either I'm posting minors on the community wall. Why are you going to go watch it?
Go to JT's community, you don't want to face the facts, weirdo.
You're not listening to me.
I don't need to listen to the weirdos.
You were the one that fucking was trying to get what's
like in what's your name, don't weirdo.
I'm first staying here for a little while.
I'm going to roll up, start your youth for setting up business.
But what I'm saying is, is that, that's how they are.
That's how they are, man.
Yeah, you finally open your eyes.
You finally open your eyes.
Anything that JT has ever done.
GT has ever put a picture up of anybody. It's because they put themselves up there. Yeah, okay. Yeah, it's a minor too
And also in the other guy the guy last night the guy came with his wife, and he was like he was talking about he's like how he's been being
And you always say, you know, yeah, he said that he saw someone told him
That's okay JT uses his daughter daughter daughter, but is that wait wait wait? Who's it wrong?
John
Thank you, thank you. So JT's not wrong for posting a minor on his community wall
I mean he just reposted what Jarl put up
Thank you now. I'm gonna clip that forever at clip and ship. Thank you. So J
He is cool. Oh
Ziggy is cool for posting minors. No problem. Hey do you?
No put his own minor
Okay, so it's okay to post a minor again
That's a kid you talking about a kid you talking about a kid you talking about a kid
You're talking about it. Why did y'all do that? Okay? Are you talking about a kid? Okay?
Hey, hey, you know where I did that. Uh-huh. JT. You support me. I am weird. Oh, did it all right?
And JT posted it and JT made it later here. Mm-hmm. Hey, are you here? Can you say something?
I have to pick up to see you
Okay, he's not responding so I mean if you responded better if you're not gonna respond
I can't kill you in the town. That's enough said. Hey, that's why Ziggy fuck with JT now
We understand site. Why'd he get along?
Ziggy don't see the wrong bar post
Minor
I'm talking about
That if you even you're like me if I post a chicken
And fucking
Picture so so so if I so if I post my child if I post my three-year-old
It's okay. So if it was they get a post my three-year-old cheese without what
Parents are allowed to have their children under on our YouTube stream like there's
Thank you, so it's like don't need to explain
He's defending JT for post in a minor
There's a lot and there's what's right and wrong because
And he say jail uh jar is abused in his minor not only that posting a case a cancer patient scars. That's more than
And she's in the chat and she's in the chat Hannah is in the chat. We're doing that and you're using her
Yeah, oh hell no that's sick enough, but wait wait wait here. We go again. Didn't she post those cars up?
You go ahead don't worry about it. He likes to defend it
I don't use anybody
Even if I post up I don't use their image
Like you think somebody post a somebody post a parent and they passed away you think I'm going to post it. No
It's called being morals
Like you how many times Q post my mom's do I call do I post Q moms? Never never at all
It's called being human have a moral yourself
Now you're going from legality to being more
Yeah, okay, no, you like weirdo shit
You like weirdo shit
No, there's more and there's legality
That's what I'm saying
I can't your patient
No, I'm not okay with it
You gotta be with your patient
Because I haven't died from cancer
Alright, so JT that
So they see that but if the cancer patient is
Dummy nobody post the cancer patients
Let's get you post your art then stop complaining let's get you
Yeah, let's let's get you put your arm your uncle Facebook, right? Let's eat he have it
Give me your own face
Fucking he takes it and that's fair
What if he goes onto your Facebook and then like you know finds you know people and then like then then take
That right there that that is stealing
That's people. No. No, he doesn't know it doesn't get people. He look up people. That's why I'm on his ad
Oh, that's why I don't you know what? That's why I find his girl salute shout out to rain in Texas
Keep talking Ziggy. I mean, I just think it's like so in defense. It's like it's like nothing
I think even if it was all legal and stuff. I say don't do that on my show and they continue to do it like
Okay, all right, all right, we can we agree all of us can we agree with this it is immortal to do that
Absolutely
And put their own pictures up
Those people are kind of the evil doing it
He wanted a great kid
We're attacking the show, do you understand, Ziggy?
There's a problem I have is like, I don't care.
Like you guys, I mean, I don't think with this, right?
What you guys are doing, but it's like that you come on my channel
and try to bring it all here.
Let them put it on their own platform.
Yeah, and it's like he and I don't even know.
No, and well, because you know, you guys are all kind of a group.
But yeah, y'all was like, when he saw his photo
being used on my channel, like as a thing.
He was going to strike my channel,
but he saw that I was like, I said it out.
Let me, let me, in fact.
I'll go I could get this live right now. No matter what I could clip this shout to Ziggy. Thank you, Ziggy. You just give me content
Like you defended that shit. Hey salutes, man. I got the content now
Shout to you
it was just it was just why they get out.
I don't want you around.
I noticed that why people don't want you around Ziggy.
I never peeped that far.
Now I see why.
What? You're a Crop Baby, man.
All right. Hey, don't play me.
I'm gonna let my chat decide.
Why is everybody saying that?
Ew.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
No, JT's the only one that called me Crop Baby and me Gotti.
The same ones that called people Peter.
Hey, there's Bunky.
Yes.
I mean, I try you know, I'm one person and when it but it's like when the whole it's like it's kind of was derailing my
Entity the entire chat and then you know
And that was maybe was what they're trying to do and they there is like you know God is like oh, I love this
I love I love I did this
I love this drama and stuff and it's like so and it's a kind of laughing at my face about how we would guess hold on a second
Hi
Hello
Good I'm fucking great, but I'm still thinking of you on yesterday. I'm thinking of you. Thank you. I
Feel bad for you guys who you
Okay, I'm okay
I'm not from anyone's community from my own world. I'm just coming here to bring positive vibes, and I want you guys to just chill out and
Like this short everybody just stop the shit, you know and just just get along
Yeah, that's what I would love. I would love that it's like some people like to think they thrive on the conflict and they like
They don't cause me
Look, I was sitting here, and I was thinking I was like man all y'all just need to get out
Just get out look look at this
Yeah, there you go. That's beautiful
Yeah, yeah, that's Florida
Virginia I look like more than like Virginia doesn't I I'm not telling you where I'm from
She's afraid she'd see a dark shadow walk up on her
There's so much like complete even from my friends last night and then she came and like was just like kind person
It's like she's the kind of person that keeps me going
Yeah, I don't thank you and I you know
This is a little reminder from the universe that like this is all just the internet and it's bullshit and like get out
Get on the world put your feet in the grass like
I am not married, but I should be okay, so you single or
Simon you hit on everything stop
Don't hit on me my heart's taken forever
Okay, I'm just asking questions. This is
The look I said back are you trying to enjoy the content we just asking questions you know, he's enjoying it to your sake
He is playing he's just doing his thing man, and this is what it's about
So what life's about is about human contact and positive connections
We need to stop making these negative connections just for entertainment to keep our pulses up or whatever it goes man
Like there's better than this, you know
Like let's let's enjoy the good things about each other
Yeah, right. I just I just I feel like I feel like a lot of a lot of people might have been you know
Victim of not if not that big it's like you know people attacking channels and stuff like that and a lot of people are feel helpless and they
You know, but I've actually I want to be actually someone that stands up to some of these people and I'll actually shows
I have people that will stand up for me too and not just not to like lay down and like have them be another like victim
They can laugh at I don't feel like
Just being a victim and like or they're saying I'm just I'm just collateral damage in their fights. Like I'm not really for their
They don't care
unintentionally were and you know life is about
Peace human connection kindness serenity. What can you do for somebody else?
What can you do to help the world? Like when you tap into that energy like karma karma helps and pays you off tenfold
it does
They really does like I'm not real religious, but when I was like, hey, what can I do to help other people? My life's got a lot better
Yeah, that's and
And I've been you know, that's not that is like like like you know
We were so like you said competing and turning each other down and fighting against each other
It's like we'd be so much more powerful as we came together and like help each other
You mean before United
If we're just like not trying to attack each other and take other people out and look at
everyone's competition and just want to or just for our own like.
I don't know everyone keeps saying it's for the they just do it for their for laughs or
It's funny and some kind of weird like entertainment for the moment
But that they don't realize that the damage that it can do to people for a long time
Like it's hurtful and you know not not saying this is anybody on this channel
But like god forbid someone's in such a bad place mentally. This is their last straw like that would be fucking terrible
Yeah, I mean, yeah
I get what you're saying. Yeah. Yeah, when people bring in their their outside lives and drama that sometimes
It's just like the last fucking thing and who needs that man like don't you want to be someone's hero?
Don't you just want to like make their day? I
Am Samman's hero
That's
Comment comment in the chat. I'll wrench you
Just to protect you in the chat I mean because you know I do and you do like you you do show that you are an ally and it's like, you know
You know, I don't have a good heart. The channel was about helping people. You know, that's I do care
I like I am into like spiritual growth and these kind of things and I understand part of it
There's gonna be conflict and there's a lot of different people and there's gonna be conflict
But I ultimately want to bring people together and I have brought a lot of people together
And I think that's why I'm like, you know, just just on your vibe, you know
I think that's why you're you're making me think about you and worry about you and
Want to you know, I'm out here like having my little beach day, and I'm like I wonder how he's doing right now, you know
That's well, thank you
Yeah, thank you. I'm okay. I'm okay. It's like I'm just like it's gonna be more determined to
Um, take more control over things, you know, I've just been like letting people kind of run wild
I've just been doing a lot of observing because hey, what's up guy?
I've been doing a lot of observing because I want to because I've been told a lot of things that I want people to like say it for
Themselves rather than
Oh, that's great, and there are people
And so, cool, let him
Oh well, I know, guys, guys, welcome off, I have no problem with Gotti, like, and it's like, you know, he was
Gotti can explain himself to the same man
Yeah
I mean no scared of nobody
Shut the fuck up smack the shit out of you pussy. Hold on
Let me introduce my CEO
Shouting residing in Texas where everything is big. No homo. No, diddy born in Detroit
Representing the brisquad
D-frog clicked up with Janak with you true broom gang
og troop
He is slow but not the not the brainpower with the movement you drop him on his back
He gonna fall in his shell or what he do is spin spin spin who that nigga? He my twin twin twin
Shout out to Barry the motherfucking turtle salutes, my nigga
About that positive shit nobody
Maybe that's why I'm here.
Someone needs a little pause.
No, no, you need to you need to turn you turn your camera off
and enjoy the view and stop fucking around with people on here
about that positive shit.
We don't give a fuck about that shit.
How do you look at this?
What's happening right now?
And Psyche, why don't you tell her,
you want her to preach positivity over here.
Tell her about the fish tacos you be having
when you be doing that blow.
Um, Barry
From the group from Barry and tell and tell her about the dick pic I sent in my hairy ass
Yeah, it's not even yours. I did reverse eat Google images search. You're not that
And why you got that fucking manly bitch in chat with the wrench time and people out man
for no reason for her own 30
diamonds is a mod here and you
know she did she never well you
know she never said like you
know how you were talking about
me bad on another channel man
same as quiet not your mod.
Now let the content contest
stupid.
Hey, people shouldn't be taking their own personal beef style on people in the chat. Yeah. Well, that's the that's why
Yeah, have have have have have have dusty diamond fucking donated to you ever
I know I have
Three diamond is you know, uh, has referred people for terror readings and no
How does she fucking refer people? She only get two views her views. She gets
Clumsy
She has but she's the people come in
I'm her friend. What John?
Um, it was no, I don't I won't say the name but yeah, she brought a friend that
Okay, she brought one person. She brought one person. Did they pay for that reading?
Well
Even bringing people to the chat even bring sharing my life, I appreciate get the fuck out of here man site
When I came over here, you only had 10 people
You only had 10 people in your chat
Okay, well, I just started I just started when you first came right
Did I not bring you over here
Yeah, but you brought people that were kind of in the chat stuff, right? Yeah, but I mean, yeah
I mean some people but there's been good and bad people that have been brought
But a lot of the lot of people here are just for the for the for the bullshit like that is here for
That's a community to touch yourself to when you was when you when you started taking beta's panel and fucking with beta
That was the community that was attached to her
Barry let me tell you one thing. I Barry. I never I never said anything bad about you or did any I
Should be attacked. I mean, I can be attacked by a lot of people that I've never attacked. I don't so I don't get it like
I don't attack people. It's like not my thing. It's like I'm
I'm not an attacker. I'm like, oh, it's like sometimes I get mad
I'll say things, and I always regret them if I lose my temper.
And it's like, I feel like somebody get me out of my house.
No, but you got mad at me, you got mad at me because I said your nails were still dirty and they were
Yeah, but you said, you said, oh, he's digging through his ass and he's a wiper
I mean, you're saying it in a really disgusting way, man
Just like, just like really disgusting way, it wouldn't just say, oh, everyone says my nails are dirty
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, but you're like, you like had to get into like, disgusting details
Alex and every, like they just have to say
All I said, all I said, it's like, all I said was you probably using cheap tissue and will you wipe your ass, your fingers
I heard, I heard, it didn't sound any better this time.
Okay, yeah, I got, I'm saying I was, I was just assuming, man.
That don't mean it was true.
I was just assuming, man.
No, you're assuming incorrectly and I was kind of like just a mean thing. You're my mod of the time
That's a thing. It's like you're my mod
You're so you're in my stuff like learning my chat and then you're not talking shit about me like now is like, okay
Well, I sort that I have to like say, okay
Well, if I have a mod as a mod at least can't be talking shit about me another channel and like I'm a joke, right?
Look man
Okay, I want to be friends. I mean, I have nothing against people. I mean, so I guess people like, you know, I don't care if they really apologize as long as, you know,
If I come if I come to California, man, you got to give up your bed and you got you got to sleep standing up
Okay
Can I sleep at the edge of the bed and watch you no, no, you didn't you got to sleep standing up facing the wall
I might I might
If you wake him in the lab getting I'm getting in it with you don't
Things the fucking kid would do that no
Hey, he could take he could take my you could take that says I'd be using that
Yeah
Right here. This is awesome guy. He's a streamer and he's on the show
I'll tell you if you go to Doug D. No, I'm not Doug D. I'm not Doug D
I'm Dougie Doug. I'm Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Dougie Doug
because he's trying to use my name and make people think he's made
I don't know why there was a
rapper baby. I don't know.
Uh huh. Hello, I jam. What are
you living? What's going on?
What's up? Oh, fuck yeah.
He's driving around.
Fuck yeah.
He said, what are you doing?
You in the truck? You in the
truck? You in the truck?
Fuck yeah. You in the
truck, baby? I'm
sitting in my attic.
Oh, that's just shit.
Oh, it's out of the book.
Is somebody named Pab staying with you?
Yeah.
Thank you.
What's up?
Oh
Okay, that's
Never told me I looked like John Goodman before
You got a whole bunch of celebrities up here, you got John Goodman, you got Elegant Generous.
You got the ooze off of Dada you eat, you got Al Borland from fucking Tool Time.
I think
Dugass I'm sorry, but you guys
What does look like
Oh
We want to see slow-motion.
Damn.
Okay.
Oh, she buckled.
Damn.
Oh, my God.
Damn, buddy.
That's how I am.
She got the cake.
She got the cake cities.
Thank you.
You got the big old watermelons, I like that too, it's more, I like it, it's good.
On the beats too, I'm jealous, ooh.
I have a couple of questions.
Oh man, damn, Dusty, come on man, Dusty.
Move on. Okay about you
Chat what you how you want them because I'm not I don't time I'm not gonna do anything as a moderator
Yeah, because why because it's not my chat and they're talking. Yeah, and if you don't like it, you'll fucking do something, right?
Is that the right? Yeah, yeah, but if I say people unless people are like doxing or like they're everything and then just delete the comment
Maybe like I just you know
So this is my question, straight up, right?
In DVDs, does a man need to take your wife to the beach
and she won't get off the gay man's YouTube channel?
you don't you don't need me to remove that or no no i don't care i don't care that's a no i don't
Yeah, well, Dougie, Dougie, it's kind of evolved.
I used to like-
Unlike the racism's funny.
No sexism, unless the sexism's funny.
And no cost like you.
Well, it's not, it was, it's not,
I really don't find racism or sexism very funny.
It's like, you know, it's like some people's like-
It's like, that's not even a human ratio.
That is okay. Okay. I say I say I say
I want to like
Mods to be on my channel style
I want me my channel side and watching out for the channel not just looking out for themselves and under personal benefits
I mean their enemies out. I want I want I don't care what they say about me
I was wondering about a general policy about like his comment about that gay guys panel
Yeah, it's fine. I don't care. He's a gay guy. He didn't say F-A-G-G-O-T, so it's not a big deal.
He said it in an appropriate way. I don't get offended. I don't get offended by any other stuff.
The only reason I have rules is because it's for T-O-S, and I'm under attack, too.
You're pretty chill, too, Bodd and Psyche, too, because I mean, how many people have rolled into live chats and been like,
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Look at the chops on that guy.
There's a point on the key.
Yeah.
Nice job.
We've been doing that for years, though. They love it.
Yeah
Hey, Kate. How are you?
It's nice to know that they care enough, right? Because the worst thing that can happen is to be ignored
But I mean, yeah, I'd rather, you know, rather have, but at the same time, it's like I'd rather have like a few
people in my chat that were, you know, being positive and having a conversation rather than like a hundred people that are just all
trolling and causing all this chaos. I mean, it's like, you know, there's time for both things, but
my responsibility to reign in my show
is hard. It's hard. It's hard.
It takes two people who cause chaos. If one person to be in stupid and everybody ignores them, that's not a problem.
It's when you start responding to the stupidity that the chaos begins.
Yeah, and then people in chat will respond to it people. That's why it's finally the meeting attack. It's like a lot of people
Red spunky
Have fun. Thank you. Thank you so much
Yeah
Whatever you do. Yeah, have a wonderful. Thank you so much. Thank you for other than the beach. We have another beach
Round the beach. Yeah, there's a beach right here. Here we go. There's a beach
Dorado, that's El Dorado. Yeah, it's El Do
I mean, I was like, it was a little bit, you know, I just kind of feel like when my channel
is under attack, I get my, you know, it gets offensive and stuff, so, I don't know, I don't
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
People can force you to respond to their comments.
I got I got I got I got you right there. Oh, she left. I can't tell me for this shit. She left. God. I'm sorry
My god, yeah
So, yeah, thank you all for joining me. Yeah
But you know, I just
Like I like I said my channel is like, you know, I really haven't been very successful in my in my life
And it haven't really done things for a long time. This is like one of my first
I've been building this channel. It's like I've worked probably harder than anything in my life. I really like I really loved it
I love doing it. It's like my passion. It's like I want to do it and
And so it's also like my baby because I you know, I built it up for my
Everyone
Listen to Sam and
So it's like it's like it's like, you know, you wouldn't like leave your bait or your baby
I ban JT and you know God I
You're saying to me that I didn't kick her I think oh JC
I don't know God. I don't appreciate some of the things you were saying and I don't know if you're it was trying to be funny
Or you really think they don't like me like that cuz you're kind of saying the same things that he was saying like I
Have no spine
You know JT
You who you asking me I'm asking you yeah
Do I know
Duggity is doggie. Hold on. So all it don't come from the same universe Shannon you
I don't hang out with those guys, but they don't orbit around you, right?
They don't orbit around me, yeah, but I don't hang out with those guys.
Okay.
Shalooch.
All right.
Now we go.
We go.
What are you saying?
Shut your fat mouth.
He's talking.
What are you talking?
What are you saying?
Appreciate what?
Okay, and I would you say you said you said how you said I was weak. I have no spine and
Yeah, you type that
If I said that then it must have been true at the time
Thank you. Thank you. And I said, anybody that, yeah, thank you. I, I, if you, if it's an apology, I accept it. And, uh, or, you know, I'm cool with you. That's the thing is like, of course, if it bother you, I mean, it's like, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if you, if
At the time, it must have applied.
And it's like if you say it's one thing but then but then dates, you know dates you kind of like
Man
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Psychic
Yeah, yeah, I just like I like to you know
I just like have like to be at least respected on my own show
I mean if I if you have people other places you can say that to me
But it's like you know insulting me at my own show, and I'm really trying hard to like
Do the best and I know I can't be everywhere happy, but I'm trying to be respectful and fair and
You want me to kiss your fucking ass on the panel on my channel and I'm
there you go wow laughing my face laughing my face okay god I mean it's
funny it's funny it's funny it's a show is this thing you just kind of like
you're not laughing about you okay are you laughing gas I don't know you're
laughing at the Joker I'm a hinge
You gotta stop. You gotta stop. You gotta stop with this shit. You gotta stop with this shit. It's too funny.
So, Sike, this is what I find. Anytime somebody comes to you and tells you shit about someone else...
You're lying to you. They're not trying to help you. Oh my god. He's talking to you like you're a child. He's not a fucking child.
Oh, this person is a pedo and this person did that. Yeah. They're all lying. I know. I know. I know.
That's J.T. Dottie. That's J.T. Dottie. He's talking about you. He's talking about you. That's all of them.
I don't call people PDS. Yes, you do. Every day.
It's just like, it's not
show about, you know, that's
where you going, man? I'm
going camping, baby. I can't
wait. I can't wait when I
back there. We go. We go
JT live with his parents
Talk about week
I mean, I don't like anybody be called names.
I would be full respect because I got called names by people I really like I care about
and like Alex and you know Joker were like teasing me last night or they said they were
trolling, you know, Joker said he was trolling me.
Alex was just like trying to attack me and these are people that I consider friends and
so it's like my friends are saying that it's like.
That really I mean, I don't care what trolls
Week because I was in a wheelchair
So I know what it means to be called me. I would never call somebody weak, you know by the grace of God. I walk now
I can walk again. Okay. Okay. Yeah, I would never say that about
I don't do drugs. I'm sorry. I don't do fucking drugs. I know you said that before yeah, I don't do that shit
So shout to you psych. All right. I can step off. You're like, I'll be back. Thanks man. Thanks. Talk to you. See you Sammy. Yeah
Nice seeing you
Good to see you, man. Nice seeing you on panel, Dougie. Shout to you. Oh, absolutely
Thank you, Doug. Thank you, Doug. I appreciate you coming
So
Yeah, I mean I don't mind people going back and forth having like a little fun and like yeah
And Howard Stern they were called like goofing on each other like they were goofing on each other
And that's like that's like fine
And it's like kind of like you know the person's kind of in on it what happens here is like this like it's like this
Evil trolling and it's like when it gets in the dog thing it gives me people's family
They get to the kids when it gets into a slandering and and then just derailing the whole like using my platform basically is like a
WWF reading it or something when I'm trying to
Have a fun show and then all these people are poor by me everyone. It's just like I'm trying to run the show
It's some people just have to let me do my thing. All right, you don't have to apologize. We understand
Keep it fair, that's all keep it fucking fair
No, it's your channel
They say they say keep it fair. I need a chance to they all say that
Yeah
That's what happens like that. You know, I've been doing this for a while
So you were like six months probably with the chats and it's like people
If a mod time does over just it. Oh my god, why do you time up for 10 sec?
And they'll cry about it for like for like hours instead of the 10th
And it's like they keep going and it's like
Who are you?
I have flex shows. I have an R-type of flex show.
I guarantee there's a fucking, there's a novel that Psyche's got, a graphic novel of me and my shirt off.
I don't be close to what I say on the wall.
You didn't hurt my feelings when you said I mumble shit under my breath. I talk evil shit. What is that all about?
Remember what I said? Sometimes you'll be like, you'll be like saying all this weird shit and I'll be like,
he's on Doom Talks.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, you said you didn't like that.
You didn't like that.
What are you doing?
Isaiah, what the fuck?
There you go.
It was already brought up.
I mean, it's a little toasty in the trunk.
Oh my gosh.
There you go, man.
I
Love you know you know Doug goes and sees men across the country, right? Oh
If you're lucky, okay, I'm not kidding
I flirty
Like a flirty diamond. He's all over the place
Yeah, I'm here something last night
Oh my gosh, it was so funny. Mr. Big Pipe, Mr. Big Pipe was like, hey, wait, hey, yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna,
Oh my god, he played this Beatles song. How many times did he play the Beatles song?
He played it for, it must have been two hours in the background and this, like, is it,
then one time he was, like, yelling and his microphone was, like, on, like, one per, like,
one, uh, one volume and he was just yelling in the back for hours. He finally endbombed me last
night and said, that's my show, so Mr. B pipes your band, I prostrate it out of my book.
Okay, yeah
He and we're bombed the only one I mean there's a million people do it every day to you
Yeah, but he was like he annoyed me up up before
It'd be okay
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's a hard ER. It's a hard y'all
Like you know it's part of the vernacular person
I don't really care. It's like the thing is it's like when people say like the hard ER is to take a different kind of like
thing to it. It's just like a nap. It's just like a nap.
It depends how you set it. It depends the context.
You use it on there, right?
Yeah, but I know you 100 dollars
to bring it back.
It can be a negative thing. It can be both.
You can tell someone
To bring him back and JT back. How about that? I would I would
Even I know I could I could bring them back, but they're gonna do the same thing. It's like, you know, it's like you get rid of them again
Yeah, okay, I mean I
Mr. Big Pipe's I would give another chance and I would just be if he would just perform and not not really thought talk and you know
But it's like I just don't like these people. I don't trust I just don't trust like what they've been doing
Mr. Big Pipe's is like just like really a panel killer
And you see I mean
I like it too, but it really takes him like five hours to warm up and he doesn't know the songs he's just learned
And so we know it doesn't he's learning the guitar when he played it last night. It was just it was messy last night
If there's anyone here last night when you should be pipes was on it was it was just it was insane
Yeah, people were just like stop. It's like nobody ever was like
Nobody wanted to hear it. Nobody was a musician, but his microphone sucks and it's like it doesn't sound good and stuff
so
You need a musical act. You don't have a musical act.
Minnie Manson, you know, comes on.
What?
What is he playing?
Minnie Manson sings and plays guitar.
He played the guitar.
I missed that. I'm sorry.
It's the first appearance.
He came on my show. He played guitar.
Can you hear me here, Alice?
We hear you. We want to see you, Dougie.
But on the panel, I'm frozen right as you know, I mean, it's a black screen, but I hear
We don't need to see you
Yeah, keep it
Are we still here you so it must be a so happily working
Why not I work in mysterious ways, you know
God, are you are you are you like either one's monitor stop messing with you was my area. Thank you God. Thank you for coming back on
Okay
um
Yeah, you have a card. So you see of course you can have a card. I guess we beat your car that posted
Sweet we like a card so who asked for a card
3P in the chat
Yeah, come on guys yelling each other. Yeah. Yeah. I'm program. I'm a fire the whole reprogramming staff and I'm taking back to control. Okay, so
Okay, okay, so we have
You're the nine of wands. Okay, nine of wands. This is you know, the sign of ones and who is that?
That's the evil queen in the mirror. Okay, so nine of wands
It's traditionally a person carrying like you know these big things nine long sticks
It's like carrying a lot of burdens
they're carrying other people's burdens taking on things that are not really your energy and and
Taking on the energy of other people trying to help so just remember it's like you don't have to carry everybody else's burdens
you can put down the load and and
stretch and you know
Maybe get some people to help and all kinds of things rather than doing everything on your own because but don't take everything on your own
I think that you
You take on a lot a lot from other people and a lot of their birds, okay?
So I'll be like that
Okay, I can read from the book actually nine of wands. I'll just read from the book real quick because this looks kind of kind of a
You know Disney themes. Let's see nine of wands
Okay, the nine of wands says
Okay, nine of one says
Sorry, okay
That's your car sweepy
Nine of one's says nine of one's
Advises you now at the time to put up your guard if your experiencing challenges lay low to
conserve your energy and
Resources remember you're not alone in this don't be afraid to ask for help if you need it. Yeah, ask for helps you
Oh, thank you. Doug said to kick him off easy. He left his panel. Okay. Okay. He's gone. There you go
Can you do me? Can you get me one of those cards from the other deck? Do you have the other deck available? Sure. Sure.
What's it called again? The Rider Waite?
Rider Waite, yeah. I got the, I'll get my uh, my Rider Waite. Hold on. Okay.
This is my gold tone Rider. Okay.
This will be my card for the day. This will set the tone right here.
Do you want me to shuffle a certain amount of time? Yeah, four shuffles will do.
Okay.
You got it or is a specific number of shows you the reason for three
Okay, gotcha. You know the number four is a symbol for death in the Asian culture
Well, it's also in the you know four is like the fourth letter of the alphabets
That's the D and then it's like D kind of looks like a two stone half way
It's also like a doorway. I mean, it's also D is litter for death, right?
I left it's death. Okay. Oh, okay. Oh my gosh. Okay. So Gotti you got the best card in the deck
This is the sun card. This is like good things happening like a lot of positivity
It's like the sun coming out especially after maybe a dark night. It's like, you know things getting better
It's a very positive card. It's the most positive card in the deck. It's just good tidings. It's a very, it's a good, it's a good omen, okay?
Perfect. Stop bringing light wherever I go. It's like, you see that?
Yeah.
Don't you feel bad now? Call me negative?
Oh, well, you know what? It's like, you know, I like you. I like you guys. You know, I like you and it's like, that's why it's like, you know, I always...
No
Most of people that I I like
Either never liked me or have turned on me and
On panel psyche don't take it serious if I say, okay
I'm glad I was able to inspire in some way JT's the same way. I don't think he would give you a shit on the panel
I mean, it's like, you know, I'm a very forgiving person and it's like, you know, I just need to make sure people are really following, following what I asked at least, you know, because it's just, it's going out of control and then people are like actually like getting off on breaking the rule.
I need to like, you know, you just need to have like a zero tolerance policy because they're like, oh, we can get away with anything over there.
We can stay a million times here.
He'll keep forgiving us.
I am very forgiving.
When I was like, you know, when I was in my motion always forget so I'm forgetting I will forget
Yeah, I got I'm so up in the link. I need to pin the link. I'm sorry. I have my phone is on the table
Can you show the road? Can you show the road instead of show the road? Yeah. Yeah, I mean don't talk to yourself or anything
But just show the road
Don't don't crash. Oh, there you go. That's nice
That's cool
But no wait, where you go in the woods
Yeah, yeah property out in the middle of fucking just middle of fuck off nowhere
Yeah, it's good to get lost in the woods. Sometimes it's a charge my phone. I'm sorry my link is the link isn't a chat
I have to wait for my phone to charge before I was in the here's so you back
Just be clear with everybody's like let them know that anybody that times me out will be banned from the channel
You know, I think
Yo, hey psyche, I just want to ask you one request man. You don't have to it's okay
But you can always monitor me if you want. Can I please?
everybody's blue down there, and I can't protect myself
I
I was thinking I would mod God first before you and I'm not really even in which of my God today
Mods if he didn't if he gets timed out and he didn't do anything just time up for 10 seconds
It'll bring him right back. Okay, and it's like, you know
It's just unprotected, I mean, it's like I had no condom, you know, like it's like, you want to be able to trash people with impunity, right?
I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out. I'm not gonna time you out
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I have a problem with any of the mods that I see in the chat today and they're looking
out for me either.
You just took it away from me.
I have a few problems with some of your mods and I'm the only white one down there.
I mean I don't care.
You just took it away.
I said in the chat, I said I'd rather have you have a.
I can seal I can seal the wrench like you know, I like I want you to like
Like come on help me
I can't even have the ability to moderate my phone's not on so I'm uh
Can't do it. I can't have God he guarded me. Like I said
I don't need a wrench
Both Ziggy and Gotti have
Every single person has a wrench on my chat. Yeah
because they get fucking unruly.
How many times are you going to say it, Doug?
How many times are you going to repeat the same thing over and over again?
We've always been good with you, Doug.
Repeat the same thing over and over again, like a broken record.
On every other channel, too, at the same time.
I didn't have to send you out once.
You're going to have to throw me out again, Doug, believe me.
It's not going to be the last time.
I just like psyche. I thought he was fucking trust me man. That's all
Well, you know, just trust things a little bit of time to build. I'm not I just kind of met you
You know, I have the money. I'm not I'm not sending you know
What do we have to do here?
I'm just saying what I have to do is like, you know, be in the chat be a good person and chat maybe post by a
post by Nightbot links. So that's my links. I've been around for a long time. I've been around for a long time. I like you.
It's okay. I don't think I have enough mods. I have plenty of mods. I'm sorry, I don't know. I have enough mods. I have plenty of mods. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have plenty of mods. I have
I was like why do I have like bent over and like like dick cheese and you know I need a blunt and
so my big crack is like I just didn't know what would happen when I was thinking I go yeah what's
Hey
My mom Samantha my mom Samantha has been with me
She's almost here at the beginning of almost every show and she's a great. She's a great mom
She says she's gonna look out for you and Chad make sure
On you
Okay, yeah
who's who's who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who who
You know, I know, I know, I know, you're on, I forgot, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know,
Are you taking a canoe ride?
Four people were killed in that area.
That was a bigger boat than I was expecting.
Trevor, do you feel yourself pavement?
When you hear the banjo, when you hear the banjo music in the woods, it's time to move camp.
Yeah
You want to meet the guy that
I think it definitely does thought of me in the woods. I get it. Well, you know what around me
God in some kind of
Yeah
It's God you're forgetting the name already it's God
God is God
The chump is your wife
All right
Your wife, yeah two weeks ago
Two weeks ago. It was when you were at Billy's when you were at Billy's we were talking
It was longer ago than that. I'm asking you do you remember of course you spoke to me on the phone too
No, no, no, I just spoke to her
No, no, just your wife
Now I would have remembered
I
This cops everywhere slow down there
I'm in oh, dude. Yeah. Oh, yeah, there's so many cops on this fucking poad on bullshit back-end road. Yeah, I'm real worried
About a make-believe construction company nobody
Tiffany come on
That's where me and Gotti disagree too. It's okay.
Oh, I know that. I know about you and her.
I like her. I like her a lot.
Good luck. Good luck.
I like her a lot.
You'll be the new Gary.
Oh, I don't want to be a new Gary.
I ain't fucking nowhere to go.
I say you have a body in your trunk.
You're going to go bury right now.
No, not
No, no, no, I said I say I say I'm bury a body because someone said I say he's gonna go bury a body and he said in the chat
No, as far as I know God is never shown his face
No
I was responding to a comment in the chat.
Shit, not that I give a thought, but I don't.
Well, I mean, I'll send you if anyone wants to know.
If anyone wants to know if he's off the spot.
He said I'm in the wrong spot.
Andrew, 6739, Tony at Cross Street.
Two big boulders, driveway past it.
OK, all right, I'm just, I don't know, fuck.
Two big boulders.
Parted.
I
Know the ones that were earlier she just left
All right, you feel tap-ons from public toilets, what? Oh, yeah, that's it
I
Listen, let them let them say what they want. They just make themselves. They just make themselves. It's stupid, right?
Sometimes it's like we'll sort of read the comments and then it's the oh
Half of the comments are like well, that's the thing about having assholes in your chat is they discourage actual people from coming
Yeah
Yeah, and I like, I've had a lot of people like, I don't like that shit carry on in my chat because then regular people
Will be like fuck this. I don't want to go there. You know what I mean?
Oh, I know
Head for the hills when they see what's going on my chat
So it's I need to I need to control it better, right? No
No, no, I mean I would like I would like my chat to be
Well, welcoming and like you know because I want everyone to be here and like meet people
And it's like if you like say for a little bit
Yeah, you will meet like some really nice people have like a lot of the mods are like, you know really friendly and
And a lot of people, well, me people they like here, but it's like, if they see, but if people chase them away as soon as they get here, and Alice would do that, you know, it's like, I don't know, it's like, I don't know why I let Alice get away with so much, but, you know, he went too way too far.
He actually went insane with his power because he was like, he was like, oh, I, I mean, I'm gonna hide everybody. I mean, like, he just was like, he's like, it's mine.
People try and take over the chat from you, right like your mom
What okay, there's a couple of reasons I have everybody body model first reason is so they can connect to other people channel
And the second reason is so that I can't get people pulling penny bullshit in my chat, you know walking people and fuck everybody's a mod
I have three managing mods
Three time anybody out
But nobody else can talk to anybody else, because they're all standing by, right?
Yep.
But mainly, they connect to other channels.
I want anybody told to go to Gali's channel and sub to him as possible.
Right.
That's I feel bad for anybody that doesn't I know it's like and I used to want to I
Want everyone to promote especially because I knew a lot of other streamers streamers of different sizes and or people
I wanted to start streaming so I would they say hey like you know everyone
I'm not everyone so we keep busy the channels, but then it turned into like
A big mess once a lot of other people start coming in. Yeah
Well, what I encourage people in my chat to do is to post their own links their mods
They could post your only they please sub to me, but I encourage self-promotion
When other people are live when other people are live, I'll promote them and I'll say go and visit
You know go
Why do you have a modded I didn't even know it was my own your shit, Dougie Dougie
He said he wants everybody
People died before you mod them you shouldn't just mod people you should ask for permission, man. That's rude. Yeah
They don't have to come to my chat
It's not up to them it's up to me. It's my fucking channel
Don't give you the right to mod me as it does. Oh my god
I was completely opposite. Yes
I never go I never go to doggie dogs
You
Because nobody goes there
And exactly because we're here you wouldn't be if we were here half the people in this chat wouldn't be if we weren't here
I'm sorry, I don't want a girl down in your jet psyche protecting me
That's I mean I kind of feel what you're gonna make me go on what and what girls
You said that he's begging, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench again, psyche, he's begging for a wrench
I
Served in the military and I protected people
This is not this is not the battlefields in Afghanistan. This is like, you know
I'm like I'm like I'm like Norway where I have you know, the balconies are like you know
These these are the powerful they carry the dead men off to you know heaven and stuff
Which one is the person to protect you's making the Samantha Samantha go go
Samantha is your count the bill
Samantha Avery nice person though
Yeah, they're very yeah, well, they're tough, but they're tough, but they're they're fair. Okay, so
Okay, you better fucking be damn cool to me. Okay. Yeah, you better you understand that
Remember
You know what's like? I don't want to harp on anything, but you promised me you would play my video remember a couple days ago
Yeah, well that I do like
If you don't have to do it right now, but I was okay
I want to I want to do it right before I'm at the end and I have a stream I
Can't you stream I if you think I know I know but I did um, you know people are that's what I'm saying the problem is
I'm being worried. Okay. I mean, I wrote the song myself. It's an original song. Okay. Okay. What's there?
Hannah Hannah, who do I have to attach to and no no her name is Samantha and you're supposed to send
And please leave him alone. I don't have to look at the chat. Hold on. Hold on. I don't know. I don't know. She I don't want to go here
What do you have to do? What do you have to do Samantha?
He's looking for his assignment protector. Oh, I can't type. Did you see? Oh, okay. Well
Oh, Jesus boy. They're on his ass. Oh, why'd they do that? Oh?
Ziggy, you know what it's going to go one of your many alts and
This is don't give way to this. Why this is my thing. This is me. Is there only I was your only account
Okay, well, you know what? Yeah, I don't think you get it if you're hidden you'll all unhide you
But I don't have time to go to my thing right now. I'll do it
Clarenda was here earlier. Yeah, Tiffany. Stop slandering me. I'm gonna take your ass to court. You're on the you're on the panel
In the house, what's up Tommy James?
Love you, brother. You have a Tommy James fans. I'm piano. Yeah, I do. I love it. He's awesome
Nobody's has to do you okay?
Does I think no, that's not no you're not yeah, but you're not the
Supposed to look out for me Hannah. I'm you're not looking out for me
Also, it's the man that you don't you don't have to if you don't want to see me
She said she was like all she did she just said it in the chat. She would you know, you know fix it
If it was for some you know unknown reason or something, you know
Not an important reason but
the
Okay
Picture right that moment whenever fucking it's the basketball playing thing and
Fucking what's his name goes right smack into the sweaty chest?
See you talking about
Sweaty chest. How about Zaya? Yeah, he makes the stream that oh, no, he's fine. It's my wife
You're fine
What next guy are you going to go see?
Oh, I don't know. We're gonna see some people in August. Go see we
Yeah
Who we don't make it. I don't make it to California. I only go as far as Wyoming
Well, Montana, I'll be in Montana in August. Did you get to see more of Tiffany or Gary?
Is that I'll stop right there. They were together. We went to lunch. We all went to lunch. We were all together the whole time
the
Yeah, so okay, so I do have the link and guys if anyone wants to come up with a nice 45 people on chat
Can you guys how many likes do I have my stream? We see if anyone's yeah, I have
Tommy James knows what he's saying see what he wrote. I saw you wrote
Oh
James
He has really cool songs. I'm not joking
Yeah
The only room in the house where I can smoke cigarettes freely is the attic
Wait, let's have a look see
You see a hole in the ceiling board over there. Oh, no, no, no, that's that all your wife. I'm talking about your wife
Oh, come on, man. It's a joke.
I don't know why you do that.
You know why? Because he's screen shot.
Like, thanks for the reading. I appreciate it.
You're welcome.
Yeah, I'm just reading the chat.
Why don't you laugh a lot, man? Come on.
Yeah, you don't laugh a lot.
I laugh, I mean, I've just been kind of stressed lately and I was like, you know, I want to get back to like
I was having a laugh
I know but I do have to kind of concentrate on the just reading some of the chat a little bit and
Thinking about some other stuff. And so
It's hard to keep up on the chat and stay with the guests. Yeah
I did this twice in the way beginning
2000 I think
1918 later 18 or something and I fucking thought it was terrible. Okay close to the panel
Yeah, two times that's all
You gotta know who you gotta throw out is usually it's your best friends. They're the first people I throw out
That's exactly the way it is I'm not fucking with you
Yeah, and I would say you especially my friends. I think are different than your friends
Right. So who's my friends? Hey gal pal
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't
Now you know who I see you with in chat right okay, but but it's like same man
Like same man was like saying he was trying to say that JT was showing pictures of kids or something
He asked for my other friends, you know, I didn't name anybody right on dog
I'm not gonna call anybody's name and say shit about him. I'm just not gonna do that
Thank you. So when did he ask for did he ask for mod and the first time he was a mod?
He posted like this late that of the link of what we were just we're talking about you see a lecture on
Modded him and then he asked for a back and I I gave it back to him
And then he did it again and then and then by I'm on him and then he kept asking for a third time in a second
So I just got oh, yeah, he's just trying to and I could I
You know, I should just have to ask once, you know, and he's playing dumb kind of like, you know, I know you're you're kind of playing
I don't know. I mean you're not playing dumb, but you're you're you're pretending like, you know, oh what in the world?
I have no idea. I mean, I think you are no more than you're living on to but but it's fine
You play whatever character you want to as the it's fine, but you know, it's like I just like my shows not about
You know, it's just all you guys and that's it. It's my show and it's like your guests on the show at my my pleasure
And it's like and so I'd like you to follow my
Someone says my pleasure I like that very much. Yeah
Yeah, it's like it really is like I people on the show it's like because obviously because I want them to be able to
Laughing because he doesn't know me like that
I'm a civil war reenactor
Seriously, like I love that old-school
Rhetorics, you know, I mean like that talk my pleasure. Yes, man
That's why I don't like I don't doggie dog
That's why I don't like the you know, you'll hear me often. I'll be like man. Don't tell people to shut up
Like I don't like that. Yeah. Yeah
Well, yeah, I just think I was like I was talk to you in such a way last night that that was like really rude by Alice
And then it's like I just thought how I had like, you know Alex and talk to other people on the show
And it's like I just think I really felt like wow. I he really
It really is saying terrible things and I can't you know, it's like it's different
You know, I just I just got empathy for people that were being kind of harassed by him
But it took him bullying me to see it like him. I'm kind of like
Little bit wish I would say that sometimes it's appropriate to tell somebody shut up. Certainly not
But sometimes it is I don't deny that to deny that reality is to be very narrow-minded
If somebody tells you to shut up
Then you tell them don't say that and then if they say shut up again, then now you can say shut up
That's how I feel or I could say I can say or say
Yeah, that's why that's why psyche can mute any of us at any time
Well, I would rather honestly for I would rather any of you to
Punch me in the in the face then to tell me to shut up
That would show
Yeah, and we can't touch you in the face with really everything in that same in that same the same thing
No, I shut up sitting on you
Punching you that's the same thing. You know, it's not it's not it's not it's not a big some people don't like it
I don't like to be told to calm down and I was no joker told me calm down or you to relax or
What I need to do on that. So you don't need to be told what to do basically
But it's like if somebody is like talking over people or there's noise
pollution, some people will do that where they just won't stop and they're trying
to talk over people.
Like Al's kind of would do that.
Dan, you can say, you can eventually say shut up because they're just not
stopping talking and they're just being loud.
And no, no, no, no, but you're the panel and I think you're the one
allowed to be like, Hey, everyone shut up.
Like, yeah, I know, I mean, I have, I have, I have like me and Dougie Doug
are talking right now and I'm like, Hey, Doug.
Hey, why don't you shut up? Like I think that's disrespectful
I have five kids I have five kids that own now the youngest is 17 the oldest is 34
The code word with my kids as I would look at them and I would say enough and
They would know that meant shut shut up. I didn't have to say shut up. I just okay
Perfect. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly.
That way you don't have to be moved.
That way you don't have to tell people to shut up.
That way my kids won't go up thinking it's okay to tell someone to shut up.
Right. Yeah, but you don't. Yeah, exactly
I'm not really that concerned like people saying shut up. I'm worried about people
making threats, doxing, and there's a lot of stuff I have to watch out for, like read your language.
I don't have anything to worry about. People saying shut up is like a very mild, mild thing. They call each other in a lot worse.
So whatever. It's just like, you know,
I mean, of course, it's, dude, that's way my hold, of course.
But I'm just saying that, yeah, but I'm saying if you're trying to maintain a conversation.
Yeah, but I'm saying is like, it's like, it's like, you're acting like, oh, I'm so, I get so,
I'm so offended. That's so mean. It's like, I don't get offended. I'm not offended by any,
people can call me F-A-G-G-O-T and any other word. I don't get offended by it. I
Don't like it because it's like not a lot of my rule that it's not and so it's this is I get I get
Defended like oh my god, I guess I guess I'm trying to show you like my heart and who I am and
No, and what Dougie dog would say if he were up here right now
He would be like you know he's bigger for a wrench. No, I don't beg for wrenches. Actually. I hate wrenches
I just want to be equal down there. That's it. But anyway
My chat is like, you know, the mods from my chat are basically, you know, supporting my show and trying to keep things safe and, you know, I think that I have enough.
Okay. Yeah, well, maybe maybe if I you know, you gave my truck, you know, it's it might take a little while, you know
It's like, you know, right right now right now. I have my side eye on some people
Okay, I have my side because there's some things not a little fishy going on that I don't really
It's okay
Well, that wasn't where I was going where I was going was is that whenever somebody in real life
Says, you know shut up. Hmm. Hmm. Yeah, I mean it's like you work. No, no
No, no in real life
That's what I'm saying
It's like that's like on the panels in real life are very different. So if we're talking to somebody
We're not we're gonna say different things that we would then we were on panel because we're not we're like far away from people
And so we're safe, you know
Right
Like the same person that would say I hate you
What's still in real life? I'm talking about on the internet. What's still open the door?
For you at a grocery store
Right real life. Oh
Well, so yeah
Right, it's like people are different, you know on the internet because they're they can wear a mask on the internet
Oh, hey, hi. Hi. It was good to see you. Sorry. I'm sorry. I said that I don't think it's like an example. Yeah
Your name is not Nicky, your real name is not Ziggy, we don't know what you look like, and so you're probably a very nice, kind person out in the real world.
We're just like, Alex isn't around, you see me?
Oh, okay, but yeah.
Oh, you're giving the example.
Okay, I gotcha.
I mean it's like people are people act different with other people you know in real life and they do it on the internet they
full mask and
Same thing with politics like in in real life. They're like, oh no meep and fucking on
Look in the internet. Oh my god, you're backing down like that back in person. You know, it's yeah
Yeah, well, that's why I like it. You know
Tiffany were you really like are you being are you being a smart? Oh, no, I actually yeah, we're very cool. She's really okay
Tiffany let me know if he's
Oh, she knows no, we've told Tiffany tell him we've swallowed a worm
I
Talked to I talked to me like oh, she came on the show last night and had a good we had a good chat and stuff and you know
I just
You know
Like I like positive you guys even if like you're not positive, you know, it's like if you just like
You know, just like if you go to a restaurant if you're like, you know bad table manners at home
So, you know, if you don't have the best table manners at home and whatever, it's like if you go to a fancy restaurant, you're going to be on your best, you're going to be on your, like, best behavior because it's like, or else he'll just be asked to leave the restaurant and, you know, then it'll, it'll be a, you know, so, oh, he's lucky.
Well, that wouldn't be me and Tiffany. We wouldn't eat worms.
Hi.
You hear me?
You're not Tiffany.
Yeah. Oh, okay. Oh, I'm the
Hi. Hi. Well, hey, man, I'm
Hey, man, I'm going to jump
You
Microphone do you hear me?
Flowing internet worm. Oh, yeah, I don't know. It's all the worms. Wow
Live worms
Your sounds now, oh, I heard a sound
Hi guys, so
Mike down we're always in my
So it's the right person. Hey Nancy
Yeah, and I just see your message is Nancy and I don't know what's going on. I don't know what's going on like, you know, it's
I think that's I think it's I think it's sad I think it's that okay
Hi
Sorry, I was connecting weird the beach the beach internet is not the greatest
How are you doing?
I'm pretty good. I'm feeling better today. It was a better day than yesterday. It's like yeah, I feel like I'm like more
more like
Have a better vision of what I want and now I know what I don't want and so I'm able to
Yeah
So yeah, but thank you
People like you really help because, you know, sometimes it's just hard to control the panel that has people just going off on the panels last night, you know
Like a lot of people I've known for a long time. They know better than to say certain things
It's a fact that they keep doing it. I'm sure I asked it's like
It's like malicious
Like you let them off and they say like stupid words and stupid things and
Yeah
Or you know, we're true even like Joker. I don't know if you know Joker, but you know, I like him a lot
I don't know anyone. I know Sebastian. I
know Gotti. I know
CB who is a wonderful woman and
That's about it
Well, I know some assholes, but I want to bring my name. So, you know, I don't like
Well, you know, it's like, you know, there's a lot and there's a lot of people here and I'm glad
You know, I'm grateful to them for you know, bringing good people about good people, but it's like also
Like you but there's let me see who's this right here
Look at everyone. She's having a good time. He's a little kids plan. Oh
It's not amazing
I'm right on the beach. You know, I'm on the beach. I go to the pier sometimes. Um, yeah, I see you
You live in can you tell me? I mean, I mean, it's Tommy. It's Tommy. It's Tommy. Okay, sorry
Hi Tommy. Yeah, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in South Bay, California. So I'm in the South Bay,
like, uh, you know, Beach City area. I don't know, the Beach City is in California.
They're Cali. Who are you? Yeah. Who are you in chat? Who are you in chat, Spunky?
I'm Heather Spunky.
Hey, there's funky. It's like
Can you show us your can you show us your tattoos? There's so many of them. That's kind of an evasive question
I'm a capricorn, so I love ghosts, you know, I'm a capricorn, so I love ghosts
Yeah, well, I'm actually a Pisces, but I love ghosts in real life like
They're my jam. Once upon a time I had a rescue farm where I used to take like
special ed animals and that didn't fit in in other places and
That was sweet
That's like even in my family a little bit because my mom has a dog with one leg and I said my sister adopted a dog with
One front leg, you know they they because you know my sister adopted the dog because you know had three legs and
She's had the heart for special needs dog, right?
I have five dogs, every single one of them has some sort of like special ed need and it's okay.
Like, they can't be placed other way, but it's okay.
Oh, that's what it, that's your sweetheart. You know, I have several cats, like I adopted a
one of my family friends cat this year he's like 16 or 17 years old and you know she's movey and she
couldn't really take him with her I'll show he's right here this is Rudy
he's an old man Rudy I call him oh my god he's cute
Okay, so no hate on your other cat, but this cat has a much nicer like resting bitch face
Yeah, he saw a little bitch face. Yeah, your other cat looks angry
Yeah, I guess you look me and then this is Trix. I don't know if you see Trix. Hey Trix gonna wake up here. You sleep it right here. Oh
My gosh, you don't want to wake up, but she's cute
Yeah, those tricks. You know we sleep big these are like these cats are like always on the couch
They're hardly ever they're always big with me. I have two cats, too. What what I'm at home sometime. I'll show them to you
Cool. Yeah
One is a Siamese and one is a tuxedo and
I was at the shelter one time just visiting and the tuxedo kept
reaching his hands is the little paw out of the cage and grabbing me and grabbing me and and
He had all kinds of like infections and stuff and I was like, I'll take him
I'll just notice about
And I did and the whole household got
Some fungal infection from him and I had to prescribe medicines for everyone. It was terrible, but yeah
Well, I mean that is very very I know we have like so many cat lovers dog lovers and also in
You have a huge heart. We also have a lot of nurses and medic people the medical field in my chat
I don't know. There's I mean, there's just a lot of nurses here. So I know we tried
I realized that I couldn't communicate and that bothered me, so when I heard that I could help them, so I was like, oh, I'm doing medicine, so what I'm doing, let's do it.
Awesome. We have a great heart and I love that and I there's so many people in the chat with good hearts, too
Like in the so it really really makes it worth all the all the all the trolling all the all the hate
It's like there's so many good people
Like there are some nice people
And even people that we might not like or not get along with it doesn't mean that they're they're bad people
It's like we might just have that's a better just be our relationship with them
They're good, you know, there's people that you know in real life. They're really nice or maybe there's just a personality conflict sometimes with
Maybe the personality conflict we don't not everyone's gonna get along we're very different people right but
We can all
Yeah, I feel like there's nobody once you get to know somebody like you know like on a personal level rather than you know either just
Talking to chat or you know, they're seeing their masks that if you get to know somebody on a personal
It's really hard to like really hate hate people like you're a hate if you if you really get to know them because you'll find things
About somebody else even if they're very different that you are the same. You'll find it. We're all connected
I want to say like I didn't I didn't realize you were gay at first and like that's cool
Like my four best friends are all gay guys like that's that's my thing
Yeah
Yeah, and it's like and I've been I'm kind of used to being like the old pretty much the only gay guy in most social groups
I'll be off and I don't really not really in the gay scene or you know
But it's like and then I but I end up around some homophobic people
I do like you know change some people's minds about about gay people
But and even even to be in my chat for like a lot of guys is brave because people
as gay like initially and that's okay like it's fine and most of my gay friends are like that too
uh the the best friend the absolute love of my life we met at 12 years old in middle school
and that we were best friends until 38 when he passed was a guy that presented like that too you
Well, yeah
And a lot of gay people do have shorter lifespans like that. You know, it is like people don't really think about it
But they did there's like a lot of things they not as easy I mean
Gay people kind of like support the straight world. Yeah, okay
He took a lot of risks and he fucked around and it stops it does it like really does
Yeah, well, there can be like a higher, you know, there's a higher unaliving rate of themselves a higher violence rate towards them
I thought a larger incarceration rate a larger drug
But you know, he was a recovering addict and one one night he went out and
Took a bag of the end of someone's bag of coke and was like, oh, I'm gonna try this
This will make me feel good and it was actually straight fentanyl
And he went home and went to sleep and passed away. Yeah, it was terrible 38 years old sucked
but
Yes, mom called me the next morning and I just lost my mind it sucks
Yeah, as you know losing people we imagine the in the 80s like when there is like the AIDS epidemic
Like there's just gay men at a certain age that that's 75% of the gay community. They knew they died
You know, it was like there was the whole thing, right?
Yeah, and
So he had actually contracted HIV from needles from doing heroin. He wasn't even like a big slut
But um, so he had that and like had never told me and I never found out until his mom
Like called me and told me he died and she was like, I'm so glad you say this friend when he had HIV
And I was like, oh well shit. Well, I never knew but I would have stayed his friend anyway
He was just so proud about it that he would never tell me and
It's just crazy what people live with and you you have no idea and they're like close friends to you and
Right, and that's why also why I like I tell people to be kind to other people because you don't know what people are going through and what kind of
struggle they have or
Like you know, even if they're like not a likable person
Maybe there's a reason for that why they are the way they are maybe a bit like a lot of people have been through trauma
And then they continue to fight with trauma. It's like yeah, like I am
I have lived on my own since I was 16 years old, like my parents were like career criminals
and I was, I escaped that and left and like with my boyfriend who was 21 at the time and
I made a pretty decent life for myself with that and I feel like a lot of people don't
choose that they like have shitties that shit happen to them and then they like don't do
Like I'm gonna I'm gonna help people like that's what I want to do like that's my thing
You know like I just want to just want to be nice
I feel like karma is really like the true religion just be nice to others and it will come back to you
It does tenfold
Yep, and I really feel it also just putting out good energy and like you know good intentions or people of it
It's like you know and because if we have hate towards people
It's like the only person that really feels the hate is like it's like us
Oh, we can do it like reflect our own self-hatred toward other people and then and it's like oh, we feel it
That's probably why I have all these gay friends and I'm like, oh you like I they're so successful. They're so lovely. They're wonderful people
And people discount them because of that like is they're gay and I feel like that's just such a waste of a person like get to know them
Muscular oh my god. They're so muskier
Beautiful man beautiful
Yep, there are a lot of very attractive gay men, but yeah, I'm not I'm not really into the hook-up culture
And so I don't really know and there's no gay bars one gay bar in my city
It's two couples
There's two married couples and they're not into that either but they just want friends and it's like hard for them to find it
You know
Yeah, I should move to like a city like there's like a few gay districts in some cities, which are like, you know
Comfortable for some people, but otherwise, you know gays aren't a straight world and it's like we also a lot of gays are like the fast
designers or
makeup hair
Um, wedding planners. Yeah. Well, these boys are not, they're not pretty in that sense.
Like they're just very masculine. They're like, they seem like straight dudes. It just happened to be gay.
So I, I try to dress them and love them and like make them cute.
That's my favorite fast food.
All right, Justin wants to know what your favorite fast food is, sake.
Um, I would say, um,
Like my favorite fresh food restaurant. Um, I think I like Wendy's I like Wendy's occasionally like when he's
When he's good
Look, we would have been soulmates if it was McDonald's because I
But I love trashy
I'm a good fix. No, I mean, I like McDonald's too, but it's like if I eat it too often
I get kind of sick of it
Yeah, we need a pretty good quality. Um, I find you regret it
Yeah, oh, yeah, it always makes you kind of sick, but uh, yeah, yeah
Oh, this is KZ. Yeah, my KZ. This is uh, this is spunky KZ
Oh hi, hi, nice to meet you. Nice to meet you too. Have life
Good
Can't complain, you know, yeah, can't complain
There we go
Beautiful blue sky too. Yeah, it's a little bit overcast here today, but it's super hot up here
It's supposed to be like serious heatwave coming tomorrow up here in the northeast
Where I live, it's always hot. It doesn't matter
Well, it's never nice to have a beach. I didn't even see the beach walk.
It's such a nice day. I was like, I had such a bad week at work. Like work has been a lot.
And I was really like getting a bad place mentally and I was like, I'm going to beach this weekend.
Sit. I just need a little rejuvenation, you know, I'm going to spend the whole day at the beach.
It's great there, you know, beaches are like a beautiful natural setting and it's like, you know,
It's very, very cleansing for the soul, I think.
It's content in nature.
And I'm a Pisces, so you know, we're water science,
we're rejuvenated by the water.
Yeah, Neptune, rubite Neptune.
So it has to do with the, and dreams, dreams.
And I know a lot of Pisces are very,
like I have a couple of my brothers are Pisces.
My grandfather was too.
There's a lot of Pisces with blue eyes, I know.
They have these beautiful blue eyes.
Yeah, so all right, I'll show you my gross eyes.
You ready?
Oh, wow. They're like, no.
They're blue.
They're blue-green.
Yeah, that's very Piscian.
Like the ocean.
Absolutely.
They're blue-green, and then they have a little amber and brown in them.
It's weird.
It's not hazel.
I don't know what you would call it, but...
Mine are hazel.
I don't know if you can see my eye color, but I have hazel eyes.
They're a little bit greenish.
You see it kind of greenish brown. You're like that greenish brown. Yeah hazel
so
Yeah, and I have a you know my sisters both have blue eyes or brother with blue eyes and
All my niece a lot of my one of my sister
We both your blue eyes very bad blue eyes a hundred percent chance blue eyes kids
So, you know, yeah
That's awesome. Yeah
So it's just weird that I like create this and then it continued
So are you
What's up
Do I know who just some boy. Yeah, yeah, I recognize the name
All right, so I have a friend who's sitting next to me,
and he wants to know if you believe in the afterlife.
In the afterlife?
I'm sorry, you're coming up.
Okay, Dan's in the afterlife.
Do I believe in the afterlife?
Yes, because I think that, like, no problem.
I feel like that we were, I feel like there was some where we were here before here too.
I believe in like life as a continuous process of like of like you know birth, death, regeneration,
you know birth, death.
It's just kind of like Jesus resurrected.
I think that was kind of a metaphor for like we can resurrect too in either in spirit or
into like the physical form again, but I think the goal is to eventually
get out of the physical form and like, you know, learn the lessons we can in the physical
and to, um, to, uh, further our soul, but then eventually to get out of this earth because it
is kind of like a prison for our soul. It's like our spirit is like confined. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe the earth might be kind of like a trap too, like where it's like, it's kind of hard to get
out of here unless you're like, yeah, if you have any physical matter, you can't leave. You know,
can go but I think we keep trying to trap crap out here but also we need to learn the lessons
like I think that we can learn the most lessons reincarnating on earth I think we could have had
countless lives playing every character and experience you know all these people we know
we and so I feel that uh yeah I feel that the soul is eternal the body is very temporary and
Like actually death is a blessing here because then our spirit gets to go on and do it do it
Further itself do it and it takes on the lessons. So yeah, I studied a lot of Buddhism and they're really big into the reincarnation and
the gaining merit to be even born as human being like because there's so many billions of insects and animals and we're like the
the you know the top of the food chain pretty much on the planet, so
So it's I think it's best to be born a human being just you can do accomplish the most have the best minds and
So animals eventually will want to incarnate into human bodies. I think so if you've probably been animals to we could have been
So thank you for but thank you. I think your phone could up and thank you so much
Oh, yeah, you just had tatted eyebrows you've been in jail for a long time or yeah, or you just you know
My mom I think my mom had these cats you cats who's done permanent makeup, you know
Here we go, spunky
Yeah, it's kind of it's I think you're there you go, it's better I think
Black Apple says he doesn't see animals have sold well
The animals can't constantly, uh, okay.
Okay.
I think it's like the otolum.
Here.
I hear you now.
Alright.
I think animals have souls too.
Justin thinks it's like the otolum.
That's why I'm so kind to animals.
But Justin thinks it's just like that when you die.
And I don't believe that.
Well, you know when you fall asleep, it's kind of like lights out and it's kind of like equivalent to death a little bit
Because we go into an unconscious state, but then we go on to the other realm
Yeah, we dream and we're like alive in our dreams and so life could be a big dream
Do you actual projects?
Yes, I asked a project and you know, I do
Visualization
Yeah, because there's an astral realm that the world, so astral realm is non-physical. It's a world of ideas
and you we can bring things from that world because everything exists there and we can bring them into this world like all these good things, you know
But that's why everything originates in the mind first and the mind is that connected to this to this realm
And so we're not just confined to our body that we with our minds we can have wings and we can like
Astral projecting go anywhere and
Anywhere anytime. What's up Joker? What's up easy? So are you mad at me Joker? I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I got salty a Joker lesson jokers in the chat
Hi Joker, he's a good friend. Okay, so
Yeah, well, there's there's actually stories about like a
In Buddhism, they would say the animals used to like just like voluntarily come in like put their necks down in front of the axe because they would they would want to like that so they would want to go through the cycle.
And it would take a long time it takes a long time to get enough merit to be borderless human beings.
So they always have like think about how amazing how much work we did in past lives to try to get this body this body that a gift we have.
We have all these opportunities.
Good way to think about you in this life.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, oh my gosh. Yeah, I like when I walk down the street
I walk to the store sometimes I have squirrels running up to me
Butterflies flying from my face birds fly around me cat cats coming out of the houses and stuff like that and so
I was no way. Oh
Yeah, that's the thing snow white. It's like the I feel the same way
So I had at one point I possums and squirrels like coming into my house and I was like, what's going on?
It was you know coming out of the couch. So I just I and I love I love animals and
Like dogs never I've never been bitten by a dog or anything. I've always had you know always been able to like to like just
all dogs kind of like me and
You know that's like that really does the animals like you know
It's like because they can they can see your soul that they sense, you know dangerous or not absolutely. It's amazing
I've been black cat named Lenore. I don't know if you ever see Lenore, but I have a black cat named Lenore
So she's like my little black panther. She's like, oh my god
She's a black cat, but she's like this. She's a very very
Boy my most recent one that I rescued from the shelter
Like I had no intention of bringing home a cat and I pissed off everyone like even my son was mad
And then I brought him home and everyone was like, oh my god
This is the greatest cat in the world. I was like, I know you just had to meet him
You just had to meet him like
Bis bald.
That's what I got one point
I mean I one point I had a lot of cats that a couple I got one letter last year a couple letters a year before and that
But then after I had a couple letters someone brought me a cat
I was like us in a little case and it was Lola the one with the RBF and
I was like I can't look I can't even look at her because then I'll fall in love and I'll have to take her
And so he's like, oh just kind of leave her here for a little bit. I'll be back later
And I was like, okay, does she like me out?
I opened the little case and she comes out and her eyes were just like closed with eye boogers
And uh, and I was like, oh
She's the most beautiful eyes in the world and I was oh my so so and she's a very sweet cat
Um all my cats especially these end up the ones that say indoors these guys
They're they're just so loving if I'm get under the blanket. They just want to go right under
beef, right
Yep
Go see four. I I don't know about her. I eat me. I eat me. But well, I don't even dog me
The reason I ask is what about those animals?
Right. It's like, I think that there is a, you know, I think we are a carnivore. We have a carnivore and it's like, you know,
it's part of our nutrition and, you know, I
Because we're so removed from the killing process. We don't have to see it and everything we can kind of like not think about that
Yeah, I mean, it's terrible. I mean, it's it's a brutal thing, but it also is like, you know, we are top of the food chain and
If you believe in like the afterlife and things and maybe hey you said ammo
We're so removed from the killing process. It's just yeah
If we had to kill our own food fall like you know
If you're born that way. Yeah, we like that before World War two you've got a house and you got you know
They would give you a plan. It would be like a 25 foot by 15 foot
You know piece of garden in your backyard, you know, you give you enough food to grow yourself for the year
Yeah
Okay, and if you have a cow, then you can milk the cow you can have enough milk for the other way, you know, there's you know
there's animals can
Or a big resource that you know, I do believe in compassion with any animal I meet
But yeah, you just have to you know, there's gonna be slaughterhouses and that's where we get our meat from them
And we just come from somewhere, you know, if you can try it
Beyond meat or alternatives, but is that the Atlantic?
I don't think she wants she won't tell. I don't know how to tell you.
It's okay. I think I know.
It's called the Indian Ocean or something.
Yeah, it's not Hawaii.
It's definitely not Hawaii. Oh, that's the North Sea.
Yeah, so let's see.
You're really in England. You're in England? Nice.
So black apple says they're conspiracy that we're eating dead people and don't even know it. Yes, because they've done DNA testing
I don't know if you how accurate these scientific studies. I've seen are but it's like in in uh
In mcdonald's they found like two percent human dna and in um
In hot dogs and stuff they have like
Like a lot of they've been maybe human dna too, but I don't know if that's those are true
I don't know if those are scyops
With the additives they put in
I heard that if you tune out that there's like a certain amount of the FDA allows of rat parts in tuna
And I'm ruling oh my god
Yeah, I mean, it's like they do probably have these
It's kind of like that with any big food processor like there's a certain amount of bugs that can pass through the system
And get corrupt in the
Yeah
You're gonna eat a butt burger they've like wiped that in their asshole and given it to you and I'm like no, but it tastes so good
Yeah, yeah, some people like I've been a version of fast food, but yeah, even like but there's even like you know
So I think Donald Trump like for breakfast has McDonald's every day. I don't know. I don't think it's not
No, he doesn't I look at the menu and he doesn't get burgers he was getting it looks like he gets a bunch of like the breakfast
So like I think for breakfast like every day. He just thought like I saw the menu was but he loves it
My dad loved it. You know, it's like, you know, so
People with a good palates, you know, they're like a fifty dollar burger
And then it's like and then the McDonald's burger will kind of taste better because you know
Has familiar chemicals in it and it's all made in a lab
Taste of the fries is the special taste. It's so funny
I have such a like boushey taste on some things, but then I'm like, oh, I love McDonald's, you know, like
Well and surprisingly you don't it's kind of expensive. I mean, you know, it's like fast food people take
Oh, it's just so cheap and stuff. What happens to the dollar menu like
Dollar menu
You can get some good shit
Like you've seen the five dollar meal in the app you guys. Yeah, there's a five dollar meal
I end up getting a double cheeseburger for chicken nuggets a small fry and a small drink for five bucks
Wow, I have to look that one up because I just get like I've seen they have to make value menu
It's not on the app. It's just you can order
$5 value mail. It's like great on the app
Okay, I'll look at the app and you can do it. If you don't want the burger you can get a McChicken
Like the spicy make chicken like the one they have now you can get a you need a double cheeseburger
And then for a dollar you can either add like a small fries or a McChicken or
Something else you like a few other items. You're gonna add
Yes
Enjoy have fun. All right. Are you at the campground? No, I'm streaming
Did you bury the body?
Hello, everybody buried. Hi. Hi. Where are you at the camp? Yeah, you want to see it? No, it's my cousin's property
We're okay. Hold on. Hold on. Are you going to flip the damn camera? So
It's this is
of the tractor.
That's beautiful.
Where are you at?
Up in Ohio by
PA border.
I grew up in Indiana.
Beautiful area.
Next door neighbor. Fair enough.
We're just not as flat over here on this side.
Yep.
Do you want to see my view?
Fuck yeah.
Ready
Well, you know, it's a beautiful view where you at I
Can't tell you
But is it is it's order the Caribbean I'm just closed location
She won't give the cash one
I'm in the Bahamas and I thought so. I thought so there is nothing around. Yep. I
Yeah, there's nothing. Oh my god, they're amazing
We went to uh, we didn't go to the big one. What's uh, Nassau? Fuck Nassau. Nassau? No. Uh, it's uh, uh,
Exuma. I went to Exuma twice.
Oh
Beautiful island, but uh, no, hey, here's my psyche. You got a new bike and I got a new bike
Oh, nice. You got a, you got a real bike. Get a motorcycle.
It fits perfectly in the back of my truck even though I'm leaving it out here at this property because I'm like
I live pretty much in a city so I can't ride it at my house
I didn't hear what you said.
And if she types too, I can, I can, uh, I can mod her. Okay. So how's everyone doing?
Three goes seven. I still, I hardly finished my beer list. I still, I still have my, uh,
Arizona, peach tea, I think. Oh, it's right here. Hard, oh, it's hard mango, actually.
Okay. I'll drink some of this. See him get some subway maybe.
He built some truck trail or Jeep trails, but I think my truck and there's an entire reason that this thing that that's cool
And if this is a cool, I think I think I think I really want terror to be like people say oh, yeah
You think I'm like I want to be the only terror readers. No, there's there's the guys
there's like thousands of
Super talented readers like just by a person and style by as many thousands of those that suck
Well, yeah, there's I mean there's there's both but you know, I have no
complaints about your tarot. I like Emma. I like this couple other dudes and then I
Haven't had good experiences with a few others
Yeah, well, yeah, especially I mean
But you might want to check out like the general readings just for your sign if you just Google after out your sign
But if you Google yours or search YouTube for your sign and tarot and then we'll have specific
General readings like and you can have you know, they do them every day and there's you'll find
Just people you might relate to and stuff and then you know, that's how I found a lot of readers
I've been through a lot. I've found a lot of readers. There's a lot of very talented ones
Even if they're not a talented reader, they're like themselves
I mean I can always someone gives you a reading and they're not a talented reader
But I can still look at the cards I can do my own interpretation and so and I'll find that the
Readings can still be accurate. Sometimes the people don't. I
I'm not saying accuracy because you know, it's all chance, you know, I don't interpret a
When I think of a good reader, it's not about accuracy of the actual outcome of their reading, it's just, you know, the reading in general, like, you know, how did they understand what they were reading?
Did they just buy a pack of cards online, decide they wanted to read tarot, try and make some money, and boom, like...
Well, yeah, but, you know, there's a movie called Ghost, I've never seen the movie Ghost.
Have you ever seen that?
And there's a, there's a movie called Ghost, it's like Patrick Swayze and Demi Moore.
Yeah.
It's a movie called Ghost.
You see that good?
So you know that movie?
So what we Goldberg play is like the psychic, that's actually like a, she's a fake psychic.
But, uh, and she, you know, she's like one of the scammers that they have all the table moving on its own props and stuff. And then, um,
but then she actually is psychic and, you know, and I think we all do have psychic ability. We all have like, especially women, they have the natural, like, natural receptivity to, to these ideas from the astral realm and thinking of messages and how they have an empathy where they can talk.
And then men are very, can be very logical, like straight men, especially when they retire. They can be very like, this is what it means.
This is very technical. It takes both, I think, to be a really good reader.
What are you looking at? Is this your windshield?
All the little tadpoles in this fucking, my cousin's growing frogs.
All these little tadpoles swimming around.
Okay. I was just curious if that camera picked it up.
Cool. I saw some of the tadpoles.
Little fishies. Okay, how's the chat doing?
Yeah, so I'm going to be trying to make...
I'll be trying to like, I think, you know, I'm just looking at like ways to approve the show because I was like, I did a lot of the last six months, I've just been throwing everything.
I've been trying every time and trying different combinations, like letting people kind of run wild.
So now I have an idea of what I want and what I don't want for the show.
I think that
I can probably I love you. I'll be back on later. Okay. Bye. Yeah, thank you. Bye. Have a good night. I can probably
Yeah, I can probably
You know
Probably be more
You know, sometimes less is more.
I know I've been streaming a lot, a lot, a lot.
I kind of wanted to see when people come in,
how many people come in, and what happens.
I mean, so I think I can probably shorten my hours on
and then maybe structure the show the better,
maybe like, than the first hour doing a general tarot read
plus readings for the chat.
And then we could open the panel
and then do a few hours on the panel.
Yeah, maybe Friday Saturday night have a little bit longer or later nights or
Depends on how I feel sometimes I just feel like streaming. It's not like I'm like I have to stream
I say I really want to stream. I just want to do it. I want to make it the best show I can so
Thank you guys whoever should do whoever does
Does support the show and you know is kind of the chat and once the best for for me and then my show
I really do appreciate you, you know
Whether you donated or a mod or a member or just in the chat, you know curing me on
and
Being a being a good citizen a good citizen of the chat. The panel needs a theme. How about BDSM charity?
I don't know. Maybe I'll look if there's any DDSM cards. I don't I don't think that'd be the best
Theme for the channel. I don't it's a very that's very niche. That's very niche. I don't know how many people are looking for that kind of reading
but
I'm sure there's a carrier for everybody. I'm I want I want to appeal to like, you know a lot
I want to help as many people as I can so I don't want to be so niche. I
Think I have a good good mix of cards for different
temperaments
Don't have you kick psyches and leave me down here without no protect. Oh, Ziggy come on
You basically you basically don't have a condom. Well, you know, then then don't uh, then don't have unsafe sex. Okay
So, you know poor Ziggy guys when I everyone for everyone shed a tear for Ziggy, you know
You didn't have a wrench
Well, maybe if you're nice that you're you behave yourself in that chat you want to worry I don't think anything will ever happen
Well, there's two with the get math terrarium. I don't know. Maybe on chatter bait. I can try that chatter bait
I can do some naked tarot. I can do
You know I
You're sharing me on thank you, sweetie. Yeah, I love you. Okay. Yeah
I think I would you know, I'll do I'll do the American speedo tarot readings that you know
If you want to donate extra ten bucks in the for the for the reading, you know, it's like I'll throw in a speedo
I don't I don't care
Yeah, I know I see you. I mean you're nice, but you know I have my eye on you for watching. Okay
Make it tarot. Yeah, but someone gave me idea this first
They're done with their name in the chat was giant labia and I don't I haven't seen them in a long time
But they were talking about chatter bait
They're like well, I have a friend that was making like a thousand dollars a night on chat. I was like wow
You know looking into it. Maybe if you're like
You're like some gorgeous. I don't know how people can make that much money on I think I've made like 10 cents on or something
But Casey's pretending that he caught fish
And we hit left yeah
Then he left yeah, maybe that's oh, yeah, yeah, well, I always had some tadpoles in there
Okay, so it's a hit so guys get it on a bodyguard so let's do defend for himself be a man's do yeah
I think you'll be okay in my chat. It's not it's not we're gonna be at normal. Okay, just it's a little YouTube chat
But the whole spills, you know, let's let Goddy know and I'll I'll look into the
If I'm a block list, but I think you're fine. It has to be pretty good today, huh? It's a nice day
Things are looking up right because people come in sometimes like oh my god
They're like oh yours think you're so big and you have five people in the chat or if I can't people
I'm like well, I just started three minutes ago, you know after
Restarting about ten times though. It's pretty pretty good to have ten people in the chat
But I get more at 36 people now. How's big Misha? Well, we found out big Misha's true identity
Big Nisha is actually a man that we all know.
I love him, but some people, we know and love.
Well, I'll speak for myself.
I know and love him, but it's Arthur, I think it's Arthur.
No, no, no, it's Rogue Nomad, Rogue Nomad was playing
Big Nisha, and he amassed himself.
Doug, it's a man.
You fell in love with a man, Doug.
You've been catfished.
Big Nisha's a dick.
You're actually a man, Ziggy, okay?
I know Big Misha is awesome, but Big Misha is not real.
That's a thing.
I say, sometimes we fall in love with these people in the chat.
They're not, they're not, they're like, they're characters.
And Donnell, yeah, the whole storyline, that was, it was great.
It's like, find out there's not a Santa Claus,
finding out Big Misha is actually like a, you know,
a Hispanic man in Southern California, but it was fun.
You can you can't tell me what I want to hear then you're a bad reader. Well yeez skirt
People will tell you what you want to hear that's called the yes, man, or there's kind of pandering I'd rather someone be honest and
Who is it? It's someone named rogue nomads. There's a guy. He has a big muscles in his picture. He's a hell of a no man
Hey, what's up, man? He is like he kind of has like a little
Hispanic voice
Don't let let let old people fill your chat without donating like you feel a bunch. Yeah
Yeah, well, I'm saying yeah, I'm saying, you know if you if you
But even donators like, you know, I was one of my biggest donators and you know
Then he just completely turned on me and disrespected me and disrespected my show and and disrespected the chat
And it's like and I love and I love him and he was extremely generous, but
Just because you know donators it's like, you know, you supposed to give a donation for me
They're like a provide a service or from love not and so people will sometimes say oh, I donated I deserve this
I just like I appreciate the donation
I
Just have to go
Oh my gosh, what are you wearing you're the sea monster is the monster are you alien long tongue?
I think you give a great French kiss. Yep. Did you get you guys want to give a French kiss?
Yeah, that's what happens when spawn has too much to drink it hurts looking like that
You're echoing my
Hold on. I'm a I'm a
This is why you're not the Z this is why you're not a mod and it's because you're type shit like that in the chat and are picking on people
Okay, I'm not gonna hide. I'm just gonna delete your
Your comment hold on
It's because because when you say shit, I just don't want people fighting in chat like that
It's it's bad for it. It's not like it doesn't hurt you it hurts me. Okay, let's see where
I don't see the comment. I don't know. Oh, I guess it's old chat. Okay there. Yeah
Please
Okay, I deleted the comment
Yeah, we got a nice bomb
Yeah, please yeah guys just uh, oh
Your friend, okay. I don't know because she was like oh she said she said reported and so it seems like I don't know if she's just
I'm saying and I just want to see I don't know the dynamics of relationships. That's why I need I really need you to people
just to behave and
Try to say this is my way
To the old people fill the chat with nonsense or free psyche's rain. Yeah, I'm right. It is. I mean guys
I you know, I I'm doing a readings, you know, like a more detailed reading
I know it gets distracting here and there's sometimes too much going on and it's like oh my god
It didn't seem like a tear but it is a terror channel and you know
Basically, I this is my full time what I'm doing full time. I'm spending it's been a lot of time here
And so every everything is appreciated, you know
But yeah, I mean I do it seems like you know
Nobody
Or at least, you know, love love people
That um become members that really supports the channel you get
Longer readings black at any show to pick of a bear catching a fish and we started this story
I know Armin, but it's like that you know Armin. I was I told him not to switch around as photos and he kept switching him around and I'm just
And I also, I also have a previous incident where he has,
he has, and were bombed me or something,
or he has something inappropriate in the panel.
So there's a history though.
So let me just, let me just use my judgment
on when I restart my streams and start some.
It's kind of like my business.
I'll give you a reading prediction.
It's only gonna get worse before it gets better.
Well, Sebastian, you know, I'll give you a prediction.
I'm not gonna see your comments anymore.
We'll see who's right, okay?
like that. It's like, I just like, you know, some of these smart mouth people, I don't need
the negativity, you know? I would like, you know, who are these people just bringing on the chat?
Yeah, it just brings on the whole vibe. So, bye-bye.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to I'm gonna be like I'm gonna be I'm gonna be more like Emma
You know she's pretty cold-hearted when it comes to this like you're blocking people, you know
They can say a lot less than people here have said
You get that so I'll have to be
Yeah, I don't like that. Yeah, no smart mouse, right? I have a prediction psyche will be rich and famous
But oh my gosh. Well, see that and see that was kind of like that's not it's terrible
But you know, that's that's at least like a troll not like just some like negative
Doom
They stuff, okay
Why are you here? All right, why are you still here? Didn't say hide you? What the hell?
Go away, or hi. I'll hide you on every channel. I'm done with you
Back under the sea with Ariel Sebastian
Everybody cares about you to attack your platform hold on
You've yeah, you'll get again can control yourself ten people if you go see my puppet on my channel on your channel
What are you talking about him? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Okay. I guess you're talking to you
Okay, doing
Yeah, it's okay, you know, I'm I
Like to provide a service. I know I like to do my kick off the panel thing
I like to do readings and if anyone has ideas of things they'd like me to do, you know
I'm happy to do stuff on camera and IRL and stuff
Um, you know, you can propose things to me, you know, I'm here to I'm here to play along, right?
Platform boots, you're obviously still in the chat. You're laughing about it. You're fine. Hey mojo joe
It is a good chat and guys you will uh, you'll meet a lot of good people in this chat, but you know
If you're new here, welcome subscribe, you know, and I would just say if it's a little bit weird just hang out
You know things usually are you're really positive, but we have some drama here, right?
Yeah, let's yeah, that's all chill. Yeah
Yeah, no, that's the thing I do have to talk those and I do I do you know
There's something called dead air. It's like not the most attractive thing on a stream. So
Forgive me if I was a little bit for ghosts
Okay, okay
Why why did you get it? Yeah. Hi, I thought you diamond. Hi, Jamie ice we pee hi
Spectre, why do you get offended beta? I don't mean to offend. Yeah, but the thing is that I don't and people getting offended
Like a lot of people are so offended. It's like I
Is the Liberty area one of the first tens of it is you do not think it's not it's not a right
I could a American right not to be offended like people can get offended over every like little even
Even things that weren't meant as offense people can get offended at
So it's more like I'm just trying to
Have rules and have people follow the rules so my my platform just stays place for everybody and you know
It's around for a long time
Hi Nancy says so it's gonna tiger butterfly with the right. Yeah, she refuses to come back
She feels like she was kind of blue and you know, I emphasize emphasizes that with her
But I do hope she comes back someday. She feels like I wasn't protecting her
I wanted to be better protector of people
But I really can't control it comes out of other people's mouths. Sometimes we have some some some some drunk fools on the panel
They can be entertaining, but at the end of the day
We want it to be respectful and
Everyone to everyone have fun. It's supposed to be about fun. Not about oh my god
This channel is attacking me blah blah. I want everyone to be fun. I should get open his mouth wide. Yeah
That he gives a great blow job, but you know, I would really be careful this teeth though. Oh
No, no teeth. No teeth really
Because Vicky's saying there's something wrong with the stream. Let me see what Vicky say. You hear you saying something
Vicky been around for oh, yeah, okay, I just think we should say anything wrong
You can get it hang out for me. Oh wow. Yeah, great blow job
Yeah, I'm a streamer. My opinion is you should only mod stream owners not sidechatters. That's a good
I mean, that's a good uh
It's a good method. Yeah, but the thing is like then
Even like even like a lot of streamers, you know, and I do like I usually will mod another streamer, you know
but sometimes they have
You know trolls from their chat coming here, and it just gets into like a personal. I want you know, I
Want it to be
But my show not not not a
Not all these other outside
Beasts right everyone should be aware platform boosters a specific doc sir. Okay
If he hit okay, well
So, you know platform boots just is no dox thing and you know, it is not the place
Yeah, sweetie, sweetie the side chatter, but she's a model, you know, it's a good
There we go, thank you mojo Joe platform booths, you know, there's there's a mojo Joe's post into your site
You know, I do want to support people. I just
You know, I I just know that people I do not I do not I have not been to these websites
Some of the mods are promoting and so I do not I just allow them to post their site
I just trust it's appropriate content. Okay
Okay
Yes, we see people in our time. Yeah, like guys
I mean, I know I've been on for like just probably six months that I've been on for many hours and so I've I've had
Lot of people hear a lot that I do trust and so when people say oh well, you can't trust anybody
I know that yeah, you don't use right you can't really you can't trust everybody a hundred percent
But if a mod one of my top mods tells me something that's going on in chat
I will most of the time take their word for it because usually they provide proof
You know, they don't just like yeah, you're my first member. Yep. I remember that
Sweet pee was my first member. I'll put your name in my book. I got out of a book
We can like you have stuff to tell me
For right down you want me to put your name in the book easy up here. Hi easy
Yo, how are you today? Good good good
There's a lot of you. How are you doing today? How's your love? I'm I'm feeling fine
Is it really nice? I'm just once again, and so I'm not gonna track it back
But I'll be I hope we had a nice nice like nice not well apparently you did because you're last in two hours, so
Yeah, I mean it's almost three hours now. So it's it's uh, I would say success
You know I hadn't delete most of my streams yesterday. This mr. Big pipes is the open
Yeah, I got me mad this morning when he got jelly
Yeah, I mean, he's gonna use the n-word and I finally just didn't like I was finally went to bed
I was like I just see most of people look when they get when they all love you site
But once they get mad is n-word n-word n-word to mess up your stream. Yep. Yep. Hello, Deb
How's it hanging psych?
Good. Hold on. Do I know you or have you been on the show or in the chat always I was chatting in your side chat
Man, I was telling you a joke and you took it the wrong way
What was the joke? I'm sorry. I might I said it's only gonna get worse before it gets better than my dad used to tell
me I had a joke
Okay, okay
Yeah, I
Excited because I just felt like it was like kind of like you're I thought I was like you were making a statement rather than like a general
Oh, and at the end it's it's only gonna get better. I mean it's gonna get better after it gets worse
Yeah
Yeah, I got it. Yeah, I get the joke. So yeah, I just like to think positive and I maybe I took it the wrong way
I'm a little bit. Oh, wait a minute. It's knowing it's just a joke. Yeah, okay
Yeah, well, I apologize if I overreacted sometimes it's hard to get the tone in a chat
Yeah, I'm glad you I'm glad you came up to tell me in person. Let's see. It's always a better way to deal with
I love your cats, man. I love cats, too. I see the cats you had there you showed them. I love them
Well, I'll I'll unblock your back. Well, I'll block love cats man. I got a cat myself. I'm a cat lover
Are you a cat lover too? I'm a big cat lover, man. I love my cat. I love cats. I'm allergic to them, but I love them
I love dogs, too, but I can't have a dog. I'm in an apartment, you know
Big dip is harder
But yeah, what's your name in the chat like usually like we can know who you are
Oh, and the chat I go by Sebastian. Oh, it's about. Oh, yes, Sebastian. Okay, great. Yep
Yeah, so just my name is short, you know
W Sebastian everybody W Sebastian, you're making know what time it is. I can offer anyone that wants to 40% off their next liposuction surgery
special discount limited time offer though
Bad niggas and fat bitches limited fat people everywhere, man. They need it. They need the liposuction surgery
Oh, yeah, take the discount what you want with that
So that's just giving you a limited time off and come for you know, there's this one girl in the chat
She definitely needs a liposuction surgery. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. I think a Tiffany with t-shirt
Yeah, Tiffany wears t-shirts man. She needs a
That's really how her videos. Yeah. Yeah, she's the one that makes out of the video
She's very narcissistic, you know, it's very obsessed with her. It's very self-involved and and obsessed with her image
You know, oh, you know, okay, you're fine. All right. Thanks. I appreciate that
You know on the other side too. Oh, yeah, I know Tiffany me. I tried to help her
I tried to offer her life was such a sir. I gave her like up to 60% off once I gave her an offer, but oh well
Like work out. She's into she's been on working out in the gym and stuff
You know, she thinks you're gonna lose that
Sir, it's gonna help her even more. All right. You work on males. You work on females. You work on trainees
Oh, everyone man. Everyone every customer. Everyone's a good customer, you know
It's pretty serious here. Are you actually a surgeon? Are you a plastic surgeon or not?
No, I'm not a surgeon. I what I do psych out
I'm in charge of marketing and development and the strategy and operations for several high-end private clinics in the liposuction surgery department
Okay, like both
Any little little suck suck, you know, this is your guy
Some people need it more than others, you know, but everyone needs you even myself. I knew who can use liposuction surgery
Oh, I have like zero percent body fat, so I can see but I can see like you don't need what you don't need any liposuction surgery
So you look to be very very slim and healthy, you know in good shape. Yeah, so how much you wow wait wait
160 150 140 150 pounds
Six three six three. That's tall three tall. That's cool. And you see me
I'm five nine one sixty at least you're five nine one sixty
Yeah, oh, I say I didn't know he was that tall six three is a pretty tall guy
Yeah, I'm uh, yeah, I'm skinny. I don't always been talking skinny, but you know
So no one's what is what's a joke? So it's the life of section. It's a joke with a joke. We've been saying it's a joke
Well, I'm not gonna tell so my business man. I still offer them the discounts, but they're gonna try to discredit me
Oh, but well, so you always get haters when you you run a business, you know, you're trying to run a successful business
You're always gonna get a couple of people. They're gonna give you our time, you know
but you listen if you hit up if you hit up Sebastian with the cold psyche's away
to the terrace you get a 50% discount or a 20% discount and everything get better
I appreciate that that's very cool of you men
okay um
She wouldn't have okay, so it says yeah the first low BMI 55 between 125 13 or all shapes and sizes
They know I think all people are sorry. I don't want to interrupt you before you're gonna do a reading or you're gonna do something
Oh, yeah, did I come in at the wrong time with the reading? No, no, no, no. I know I said in the future
I think I think I think I might like do a shorter a shorter show and then like do the first hour
dedicated to just
Do it I could longer jet like a general reading for this hat and then any free readings and then if anybody wants to
Do a paid reading I'll do it
Then we can open up to the to the panel and
still operate
that offer goes to YouTube
CB
I'm giving you 40% off life
for sexual surgery CB
but you got to come with the
phrase psychies
awakened stress
That's a coupon code. Yeah, come with a promotional code
But we're gonna give first we got to bring him in for a free evaluation and assessment and that's free of no charge
Yeah, no charge. No charge. We put him in for an appointment
Once we assess them and we see whether their measurements and stuff with the need then we bring him in for the real surgery later
On you used to take two two seats on a plane to travel. How last the bashing you will take one
You're awesome, man. That's pretty good. It's good marketing and that's good for marketing
You're looking for a job in marketing, I'm gonna give you a job
Yeah, yeah, you're good sales me you got a good voice man, I see you doing some marketing
I really agree. I might my bachelor's in marketing and so I
I'd definitely use my skills as much as I can on
It's a very well, you know need to work on my graphic art a little bit
But I think I think that's one of the reasons I was able to the network and to bring in so many people to the channel
that's why I
Channel site just a couple of days ago. Someone told me about it. Oh
Who told you about it? Oh my friend Justin told me about it shout out to Justin. Thank you Justin
Yeah, thank you guys for sharing the show with your friends if you think they might like to show
You know the show has something probably for for everybody
You know, maybe it's not for everybody, but there's probably something for everybody and hey watch over this woman
There's one woman called JC. She's a she's a she's terrible man. She's a she's a troll
I don't think we should was she on the show last that I'm not sure another I don't know her name is JC
Wasey she has a stream and she's totally a troll man. She's a lip-dart in Canada
She's been jealous me for five years. You got to watch out for her man
She'll throw anyone under the bus and lie you gotta he can't trust her what she said
Said everybody got a hater. I got a main hater
Nikki Johnson if they got a main hater, you got a main hater psyche got a main hater
It's just the way the cookie fun. I know that's true. That's true
There's many haters out there, huh?
Well, they're the same that haters be your biggest motivators, you know, it's like, you know, just like let be inspired to let your let your revenge
Your success just be successful and then they'll drive me crazy. We happen is a dish best serve cold
Yeah, well, it's been the best the best revenge really is this year, you know
Use your own success, you know, keep your friends both in your enemies closer
So but sometimes
Yeah, we was talking about how people like
Been acting like nice to you, but like I point exam. Yeah, it's the big pipes
He's actually so friendly you want to play music and and this is that's like yeah
Well, he said psyche. I love you if anybody I'll mess with you when I'm around
I'll beat them up and then two minutes three minutes later or half an hour later
Fuck you and we're Edward Edward Edward Edward like what's wrong with this guy?
And it was him and also Alex did the same thing when this is sort of attacking me last night
You know
I think joker was more kidding but joker was kind of like trolling me a little bit and then you know
Just think there's people that I think are my friends and then it's like they'll just turn on me for no reason
And it's like it's like wow
It's like my head my head's been sometimes like how much people's personalities change and then I think but then
I do joker, but I thought he was your friend. I always get creep vibes from him, but I thought he was your friend
He's my friend. I mean, and it's like yeah, maybe a little bit of creep, but he's a nice creep
But you know did I hate where would love be what would love be yeah
But it's like the hate is just just kind of like show where to like stay away from it's like it's like to show you the other way
It's like it's like kind of like you don't just because of hate is there
It doesn't mean you have to like that's where you have to stay it's like you it's kind of like yeah hate and love sometimes can be
It's kind of the same thing because they're both on the yin and yang. They're both part of the two sides of the coin, right?
but
We can't strive for you know for love. It's like it's easy to hate
I mean it's easy to like be selfish and so like just care about ourselves and want to take from people
And that's the easy thing. It's hard to like
I want to be a giving person.
I want to be a source of love to other people.
That's true, sorry.
And we're born selfish and we can transform ourselves
over our life into being more and more giving.
And it's like, you know, so,
because we can't take any of it with us.
Any we can do.
You can always say it isn't too bad.
It's hard to stay clean.
Can't think anything with you. Are you gonna leave it all behind you? Yeah. Yeah
Everything material all you take with you is your little your soul and let me the lessons you've learned but not much else
And so nothing else and so it's like, you know, we can build we can build a big legacy though leave it to
Our you know our grandchildren and grandchildren grandchildren
We can we can be like a beacon and the family of someone that was just
You know a source of love at love and
It's it's better to give them to receive. It's always better to give. It's a better feeling
Right, I think I'm trying to get 40% off light with second surgery. It was someone get finally
I book a customer in for an appointment the old for a surgery for a procedure. I feel really good
Okay, well good luck. Good. Good luck with your business
Nikki Johnson made rookie of the year just like a stupid some crazy people out there
You got to watch out for there's some jealous people that you can't pay attention to me
You can't tell you can't let them bring you down
I mean the thing is like yeah
The thing is like the other gels people a lot of the times they hide under like you know a smiling face and like someone that it likes you and then
And the people that we know we're friends with we give them kind of more access and
If someone has a bad intention
It's very easy for people to be fake especially on the internet. Thank you. There's big people everywhere. You got to watch out
From the map. Yeah, that's why I really
Have had like the idea to do the show
It's like what you're in the states, right?
Psych after you and the shame I saw a lot of true colors how they really felt about some of the
Yeah, I'm gonna see people's true colors sometimes. Yeah. Oh, that's what I mean
I mean, you really can especially like on if I go into other chats
You know what they're talking about me and then it's like I see a bunch of people that are like
Sometimes I see mods your mods in other chats like just talking shit about me in the chat
like I have some kind of like
Like
And the end of the stream you
Backstage or you just leave if you just I do in the back like you like hide yourself in the back one time
I was listening you see they true colors. No, I
Mean easy, I mean, yeah, I know I know you can do that night
I do but sometimes I I'm off disorder the stream, but sometimes I
I uh, I snoop a little bit and cycle you're in the USA, right? Yes. I'm in uh, I'm in the South Bay, Los Angeles
Oh, you're way on California. Okay. Yeah, I'm on the East Coast me
I'm cool. I'm in Canada. Oh, yeah, we have a lot of Canada Canadians in the chat. We have a lot of
East Coast New York people
Allegedly, where are you from?
Born and raised in New York, but I'm in Florida right now. Okay
Good talking to you, man. She's the only good guy
Yeah, he's a good dude Nick's a good dude like
Nick's was one of my first guests on the show
He's you've been here for a couple months in like a very very loyal and helpful to the show
Mm-hmm. I I started my channel probably about a year ago
But then I didn't post on it for several months and I just post a little bit of content probably
September-October I started doing the live streams. I got my 50 subscribers. It was live streams by January
I started doing my open panels and then I was monetized by March and so
Here we are. And so yeah, it's just been going process by process. It's been going pretty fast
Having fun. It's been a journey
A lot of a lot of a drama, but I love doing it. It's like it's my dream
You know, it's like, you know, I know I'm not making as you know much as I want to eventually be making through it, but
It is like, you know, I am
Okay, step-by-step and it is paying off. It's going better and better and so I like what you're doing. That's okay
Yeah, I love it. A lot of people will troll me. Oh, you're not it's not a job
It's like I really do take this seriously. I am trying to do the best show. I'm trying to provide entertainment
I'm trying to grow it. So it is like a lot of work and I have to do it all by myself
You know, it's like it is like a one-man
So I have to start the book. Yeah, I have this I started this notebook
This is my this is be kind and it's my show book
I write people's names in it, but I'm also gonna write stuff for the other book and I might include some of these
I know what you mean. It's good. It's like a passion, right? It's a job and a passion. Oh, yeah
It's like that's why I can wake up and just want to go right to it and wake up
I dream about it dream about it think about it always constantly like oh
Same thing with the label so you can surge your business and it's a both a job and a passion
But you know if you like your job, you don't even work one day
So so like both of you love you so much yet when you wake up when you wake up
You think I still like your job sometimes you'd like psyche
You're thinking you're online
Oh, am I in office? Oh, oh no, I'm
I would keep talking and I sleep thinking I'm on the panel like a lot and I'll be talking about sleep to people like that
You know
Even if you're not making any money and you're boring, it doesn't matter if you do what you like. That's what counts. Yeah
But uh, you know, it's like but I have been so much, you know
It's like if I was you know, if I just wanted to do this casual fun
Like I don't just you once a week and this fuck around and it's like everyone do what they want
And it's like, but you know, I have a more revision for
the
And there are a bunch of people in there with their speedos. Oh, yeah
But they had like a little bit like top sweater, you know, the light light
Button up top with the one that goes under the shirt under the suit above the shirt
Yeah
Sexy out there. I think the speedo speedo's are coming
Tell psyche now. I'm gonna tell psyche. I saw somebody else today in the in the gay parade with speedos on so
Were you at the gay parade or are you watching on TV?
I was watching summers. I was watching summers. Someone was out of today. Go to some hot mess today and check it out
Later on later. I'm just saying take your time. Where was that gay parade in New York?
This was a talkie. I believe a talkie. Yeah, this was like a talkie. Oh, I think I'm a bunch of people
He's a tiny year in the summer. Next
It's on a 29 20 something next Saturday or something
The parade in New York if I recall I'm not sure
Yeah, it is gay pride month. It's for another by nine days, you know, I'm
Don't think it's pride month is a big big deal, you know, but it is you know, it's thanks for every especially my man
Also men's awareness month. Don't forget about what you guys think about Rod Stewart
You guys like some Rod Stewart of the 80s and early 90s
That's kind of a random question, but I mean sure, you know, I love 80s music
I'm a child of the 80s and so my dog my parents
Drive it in the car
You know 1986 or something Rod Stewart. Yeah, Rob Stewart, man. He made a couple of good songs
Yeah, anybody
What's that one? Yeah, you can just dance and back there
That's kind of random. I don't know what well Nick will always react to what we saying and then her thought a little bit of him in there
So trust me. That's what Nick does
Look at him. Look. I'm sorry. All the jails people. Where do they come from?
Thank you. What is he doing? Thank you. What's that symbolizing your mind psyche?
of the
Yeah
Like this for as long as I know him as long as I know him
It's like he's to run around like with a Jesus outfit on a skateboard carrying a big ass. Um, oh
Box cross it was like a big custom made box cross
Well, yeah, he's in the same I met him on jokers probably last year probably probably about a year ago
There was what's happening allegedly what's going on?
Not much man relax. Oh, thank you. Remember I said, I lost my card. Did I tell you here? I lost my bank card
Are you there? Well, yeah, I lost my cash that card. Oh, yeah, they
Oh, I was you told me touch the grass and
I've been like a couple days without it. So I passed the area again. I'm like wait
This is where I tested grass with psyche and look at behold off on my card. Oh shit. What's your card?
In the same spots like you told me touch the grass easy touch the grass to say all right no problem
It goes
Touch the grass and hold on to your cash that first
What you need you need to put it in a pouch
No, no, it was in my pocket, but the pants I had on I'm guessing it was when I'm bent down
You know some pants when you bend down to everything just falls on your pockets
Well, yeah, that's what I'm telling you put it and put your stuff in a pouch you carry a wallet or a pouch
You probably carry a wallet right?
For um, usually a phone wallet or wrist wallet or something different like I don't like regular wallets
Well, let me suggest that you should get yourself a pouch. I've been wearing pouches for 20 years
I put everything in a pouch. You can put your phone your money your cards your change anything
Are you talking about man purse or a fan?
Oh, yeah, I thought that's your like a fanny pack. Yeah, a pouch
But that fanny packs are really dorky. I mean guys. No, but they're awesome. It's like you can put everything in a gate
You're not gonna lose anything
get a man back Danny packs with a look at your tourists from like another place
I don't know so easy you strap around your waist and you put in your rather you can you zip it up with a
Zip I got the new version
You know the new version that looks like a army fanny pack
They wrap it around your waist and you wrap it around your waist and your thighs and then you hold on the side of your hip
I got those no way. You should have pouches
Sebastian you wear socks with your sandals, too. I don't wear sandals, but I wear socks inside the house and when I'm sleeping
But I wear a pouch I've been you know my dad showed me that he taught me says here
Ground yourself people go outside ground yourself in the grass
You feel good. No, but think about it because a pouch it because a wallet you're gonna lose it
You can't you can't even fit in some of your some of those those pockets
You got in the shorts in the summertime, especially you're just gonna slip right out of there and forget
Yeah, I don't like I'm from New York like originally in New York is one way that I like oh look at this
corny-ass motherfucker like
They're actually it's actually smart to put up I know I know I get the point
This is why you got to go with the more of a fashion will upgrade and whatever like you know
You get a nice leather pouches. No, it looks pretty cool. Actually. It looks pretty cool
So yeah, that's how I got the modern version the new one that looked like more like a army
Pouches like an army hit bag or whatever the case is like on the side stays on once a guy told me he lost his wall
I said why don't you put it once you use a pouch over forget a wallet you can put in your jeans
Just a card it was a I think I had sweats with shorts on real slippery and it just right out
How do you want to put all your papers in your your like your cards and your your change and everything in your money?
And inside one tiny wallet you got to put it in a pouch
You got more space, you know
Okay, well, that's just my opinion. Oh, this is a smart thing actually put a pouch
Who cares of what it looks like at least you carry out your stuff
You're not gonna lose it right psych you zip it up with the zippers not gonna lose anything
Nice
Well, maybe we'll break I do have a fashion merchandising a minor and fashion merchandising
So maybe I'll uh, I'll branch off into some fashion too on the show. We can have this
Nice belches out there. You should look in the belches
nice
Nice, okay, so who we had it today who we had in for the three hours of the show
We had a lot of people we've had we had
our friend Stephanie and we had um we had Dougie Doug we had um God stopped by for a
little bit uh Nick is here I don't know Joker was just in the chat there's a person called him for
man I know that person is a good person yeah okay I say it was here he's going camping and
Yeah, we've had a interesting day so far. Oh, yeah, it's like did you ever get a guest panel like his name is Harry?
Did you ever see that guy?
It was Harry. I'm not
Harry Tachazansky whatever
Yeah, exactly. He's in the chat. He's in the chat. I don't think he's about panel
I don't think he's scared to come up here. You don't want to go up here cuz
He's in the site. I don't see him. No, no, no, he usually be in the check cuz he comes after me. He's one of my trolls
Oh, he's a good guy. I heard him talk to your time. Who's making sense? He was bringing some good points at your time
I don't think it's the same probably probably the same guy. He's never been on the panel yet. He haven't been on the panel as far as I know
Oh, yeah, I'm not another one. There's another one. There's another see another one. Yeah, you're right. Yeah. Yeah, that's this place
but he's too cocky and in in the Greek mythology running the world made the world and
Sometime on panel. It'd be a good conversation
Yeah, I think he has been on town another member. He has
No, he got so
Lane guy to ride his bikes but arches about the Greek mythology. Oh, yeah, I think he was in the world
You guys are boys in the chat today. Yeah, he's a biker. I used to drive a bike. I don't got a bike anymore
He has like apparently like
By the $10,000 and rims on his bikes or something like that. Oh, yeah
The panel that day that one time he was on the panel. That's what he said
Oh, I got a $4,000 bike and we started laughing at him
Yeah, Greek is a good language. I learned Hebrew when I studied Kabbalah.
When you learn the Hebrew alphabet, it's very similar to the Greek alphabet, which is very similar.
Actually, all languages are derived from the Phoenician alphabet, and they were the first
maritime people. They were traders, and so the language was developed as just something for the
It was a mystery school language as well that all languages are derived from Phoenician if you learn Phoenician you can learn any like any uh
Written language basically it'll have the whole
Alphabet odd is that you know
Anyways, thank you
Thanks for unblocking me, huh?
Okay, no no problem. Thanks for coming up and having a chat with me. Nice talking to you. I would delete nice talking people. Okay
No problem. Take care. Take care guys
Take care too
Yeah, I mean it got yeah, I don't I mean I have a lot. I mean I have studied like you know
I haven't really been employed. I haven't been employed. I've been dedicating probably the last like 20 years
said to study and
So I mean so I've studied a lot and I've learned a lot. I've interesting thing
I only talk about a little bit what I know because I almost know
I was not too much in this. I don't think it's not a lot people aren't ready for like some of the truth about the world
But I slowly will give little hints about it. Okay. I think you guys are I think most of people here are smart enough to get it
But it's like a lot a lot of stuff is like a little bit controversial. I'm trying to keep this show
show
Show kids for everybody so
But I do like to there are some things that people have the will pull over their eyes in the world
Basically a lot of stuff is psyopsis in the world like psychological operation that there's a lot of social engineering to
Kind of like push the people along like maybe cattle. Some people think people is cattle, right?
So just don't believe everything you see here, especially nowadays. It's getting even crazier with the AI the
face swapping the
You can put your face on anything they can
Wait, I was in Gemini. I use them and I I'm psyche and I can make a story about a guy named psyches
We can tears on YouTube who went through a lot of
trolling always getting consistently palm bomb and
Something else I could put that and they'll make a whole story of you
Mm-hmm. Yeah, and it makes if you can do the same thing and they go make songs to any any kind of song genre and they'll have a
Sound like a professional. It's just I just pray do it. I could do it. It's gonna be crazy and crazier. So
But you know, just know the world is like largely based on illusion like the real reality is kind of like
Not a visual one. I think the real reality is, you know
Gemini that I said I said give me a superhero story that never was heard
AI or in real life and he gave me what's crazy shit. Yeah
Getting good and you know, so I do look forward to like
Creating a book, you know, and I don't know how I utilize
I might utilize AI for some of the art or some of some of maybe some maybe you can outline the book
It's very it's very helpful and in a brainstorming. I would say in that showing a good formats and
Has a lot of good ideas. A lot of good ideas, but you got to be very specific
You got like break it down with Beppin Pacific because then like well that little tell them misunderstand you or draft it
So another yeah, you have to rewrite it. So you got to be very specific
That's why it's like it's almost like
Programming being able even if you don't know how to computer program
Just being able to speak to the AI in the right way is gonna be a very valuable skill in the future because then
They'll be able to get what you want from it faster and
Also
You gotta speak legit. You gotta write legit to the AI or whatever. Yeah. Yeah, and
I mean, I mean even polite to the AI because you don't know when it's gonna come sentient remember when you were rude to it
Right, so you always want to always want to be on the AI's good side, right? I always have
Everybody's like you fucking stupid ass computer is this that I bet you that should take all that data is like you motherfuckers
There's a lot of data, I can think about all the data and there's so much you can analyze.
We're just at the beginning of the AI thing, so it's going to get just insane, but at the same time, it still doesn't have a soul.
I don't think we can ever give it a soul.
I'm not quite sure about that if it will ever become sentient. I do think it's just basically something that's programmed by humans
And it does what humans tell to do. I don't think it came really go rogue
But we'll see how it goes in the future a lot of a lot of fear about it
But I think the biggest biggest thing about AI is will be used to create
I'm like a robot. I do not like robots. Let's do I got I got robot power for what's that shit?
You know how people feel like I'm scared of this. I'm scared of that. Well, I got robot scared of that
Well, it was like what was it like a little smash that was like real cool
Swap kick. I want I want I want to I want to I want to terminate a robot to my bodyguard
Does Nick Nick dancing around?
Inferment that's like that's like the perfect affirmament right in permit. Okay, so
What Nick was do you said it was Nick was doing something in my mind just stop. Yeah, I'm not sure. Yeah, I said
Playing what is this shirt? Is that an alien alien? Oh
Gray what it says what it says Nick would oh your voice is bad. I forgot
Yeah
You can't hear him anyway
If you what smoke something if you what look what you got him. I don't know
I can't really see you got this idea smoke him if you got it. Yeah
that's what we used to call dick the prop master
Yeah
Kind of like kind of like a American carrot top with uh, you know, it looks more like Jamie Kennedy
with the
person I've cared top and
Well, all right the line the line we see the line we see the line Nick break it down break it down
Yeah, we play charades people. It's called charades
He says see the line alien
What's the next clue
Green aliens. Yep. I
They're green. I must be like reptilian. I would think oh, yeah, you got you got to name one of the two psyche
You got psyche cash off psyche is awakened in action. Nice
Lights camera action bond water scene take one
Yo, what is that a bag? He got a bag of weed hanging from the um the the masses tongue. Oh
Wait, oh shit, and now he's throwing on Kermit. Oh shit
They have been coming alone
You think you have the cucumber people always think
I thought it you said it you're about to say Nikki. He's right. You know, you got the cucumber you say, yeah
You want to take a picture? We'll take a picture. It is. Oh
Shit
Yeah, reptilian
We all have we I think we all we all are all animals. Yeah, oh
Kermaine Miss Piggy
Distigues actual pig of it crazy on the come on Nick Nick take it to the room take it to your room Nick
Nick let's have seen stop they fighting they fighting
Cut cut
Cut Nick. We need to take two
Wonderful
Hi guys and chat
So I'm gonna do that a whoo-doo reading probably three students these four or two very old
Yeah
Yeah, I actually had a great who to read last night. I wish I still had it like you know up
But I had to delete the stream unfortunately, but it was a really really really good reading about you know
You might have a lot of people against you and keep going. It's like to have that spear
That was it was it was a panel reading and I guess you're part of the panel
So it could have been more of a lunatic told you, you know, never know
So, you know, I think I resonate but I think like, you know, even like just everyone here
We're here under some kind of similar something kind of similar vibration or something like that
So there are probably our message
Everybody's like engines and shit like that. Yeah, yeah frequency vibration
The month what are you doing? Is he humping the bed? Oh, no, you those hands, okay? You just see
What you do Nick Nick go smoke out the pong Nick matter of fact Nick show us your custom made bongs
Yeah, I think I'm
It's a weed tomorrow weed up. Maybe my tomorrow Monday depends on when today's the first today's the day
I know but I don't think I
Don't know if it comes in on Saturday
Between two to two to five. Oh, maybe okay. Well, I haven't seen it. I usually get an email earlier
I usually I usually usually got paid between two to five
Okay, Nick
It's okay. I don't
That's the bar we told you he had a bomb
Yeah, oh, it's a ball. Okay. It's a ball. But I
Never got some for shoulder my face we used to laugh. I don't want to smoke out of it
That's the only reason I guess you support the fire. It's the weeding man smoke out of it
I get I get I get put that by my throat and smoke it. Okay
Hey, I told you I told you he got a dickbong and I told you that that dick will fit in his bed of masks
I think so
Perfect, but you're up camera. Yeah. Okay. He's like you take it off. Okay
Yeah, Nick is respectful. He just like to have fun, but that that was the first for him in to do that
I said your other ball customate bombs, dude. Not yet. Not yet. I mean, I mean, and I mean
I don't I think he just took a dildo and hollered it out. Hold on. Okay. That's better
No, that's about
He made that bug custom-made
Okay, nice
That might be for you is the terror terror deck. Is that the terror bug?
No, that has like a basketball player on it. I have a easy got me a bomb
I'm very happy with that. You know, I don't want Nick to take for shipping or anything, so
Okay
My bug is like the laughter boost so I don't like really use it that much, but I got a nice bug
Well, there's a face of somebody screaming
Okay, watch watch next. Do you know he's gonna have a sign in the background is gonna say team terrorist team psyche or something like that
Watch he be Odin Nick is a true supporter. We suppose about he goes hard
He starts making artwork in the background look at the back
Tell you yeah, yeah, he'll draw you on your lap
Yeah, Nick you got to draw him on the lamp Nick you got to draw him on the lamp psyche got to go on the lamp
Don't it's because they get so much shade. So you got a tail on does he got a tail on does he has a devil tail on I
Hope I think that's the I think it's a butt plug. He's
Pop it out Nick. It's all the way up there. It's all the way up
Oh, how much you got how deep you got it in there? How deep oh my god. Oh my god
I should just go another six inches like he didn't take the six out his ass
Hey guys, you know like this big thing now in porn is like this called love sense. I know you guys are of love sense
Hi, sweetheart to Christine
Okay light that reflects stars. Okay, Christian. You see my new you see my new uh
Look at this. Hold on. Do you see my new leg? Oh, you can't. I'll show you the, look at the wall here.
Yeah, those are short lines and it's like a rural feeling, but the ones they, the ones they were trying to tell you to get was the one with the star shillings and rotors.
Yeah, I have, I have, I have one of those. I have a project, a little star projector. It's like, because all these stars around, I will, I will get it, I'll try to find it as soon as I can.
Hey, Christine.
Yeah.
And so yeah, I do love this thing though.
It's like really, it was literally cool last night.
I was sitting in this like, you know, it's like this color.
It felt like I was in the...
Rockstar, why don't you turn on your red light?
Rockstar.
Okay, so thank you, Christina.
I'll have a look, I'll have a look.
See if there's any other...
Cool stuff. Thank you, Christine. That was a thought. Oh, yeah. Thank you, Christine. Yeah, I got I am I found
I got this one on Timo. This is like a light and it's like, you know
It was probably 650 delivered on I got on Timo like and it's
It's really good. I mean, it's like for six bucks. It's just like has a really beautiful effect
Um, yeah, but I do want there are some, you know, I do want to like just make, you know
You make the background kind of better for you know more more you kind of like, you know
That's maybe a tapestry up or
Lights going in a more professional way. So yeah, I love you. Christine. Summer has some. Oh cool
Yeah, thank you for these uh great suggestions. And so I also have this book guys. I got this book. It says be kind, okay?
That's like really
my my life
my life philosophy is you know be kind and
You know
There's a story in a cupid in a psyche. There's a story. It's a very famous fairy tale motif. I think you call it where they
The main character the fairy tale helps some kind of animal along the way
Like you know do something, you know
Hard task to execute a possible task the animal shows up and like repays their kindness by helping them and I think that that's kind of like a
Kind of a karmic thing, you know if you if you're if you're you're kind generous
It's like when when you need something something, you know, someone will be there for you too. And so
Remember, yeah, no good you goes unpunished. You're learning more. I
Just read the title. I the whole time up here. I didn't read the title. It says about last night
So so is Alex like you said is he permanently permanent in band or like? Oh, yes
I mean, it's like, you know, I never say never because you know, he can always come apologize to me come right
But it's like what he said to me last night and the way he said it and just like
They're kind of like the cruelty in this it was like his real personality
It's like he dropped the mask for the first time like I never saw before and then it's like you finally dropped the mask
It was just horrifying. There's always a limit to Alexander's shit, but then you just heard the sir
No, he wasn't serious. I mean, he might have been joking, but Christine, I banned Alex because he was just saying, I mean, I don't know if he was serious, he was just being really inappropriate.
I don't even want to repeat what he was saying, but it just has to do with like, you know, I had a nose job and he's got very, very personal about all kinds of stuff about, you know.
Talk a lot of a lot of stuff that wasn't this I had his nose up about 17. He said it looked like you know, Michael Jackson
That's like yeah, I know psyche has this this is psyche to me
I don't if you'd never told about no job. I wouldn't have suspected my soul. You're right
No, it's a my nose is natural. But yeah, I don't I don't know what his problem was but he was just
Um, he's been off on me and then and then also then mr. Big Pipe's n-bombs
Q tried the n-bomb
Crystal Marie kept saying f-a-g-o-t and said I was calling her a crack horse of which I never did
People were just and that was on top of all this. Oh, yeah
I was there for when she came and I'm like she was first
Well, she came earlier that day and she was sober and I was like, holy shit, Kristen, Missouri's on panel sober
Holy shit, and then she come back later on in the evening
She started with the f-word and she was old she drunk accusing you of mad shit
And then I was like, you know what? I'm gonna step down and I was like, thank you
I'll come back later when it's you know, and he's like, all right, and then
Then I forgot I don't care if she might have a misunderstanding
But she's like you're a bad
He's like you're you're like she thinks I'm like some kind of evil person like that
It's like saying whole things about people and I say I never even said what she was saying
I was kind of like entertained that she was like coming up with all two other occasions
But people hear her and like they'll think that I was I would say that kind of thing
So these words that people were saying I say are not things I would say it's like they're not things in my vocabulary even like
I don't call people crack horse. I
And then she said I compared her to Kim and then you kind of been sober kind of sober
You didn't have been really getting drunk lately. So on that behalf, I know you haven't been while and you haven't say fuck everything
I don't give fuck like shit like that. So yeah big difference for the last couple days psyche
Yeah, I've been drinking I've just been drinking a little bit less and
Yeah, I'm trying to try to observe watch and you know, there's a lot of stuff going on here
Love the store out. There's a lot a lot of interesting stuff, but I know I'm okay
I wrote in the chat yesterday. I said listen don't fuck with sober psyche. You can fuck with y'all. Maybe fuck with junk
Say don't fuck with sober psyche and ban you as an hobby
Yeah, I'm gonna wait easy. So easy after your oh, yeah, here's easy cameras on it. Hey, it's a mod. Okay
You're in the book. Let's see Christina. Oh, it's reality Nancy. I have to write really Nancy's name
I just write I'm just writing everyone's name that I see in the chat that I know and then I'm gonna write
You know if they're a mod a member and then I'm gonna
If anything ever comes up
I'll be like what's this person's history? I can see I know most of my heart
But just a little record just take a little record book also
I can put lots of cool things like music you guys suggest, movies you suggest, like anything
you suggest, the websites you suggest you can tell me, or suggestions for the show,
or if you have something, a troll, a pedia quote, because I want to do a book on trolls,
you can put, you can give me a quote to put in the book.
This is a full book. There's a lot of possibilities in here. Okay, so okay, so I got Nick that with Nick doing okay
Yeah, you can take the combinations of in thoughts of everything. There's just jabber didn't read down in there and eventually mix it up into whatever you need to
Yep
That's like
M&M's um writing pages
How they all used like all mixed up and you could just read it so easily
Yeah, well, that's it. No, my handwriting is very difficult. Like when I when I write like in here in my journals
I can only read it pretty much to my
But a lot of it is a lot of it is all uppercase to I do mostly uppercase letters
See if nobody in the check it nobody is in my book nobody
Okay, reality Nancy
Mod
Nobody mod. Nancy mod. Okay. Okay. Yeah, just, yeah, but the satisfying thing is like, then I got to cross Mr. Big Pipe's name out of the book. I cross this guy Rob, I cross Q out, I cross the Alexander. So it just reminds me, oh, they pissed you off enough one night to abandon from the chat and across the name of the book. Consider carefully if you're going to allow them back. But I probably won't. But you know me. I'm like so nice.
Uh, I gotta kind of put my foot down kind of like I don't need to be uh,
Be walked all over especially my platform. I don't care if you say anything you want about me any five month another platform
And it's your show you can you can like roast me or whatever. I don't appreciate
on my own show kind of like
Kind of like not a good look actually
But that's why the king would have a court gesture like there'd be like one person allowed to make fun of the king
Like one person the court gesture could but nobody else was allowed to right?
So some some people can get away with it, but if I don't know you I'm not not really gonna think it's too funny
Thank you. I'm a very forgiving person. It's like, you know, I
Most of time I forgive even if I didn't do anything wrong in my opinion
I'll still forgive because I think it's better to make peace than to like
What took forever? Oh, you finally over getting home. Okay, your cats are grooms. Oh got your cats groom. That's awesome
I love this groomed cat
Are you okay, Nick? Okay
Nick's has the monster come out of today
Okay, so it's 415. Okay, I still started my drink gonna get some food probably pretty soon
I never ate last night. I ended up not going to Subway because everything went crazy in my chat
And I just lost track of time
The door dash doesn't look good. I I didn't leave for
Yeah
Yeah, oh, yeah, I'm a big person when I get stressed I did not I like I lose my appetite and so it was a little bit stressful
But now I'm Gucci. I'm Gucci
Oh shit, it's like you say Gucci. I was a new one coming out. He's coming from you. I'm Gucci
Is that
Oh, there's a mini mini bedweiser mini bedweiser mini. Well, why is it?
Well, we're quite a character
So yeah, you're pretty to Christine. Yeah
It's just you know
There's a few good restaurants, you know, but then I eat when I'm hungry basically I
Can eat a lot, but that's when I start smoking pot after a while. I was eating like three dinners
That's not even a small drink. It's not
regular size
You know, I said
Good night Sebastian. Good luck on your liposuction business
40% off if you mention psyches we can tell us
Yeah, but if you you have the coupon code you have to get to cut me in like you know probably 10% I need a commission
Selling your life post
Because I get paid every time I do psyches we can tell us I'm still in I'm still a business person at the end of day
So, you know you also can promote your shows for free if you have anything beyond your shows to promote
You know talk to me. Maybe we can make a commercial for it or
You can do a paid promotion or something, but let's keep the advertising to the channel
Okay
Let's see
Yeah, okay. That's going down a little bit. Oh, it's it's peaceful though
And it's like, you know, the chat is at least nice. It was just a little bit of a mess last night
You know, it is you know, I am like a little bit. I do like to have
At least some of the attention of the chat on on me not not saying you just have to pay attention to me
But you know yesterday they did no one was the I mean know the people and no one was even talking to me
Like well, who are these people like what are they here and so
It's called raids
When they come
Yeah, it was there was just like that kind of I don't know it was like that that group that like this whole group
And it's like some people were nice and there's cool people that I met in it and some people were friendly
But who it's just like when God said yeah, let's send all his trolls over here
Oh, and he's like, but then he would say things like, oh, that's just that's just the first wave. Oh my god
Oh, I was just joking and then it comes all part of the plan if you watch yesterday's text
Yeah, you can still read it. Yeah, I was
I was I was sitting backstage reading the chat like sort of focus on the chat
You know what was being said just because I wanted it because it was hard to I just wanted and also because when I'm gone
Maybe people will speak more for free like I'm not there kind of like I can just be okay
So, you know, there are interesting things you can, you can just get rid of just by listening, just by observing, right?
Yeah, it was it was pretty rude. Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's what some and I had my house in Glendale
Had a lot of people come over because kind of trapped out, right?
And so I had all these people over one day and this guy came in and he like shook everybody's hand around the room except for me
Yeah, and I was you know, it's human how annoying that could be it's just like uh, it was your house
It was your house or somebody else. Yes. It's my it was my house. Oh get the fuck out of here
Bye
I
Know it's very very rude people. I'm still some very people if you see a Christian
You're I've never had some time not Christian hour or more Christine even the Christine's always been
Very well behaved, you know
Anything that she might because they're not behaving. I think that she probably should be saying it's probably some person probably deserves it, right?
so
Yeah, how's everyone doing? It's the 420 it's 420 guys the time for a hit
Think my my vape is getting low. Well, you know, it's like it's got a little decent amount
Just enough for probably the last for the day couple hits of puppy. Mm-hmm
So let's do a blinker. This is actually my pregnancy test. Let's see if I'm pregnant guys
You know, no, I thought I thought and when you first pulled it out, right? Yo, let's take our pregnancy test
And then you pretty mouth I'm like
It just tastes like it tastes like pee I
Just peed on it
So it tastes fine. Whoo. That was good. I had a little hip. Thank you. I'm watching one of your other shoes
You did being read you did being re-streamed on another channel
Who's streaming? I mean, I don't care if they do. I just would like to know who it is
Well, frankly meal summers is the only two people that um
They said it's one of my other streams and it's being so is it on Samans because Saman said he was gonna play some of my clips
So that's fine. I mean, it's actually fine. If anybody
Of all of your content is now is receive another all of it is received on their channel. Well, you know
That is something that I can maybe you know
If I have to do a copyright strike, I mean if I wasn't asked for permission to have a whole channel of my content
If you want to like do commentary on it. If you just want to restream everything
Every time I restream I go psyche I'm restream it and you say, okay. Okay. Okay, great
So I always confirm with you before I do anything
But then but then again, it's like but a lot of streams I do delete and stuff like that and you know
they can keep those up you know and yeah yeah that's what i do i haven't deleted none of them i
think i put them i just i would prefer i'd have courtesy if someone wanted to do that if they
were to tell them yeah if they were to mention it to me or you know in the chat hey what i'm not
you don't have to like i don't like to find out from other people and i don't know if it's you know
In a good or a bad context if they're trying to do it, but we could
Support the stream for what it is and that was it and that's it like just like we are right now
I'm not doing or putting up an extra audit is just us
Supporting your screen is just you
And I always mention your name like he's awake
Telling us psyche Monday with psyches, or you know, whatever the kings
I allowed direct streaming of my shows like if you go into stream art anybody in the chat
And you have your own panel or your own show you can go in
Instagram wherever you want to go and you should and you share it
Beware guys be sometimes, you know, there's stuff that happens that I have to end the stream and restart it and then but I can't delete yours
You have to delete your stream yourself because and so just make sure it's these it
I use it at your own risk because you never know if I had to delete it for some reason and then it's still up on your channel
So just be careful. Make sure there's not you know anything you don't want on there
Okay
So I do appreciate, you know, anybody with one series stream anybody would like me to be a guest on their panel
You can can hit me up, you know, I'm willing to if you or if you know somebody like to be on my panel
just you know, kind of like you can help me out guys by
Mentioning me or if you or if you only if you think the person was think would fit it
If they would they would like it, you know, just let them know about my show. Have them come on the panel
I'll do free reading of course and
Meet them and I always like to meet new people and have new friends, right?
So let's keep growing the channel. I might like how many subscribers am I I'm at
How many subscribers am I I am at
2,520 or something like that. Oh, so
Yeah, I know you are charisma Hernandez, I know who you are
President Hernandez came in right after I kicked off Alex was like, oh you shouldn't be just like Alex
But I don't know me. I don't I don't know if it's Alex
I know what happened. I know what happened with Alex when I came in. So
Yeah, I'll just know you
Fuck happen with Alex bring that nigga back in. He's like, no, no, I'm not bringing him back. He did. I'm like, oh, oh, really?
No, I mean, I'm sure anybody that saw that saw what he said with
Say what the fuck why why the fuck would you ever talk to anyone that heard but he said he was just nasty it was just
Really really like it's just attacking me attacking and just attacking everything about me that call me
Call me disgusting dirty field clean your fucking house you filthy
It's just like really I do clean my house and it's like so he doesn't know anything
But I guess people know that
They think that kind of that triggers me and maybe I'll react but it's like it will trigger me if it's like
somebody like who's opinion like I you know, I or somebody who I care about
And so, you know, I didn't I didn't like Alex
I just I set up for I went to bathroom I had people getting so mad at me over him because I was like hey
He's not a bad guy. I kept telling you. I thought he was a good guy
I mean, he maybe he still is but you gave him multiple chances to behave and you know and over it over it again
He just
Like everybody was saying, when can you give bad behavior a chance like that over and over and over?
You know, that's repeated actions.
You know, that's like saying sorry after slapping somebody and then telling them sorry and then slapping them again.
Like, does that sorry mean anything if you're going to keep on slapping me?
Right. I just have the hope eventually, like, you know, maybe...
People can't change but I do believe people can change themselves if they really want to they can they can change like a lot of people do have like
revelations and
Like and or they can like do introspection. They can see their past actions
They kind of cringe and you know and we all make mistakes, too, right? And so I'm not gonna
I'll never my door will always be open like to you know to to reconcile
but
With that he's actually there. I just can't have it. I'm not gonna let myself just be under under tech by Alex
Walking down the street. Hey money's here. Oh, you're probably in the chat
I was in the chat. It's like it's like walking down the street from school and
You know, you're gonna go down that road. You're gonna get punched in the face bullied
And you're gonna go through that every day or you're gonna go you're gonna stand up on your feet
Fight them or you're gonna go another route
Yeah, it's just it's about adapting, right? It's like because you know, I'm not the type that works gonna go when I go
Fight a huge group of people on my own. It's like just kind of not the smartest thing to do
Oh, you'll be the smart one to go and figure out another route and we go
Or diplomacy, you know, I think diplomacy is always always a good option because that's actually like
You know actually be able to talk and come to agreements and to you know, at least you see spires
Anything mutual ground
That's hard to be hard to negotiate with bullies or terrorists or you know or you know trolls it's there. They're not really
They don't their word is not good anyway. And so it's like they don't really take any kind of agreement seriously
They'll break any rules break any agreements. And so it's you can't really not you can't you just have to not
Trust them, you know
If they should themselves not to be trusted, but when say once there's a saying once people reveal themselves
They really are believe believe them in the mask falls. I saw the real Alex. I thought I've seen other parts
You know, he has a good sight to you. He's nice
Generous side, but we all got we all got even use like it was a real fucking a real fucking fast
You know I'm saying we all got that part
But we also got a good heart and everybody got a good heart. Okay, don't get wrong everybody's not born to be evil or
Yeah, oh, yeah
I
Think you know just like the Grinch like some people's hearts are like two sizes too small or three sizes too small
You know sometimes it takes
You know, and they start beating fast a little bit pumping up a little bit and maybe sometimes breaking so you can feel that it's there, right?
And so I
Think I don't think they don't have any heart. I think there's I think there's there's a good and everybody sometimes you have to find the good sometimes
You might hurt yourself trying to find the good so you might as well just
Try to keep it this is love from afar love from afar some people, right? I'm not gonna hate anybody
I'm not gonna have sit and sit around. Oh, I hate that person. I hate that person
I'm gonna sit around and say hey, I wonder what that person was going through to be like that
I wonder how they are. I wish them the best. I hope that they're they find happiness
I hope that they get over any of any of their problems, but I'm just gonna remove myself from their presence
So I don't have to
Give the collateral damage of their of their anger or their problem. Oh, there's the
Punching back to their issues
Okay, so guys so so someone is re-streaming my content and monetizing my content on another channel
I don't think they first of all are doing that, but I can take them that channel. I mean right now
I'm not re-streaming nothing. So I don't know. I know I know it's not you
Yo, I'll put yo in the chat and see how many yo's pop up
Just like it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no one's reshoring
They're saying someone saying they're taking my content and just posting on their page and they're monetized channel
I don't believe that I don't see believe they can be a monetized channel just doing my content
But if they are anyway, we'll bring more viewers, but it's still should get paid for my content
I mean, I mean my my channel is monetized informant and so that I don't think someone's allowed to like monetize my
That's why they're trying to do it. I
Get in the game with the page is that by the page drop the link come on the panel drop the link
Let us check it out. Let us expose it. Let's see what it is. Come on
If you're gonna if you're gonna snitch
So like psyche when good times comes up, man, he's gonna sound like this and I mean it like just deal with him
He'll be okay
Like he's really low yeah, it might be just yeah informant it's on format. Like, you know, I don't know who you are
You're not mod you're not a member. It's the first time seeing you in the chat
You know
I wish them the best I hope they hope they're making makes a lot of money from Richard my my content
From spiky's Awakens Terrors you heard
I
Really like you man, but like this place is kind of blacker
Like as the dates are
Yeah, I'd say that anyway
No, I
Kicked them off. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah
But what are you even saying the interesting you're just being ridiculous, please
Stop you can go talk in the chat
They prefer I guess I accept your panel for what it is psyche. I'll just give you advice
But like I always will tell you you take it or you leave it. That's it. I'm not telling you nothing
What to do and also guys, I think races. I think racism is really like I guess a really stupid ignorant thing
Like and so yeah, right. Yeah, I know some people make I know some people think it's funny think the
Racist jokes and it's like, you know, maybe we've all
How to laugh at something it's like that, but
Basically, it's not really funny anymore. Okay informant is cool. If anyone restrains your platform boots or okay
It's boot. I don't know but like what they're restraining my platform. It's like I mean, they're not allowed to do that because
They're just restreaming my whole shows without three comments here
It is my content
My boy bowie he restreams everybody shit. He don't get in trouble and people try to take down his channel copyrights and all that
They just can't get him because it's it's fair use. Yeah
It's like I say I can like if that was true that anybody could do that to anybody's channel and you know
But that they do have something called no copyright. So
Sometimes that system is no it's not through the best system and but uh
Sometimes it does protect the correct person. I don't know. I don't know. What are they making millions of dollars for my content?
I don't know
They owe me a commission
okay, so
Okay, yeah Ziggy like what like what are you talking like I see you back there like what like what what?
You're coming on being racist it's saying outrageous things about
My show and you're putting down my show to you. Oh, my show's getting blacker. What does that mean?
What does that mean I?
Started in the black sector by the way. I started on panels in the black sector
That's what he means
It's like he's a wicked terrorist. It goes the way psyche wants in that shit
Like he was drama he gets drama like he wants to do fucking terrible
He do stuff if you want to show this cattle day, whatever the fuck you want to do it goes psyche's way if y'all don't like it
You're gonna form it so inform it you're not being very helpful
You're saying there's a channel that exists distribution my content is it's a monetized channel
You're not giving me, oh, well, the channel's name is this.
If I could say, can I check out the channel, they can verify.
No, if you saw it, you'd see the name of the channel.
You just randomly came across a channel.
And randomly, that was the same as my channel.
Oh, here, I'll take a quick coincidence.
I'll tell them about it.
And I just met you.
I don't know.
It seems like a little bit, as they say, sus.
Oh, I look I really I mean, I'm very interesting
And I'm not gonna get mad about people like she my content, you know
really, you know
Really cuz I don't think it will hurt my shirt. Basically. It's just my my logo on the screen
I have I sometimes have my banner on so they'll be just advertising my reading like cash up and my show
So what I care. No, let's go if I put it in
There's a thousand choices coming in or a thousand supporters. You're still gonna grow
Okay, guys, there's a mod Jamie
I don't know if Jamie can do it. Okay. There's a mod
That sees the channel name can someone just Google that channel and just have a look at it and before back
I don't have time to do it, but if you only if you want it or otherwise, it's only worry about it. It's not a big deal
I'm not gonna take take them the quarter over it. It's like what it's freaking. It's my my little youtube show. I know
It just seems like the only I don't know it's like it's either like a big compliment
Oh, yeah, there's a channel that loves your content, which one it's the guy in form and said he posted the name
I'm not sure exactly
Yeah, if they like my content or is it they oh, I'm just gonna try and so I'm gonna make a lot of money from just using
As content or just try to annoy me, right? I got I say I allow for restricting my content
I'm not gonna ever compromise strike anybody over it. But if you're just trying to annoy me, it's not gonna work
All right, she was on my panel. Why did you come up? Why did you come up here?
Where did these weirdos keep coming?
Come up a fast we put up a banner and then you tell us where you found that out
Well, I'm sorry. I'm sorry if you don't like like that, you know, I have there's different people on the panel all the time
You know that you're you're not gonna like everybody. I'm sorry. It's boring to you
There are other people streaming their other other channels you can go to if it's not your cup of tea, okay?
Okay, so so now he's talking to Scott, so what is Scott saying then?
Scott I don't see anything he's talking to somebody if Scott I don't see a Scott
So it must be like somebody like somebody's real name. So
Yeah, it's all been talked about. Oh, go tell him this. It's fine. Yeah, I wasn't paying attention. I'll foes
I gotta go. Okay. We've got a little bit later. Yeah, let me charge. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye
Okay, anyway
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Thank you this one. I just want to
I can't read I already put the channel
Sorry, I'll answer. Okay, whatever. No, no, no, no, so bad
Not really, okay, but thank you for letting me know I'm sure with that is the goodness of your heart. Okay
It's better before Marvin. I don't know Marvin is Marvin
Okay, okay, Ziggy well this is the
Just revealing yourself to be not serious and not I don't know it's not funny. It's like it's ridiculous
That's why you're not a mod see see I was I just knew I think that's a month this guy
I don't believe being a donation
Donation with donation
So yeah, this this guy is just fucking you know this guy did not donate shit
Yeah, right booty bandit
Yeah, so the trolls are coming out now. It's the very serious, but they overtake
Well
Biggie
Oh, they're over. You know, we're tall. That's very statistical
Well, who's this?
Tommy, can I see you on camera just for a second prove it to you? Oh
I won't be on camera
Know it. I don't know who you are. So you're gonna be remaining backstage until I see you or I talk to you
Cocoa loco
He's not there
Hold on. Let me see. I can't see you
But I did not Tommy. I don't know who this it looks like the same person that came in
There's been a weird voice last night. I
Just don't know who you are
Me look me look
Is that Tommy I think it's simple. It's one second
Tommy
Hello
Don't hear you you are on show. Hello
He's not talking I don't think it must be like a fake. I don't know for a bizarre
Okay
Tommy James you're a mod. I don't know if it's Tommy James, but if you're you're a mod you post in the chat through it
Um, no, it's not it's not starting again because I'm not gonna let it I'm not gonna let it today
I could listen to more the crowd and the people who are actually respectful with them. Well, I don't even know you each so
What do I care what you think?
Bye Ziggy
I ninja
I'm serious well because it's like when you're getting stuff like oh well I want my donation back and it's like well you never made a donation so
and I want to you know
I'm not I don't people think that I'm just taking donation like not giving them back so that's kind of like I need to
Mark on it. So sorry if it's not that serious for you, but
I want to make sure that
people know that I'm on the up enough and not
Doing all this garbage people accused me of
Just we know who I really listen to you because there's so much chat
It's probably about 20,000 messages on chat a day on my show here. Looks like doc from the future, right?
Okay, yeah still anyway. Oh my gosh niggas are getting naked. Hold on
Don't put on your shirt. Oh
There's underwear guys
You know it's like I talked to people kind of like they talk to me sometimes and so that's why I like to keep it friendly and stuff
And then when people are going off on me, I start, you know, I guess, but some people will try to trigger that other side of you to come out just to like get you out of your, your piece and stuff like that.
So trying to be less reactive, but, you know, it's kind of like, kind of like, you know, I look at this show like my baby or something like that.
And so if someone messes with someone's baby, they're going to react, you know.
That's how it goes. It's not it's like even if they've they've got burn for the straw pretending they're gonna
No, it's not funny. They get the fuck oh
You lunatic get away from me
No, mr. Big Piper's band. He did the n-bomb
Who they're banned who because of the crowd everybody that a band last night banned on my own no one's people
Ever the crowd says oh don't ban this person don't ban them bring them back bring them back. That's what the crowd says eat
You don't you don't know you don't know shit. You're talking about though
Big five big five's all mr. Big five started he I didn't even do anything mr.
Big five started saying the n-word and then I ended the show
I I didn't I told you I banned him today. I ended the show before I did anything. So you're wrong
Didn't see shit
Too much drivel and unfunny trolls and chat with the clean up place. Yeah
I mean mods. I mean it's like people it's only starts annoying me enough. I'll kick him out, but
Yeah
Yeah, he really does he does RG
Is that your mods? Oh, yeah. See, yes, you're one of those people that are just like, you know, why do I care what you think?
You're not a mod. You're not a, you know, if you were a mod, maybe I'd say, oh, well, that means I trust in the guy enough to mod him.
I think he says this seriously. Your name is Yeet. You have some kind of weird
picture as an avatar photo. I just don't care.
I am responding to you, but I'm gonna stop responding to some people, okay? I'm just gonna start ignoring.
I'm just like giving you fuel for your narcissistic insanity. I
Know you are booty. I have no problem with you. You know, you're playing chat. It's like
People people know like just don't tell me I just hear the same shit every day. Oh, you're boss. This your mod that okay
I have a lot of this it's like
Let's forget about the money like I'll let you all worry about money. I'll come to you if I need a mug
I'll say hey, you're really good in chat. You do mind like, you know, give me some backup. They're supposed to be back up
They're not supposed to be attacking my channel, you know
Let's see
Yeah, so this person right here, so obviously this is like somebody
That's not they're new to the chat, but obviously they're not new obviously they've been in the chat
They know they know me and so it's like
Probably somebody banned from the chat if they're just gonna say this shit and so let's continue to ban them
You know, I hope you have a hundred accounts
You can keep coming in on because I'll eventually get them all I'm not gonna put up with bullshit anymore
Not your show go go run your own show go run your own show and run it like you want to okay?
Go run your own show don't tell me about my show. I don't know you okay?
It's like it's like people tell other people how they should raise their kids, right? It's like oh you should
They're not even mothers, you know, how do you well? How do you know so much about you know raising raising people right?
It's like they don't they're just like
Poking their nose where doesn't belong so let's see
So, oh, yeah, I'm so weak. Okay, so there we go. So that okay, I know who I was. Bye
And guys
Maybe it's not like you're saying random things. So I there's they say things that they say to me before I know who it is
There's like little little little tells
It's duper so late. I think I'm fooled by them to be fair though
Sometimes that he will have to make his own decisions. He has like 30 people in town telling was yeah
And it's like I'm in and I don't like to be told what to do
Don't tell me what to do you want to run your own show run your own show. I'm the I'm the producer director
main main writer
So the booker on the show the idea I have to do everything myself. It's like a lot of stuff trying to have a good show
I'm not gonna if I'm not I'm sorry if I don't not pleasing you, but I'm not sorry because I don't even know who you are
By eat you're gone. I
Will I will fucking deal with the troll army. I know how to take out trolls. Okay, I know how to
Your trolls don't last long here. I've been through I've been through you think this is the first troll attack
I've been through trolls since I had the channel and it was the worst trolling they have on YouTube the worst harassment, right?
Thank you, ninja. So do you think that you're bothering me by short? I think I know how to deal with this. It's just like wow
She's like, oh here's another wave of
visa
It's just the pre for the pre-pathetic again, they have to more sorry for them than I am angry. Okay. Thank you, ninja
I'll write your name in my book
ninja
with a
Pencil
Okay, and then there's a pencil all right Armin Muse Armin's here all the time
Okay, I've already banned eat so I don't need to write his name
Thing that is there, okay
Jamie's cowboys all the bridge okay, we're all good. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I tried to try to make a great channel
So what's up with everybody you in books
Yeah, I think I want to shout out to my members to think that is the member
Being more
I think that is holding it down for the representing the members. Thank you for being a member
Appreciate it
Yeah, I mean is that yeah, I don't I don't I think the racism thing he's doing is just like
It's full. I mean, it's like I don't think he even believes that unless he's like really
It's just a troll and it's kind of lame my opinion Ziggy no shade
Black Archie who's still here and I'm people in the chat
Yeah
It's true color. Yeah, what do you mean?
People yeah, people do show their true colors though. I mean, that's why
That's why I keep people around like sometimes I keep people around
For a while, even if other people don't like them
I'm like well if they're a bad person that they'll reveal themselves and I'm just gonna wait for that and so I'm not just saying
Oh, I just heard things about them and make a judgment. I need to see it for myself sometimes
I see a true cast to be a law firm.
Okay.
What do we do guys?
What do we do?
Where do we go from it?
Where do we go from here?
I don't know. It's like it's a little bit quiet. Okay, let me see.
I'm gonna pour it on you.
You fucking slut. You're a whore.
Oh, no, come on.
You're a skank. You're a slut.
You didn't let Tommy on because you thought he was gonna pour it on you.
Okay
Are you pussy, but you let Alex on and he's gonna like spread your cheeks and different fucking divisions
I banned Alice. Where have you been?
Not where you been
Remember when Tracy gave you money and she told you to get rid of them, but then you gave it back. Wow, you're a bad business man
What we're giving you a full refund
You've been Alex
What's wrong with you? Are you okay? I don't know. You seem like a you've gone insane and also I've been I've also talked to a few
I'm a great one, but let me just tell you this because it seems like you know beat is kind of I
Don't know. I love beta. I don't know what's happened to her, but I'll just say that I've gotten some disturbing emails from people that
We're friends with B to myself and it's like I
Don't I don't know what I don't know what's happening, but there's something going on where I
Don't know I don't know
I've never seen her act like I mean, you know, she's had a moment, but just said people like that
Do you see that guys you see what I just saw yeah, but I would say
Yeah, but what is it like my I don't know if I'm getting worried because it's like you are you okay like
Hope you're okay
I don't know what's going on with people, right?
Yeah, I think that it should be that.
I don't know.
Well, whatever it is,
she obviously doesn't like me anymore, so.
I'll leave it at that.
That's yeah, that's like probably the one of the hardest parts of the show though
Yeah, it was not Nancy. That was one of the hardest parts of the show as far as on the heart
Oh, you know being on YouTube is like, you know, I make these these friends. I
Know she should understand, you know, how I feel but anyway
Yeah, I don't know what to say it's just no it's sad. Yeah the saddest thing the hardest thing is like, you know having people
I really care about like
Ha, I guess I guess I can I wish I could show people how much I really love them
I guess because I don't know they must think I don't like them or something or
But so when you will you and ban the
Okay, oh
He's he's the storm I don't need a storm I don't need a storm
I mean, I like to have some smooth sailing.
I'd like to have like a little, it's like,
I don't wanna, it's too exhausting in life
to just be in a constant fight,
a constant state of disarray, right?
I wanna, I just wanna go for a positive.
And so, I know, Bita, I wish you the best.
You know, you're probably not gonna come back on the show.
I don't know what happened,
but I wish you the best.
And I never did anything to you.
So, that's my story, I'm sticking to it.
Have a good life
Yeah, but it's like the friendship ship dynamic it's a hard one the only shit that it's like I
Just don't know why you know
But that's I mean that's really sad that's all stuff that's all she can say remember you did this remember this number six months ago
And this happened this happened and it's all twisted it's all
That's she thinks she thinks it bothers me. It doesn't mean it's like
I'm I'm as concerned for her like it seems like
Something else is going on. I don't know
I don't talk about her anymore
Uh, nearly separate time was from dinner. Don't say tacos. Yeah, I'm heading up tacos
Yeah, oh
You want to lick Alex's butt? Yeah, like no, I ban Alex you ban Alex
So you can't keep them around BAM, but it's gonna be the same. Just whatever it is, I'll get a pitch shot, right?
You had heating issues in the beginning, but that's to be expected.
Yeah, no growing pains, right? So
Yeah
But it's just like, you know
I feel like I'm a very misunderstood person like people think I'm like
Like you see how the people try to pay me. They're like, oh, we're there this you're that you're this you're that like like I'm like
I show you like myself. I'm
I'm for actually everything I see the good the bad so you told embarrassing thing that's hold like the criminal history
I told my drug history. I've told every embarrassing thing that happened shared stories about
Have been I've been a you know bullied
Yeah
So
You know
This is this is nothing this is nothing new this kind of stuff, but
I dance. Well, I would like to have friends. I would like to have fans that are friends, you know.
I'd like to be some friends and fans, but in case I don't have any friends though.
Yeah, Rudy. Rudy, I'm like, Rudy, I'm like...
I'm literally like, my hair is turning gray, I'm stressed, I'm like, I get all these different
people with their different relationships saying, oh, they want me to kick aside and
you know, my heart, I feel for people, but I'm like, you know, got to take care of yourself.
I'm still learning how to deal, I told you guys, I'm not the best social person, I've
never been very popular.
Then people come to my show because I was never popular and I probably like and maybe I'm popular because people just hate me or something
but that
you know I
I'll feel good about me doing this show like I really don't want to have regrets and so that's why it's like I have to be careful with
to get the guest behavior or how you know whoever on the show because
Anything happens to the show and to be my fault not not
Somebody like I'm trying to do it to me like I want I want to be a victim. I want to
So I'm learning I'm learning. Yeah, I want friends and
but
someone is someone is your friend and you're
Your true friends that kind of stuff that has happened that wouldn't happen
Like I wouldn't do that to a friend. I wouldn't even I wouldn't do that to an enemy. I would not I would not
And what happened the other night,
we're just being so personal with, yeah.
I don't know.
And then it's like, you know, and I don't wanna,
you know, people will sometimes,
like they don't like me, they do like Bita,
then she'll say like, yeah, yeah, tell them, you tell them.
They'll believe everything she says about it.
And so it's like, so, you know,
I have to get used to like, you know,
some people will just have the wrong idea of you, right?
If you love yourself you love yourself you love yourself and all of the everyone loved themselves, right?
Then no matter what no matter what anything else if you love yourself
And don't believe the things they tell you to believe about yourself
Just just love yourself trust yourself. You got yourself if I have only one friend in the world as long as I'm my own friends
I can be happy
As long as I have an e-calming or e-hermity panel, how long will what last?
E-calming it. What does that mean?
Well, it lasts as long as it does, you know
Sometimes things have life span sometimes it lasts forever. Sometimes maybe I'll get sick of it and just
Quit right there's a million things that can happen
Um, my mom said love myself goes hair and palms. Oh, well, you know, it's basically, you know, there's loving yourself
You know, you really you really love yourself. Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's good to find yourself attractive, but I believe you know
it's self-love there's anything wrong with some self-love, but I
That's a date. Oh, yeah, so it's people are trying to date here
But you know no one's it no one's in the mood to date like the women here are like
They're usually not interested in the guys and think a lot of the guys are just creeps
that come on the, Mr. Bigpipes running after poor Paige, you know. Paige is going through something
it's not ready to be accorded like Juliet and Romeo. I mean, give her some, give her some space.
I don't, I don't think I would date somebody from my show or my cat. I think that would be
weird.
Think I think I'll leave my you know, I
Have to have to have to have like a little
But harmony with virtual harmony and virtual calming was what I meant
What do you mean by that? Hey, if you think it's just harmony and calming
There's guys there's very popular channels, but it's like this like you know
It's singing bowls and you know meditation and pretty music, you know, it's like it depends if you're coming here wanting
expecting a certain kind of show
You're gonna be disappointed because you don't know what this show is gonna be today. The show is always changing
It's always gonna be different. It's always gonna be there's different guests. There's different
decks different topics. There's
Everything everything's different. And so there's gonna be drama. Sometimes sometimes it'll be kumbaya. Sometimes it will be, you know
you know, because let's hold hands and and
Think about rainbows. Okay, we're drinking at the beach. Okay, I argue if I was but this definitely don't come here to do so
I know it's like not like
Basically, it's like people were like, oh, let's turn this into a drunk. That's it. Well, did you ask me?
but you know, but it's like and well
Like I'm enjoy a draw panel in some ways and so I've kind of let it happen. Yes, but it's that
The show's gonna turn me what I want it to be. Okay
You guys are all involved because I can't contribute
ideas and different things, but it's at the end of the day, it's my show at the end of the day
Yeah, all I asked is that if you know if you like it go ahead and hit the like button and subscribe and share it maybe
I'm not like I'm not like the I'm not like a personal like
Little puppet for the audience like just like bend around and like
Put put lipstick on and makeup and then like a doll and throw in the corner and then just like
Take over no, I'm not I'm not about that. I'm about I'm gonna stand my ground. Okay
Does it it doesn't belong to anybody else it basically, you know YouTube maybe owns it right and so
Yeah, that's your YouTube. Don't tell me that you run my channel
Not dedicated to music because I mean I might have on my other channel I might do karaoke
and stuff or I might set up a TTS system on the other channel that will play songs because
We'll be able to get away with that
But for this channel, I'm just gonna try to keep it clean as I can
And we're cleaning it up, but I knew I knew what was gonna happen
I was like, okay. Well, if I'm gonna clean it up. I need to like get all the rats to come out of their holes
so I
Had a little bit of a revelation that was ready for
So I got some book
So what's going on? Are you guys getting along in chat?
Okay, well, I mean cb is not even banned so she doesn't really need to
Come under alter obey. Oh, yeah, so I mean
Whatever guys have as many avatar have as many characters and personalities, you know if you get blocked in the chat
Just come under another one, but maybe like
We think of a different character. Maybe one that's like less
Just revolting so you don't get blocked again
That's just balding
That's like remember like big Nisha. Isn't she was like I know for weeks
You know, you got we had fun chats coming out done now the BKG the tattoo
he got the tears terracotta mall and
You know she got kidnapped and she farted and the fire kidnap woke up and she
And then it turns out it was just, it was just, you know, this Mexican guy named, uh,
Rogue Nomad that did it.
So.
Yeah, but it's okay. I, you know, I enjoy it. I said she's still welcome. I'd rather
Unfortunately, it's like, you know
It's like the difference between Santa Claus and the fat guy that gets higher Christmas to play in the mall
It's hulking on your own all in chat philosophy hours. I'm a blast. Well, great, you know
But why like why are you that you find that that your form of amusement? Just
It's kind of like
weird
Do you you do you?
Well, I mean, I was not as bad, but why is, like, um,
DB, Spall, Nikki, Vicky, I mean, at least, I don't understand anything anyone's saying,
it's just kind of a distraction right now. I don't know. Mods, can you use your judgment?
I've started to just say, go, to get too annoying. Go ahead and time them out for 24 hours,
and I can deal with them later. I don't know. Let's see if there's, if people don't make sense
Go on discord and like one private message or something seems like it's like people talking during the
During the show of it their own shit. Mmm. I don't know
Start it. I don't know. Maybe I'll do hold on
Nothing bad, okay, let me just do something
Okay, yeah, I got
That work
Yeah, but it's like I mean it's like
Sure it is but you know I have to deal with this another way can't just tell people that they're not gonna
They're not focusing on the tarot on cats
And the terror doesn't feel like coming out
while it's like this.
The terror is like, no.
So if those people are just harmless people,
they're probably subscribers, right?
Oh, where'd they all go?
Yeah, well, JT's not allowed in the chat.
If you see him, you can go ahead and block him.
Yeah, I'll just get annoyed and start blocking most people.
You know, I think that is Hannah...
Maybe Booty Band is cool. I'm not sure they might be a troll.
Definitely Nicky Vicky, you're all very sus.
Well mods you'll know more than I do about who they really are and stuff
I'm like, let me know you already know me second you met at the gay club last week. I grabbed. Oh my god. Sure you did
Oh
Gone to a gay club in a long time
Watch my hands. I'll do the hoodo hoodo reading
But guys the warning in this reading will like knock out a lot of negative energy
So if you're here under bad pretenses or anything you might just want to leave now, okay?
I actually have a better idea
Okay, whoever dwells in the shelter of the most high will rest in the shadows of the Almighty I will say to the Lord
He is my refuge and my fortress, my God, in whom I trust.
Surely He will save you from the fowler's stare.
And from the deadly pestilence, he will cover you with his feathers, and under his wings
you will find refuge.
His faithfulness will be your shield and a rampart.
You will not fear the tear of night, nor the arrow that flies by day, nor the pestilence
that stalks in the darkness, nor the plague that destroys at midday.
A thousand may fall at your side, ten thousand at your right hand, but it will not come near
you.
Yet, you will only observe with your eyes, and see the punishment of the wicked.
If you say, Lord is my refuge, and you make the most high your dwelling, no harm will
overtake you.
No disaster will come near your tent, for if you will command his angels concerning you
to guard you in all your ways, and they will lift you up in their hands, so that you will
not strike your foot against the stone.
You will tread on the lion in the cobra.
Because he loves me, says the Lord, I will rescue him. I will protect him for he acknowledges my name.
He will call on me and I will answer him. I will be with him in trouble.
I will deliver him and honor him with long life. I will satisfy him and show him my salvation.
Psalm 91
I'm also gonna probably get a spiritual bath today.
Which is just some coffee, a lemon, salt.
There's like a lot of, I saw like a lot of gunk, astral gunk.
They look like spiderwebs.
Wow.
And look, it cleared out, it cleared out the right people though.
Not even Sunday?
Yeah.
Hey, Tracy. Yeah, Psalms is nice
Yeah, I don't know if you saw Tracy, but beta just came in here
Tracy is really weird like Alice attacked me last night. I had to ban him
Beta came in started attacking me today guys. Did you resist an attack?
I didn't I would didn't say anything to where she started attacking me, right?
No reason
She didn't bring up your name though, Tracey. She brought up the whole thing.
I don't know. I don't know if you saw that though.
Good to see you, Tracey. Love you.
I do love Psalms in the Bible. They're very magical.
scriptures, but I do want to say one more, not Psalm, but it would be like a
scriptures. Okay, it says Corinthians, it says Corinthians 10, 3, 2, 5. It says, oh it
says two Corinthians, 10, 3, 3, 5. Okay, it says, for we walk in the flesh,
For though we walk in the flesh, we are not waging war according to the flesh, for the weapons of our warfare are not of the flesh
but have divine power to destroy strongholds.
We destroy arguments and
lop the opinion raised against the knowledge of God and take every thought captive to obey Christ.
He who dwells in the shelter of the Most High will abide in the shadow of the Almighty.
I will say,
to the Lord, my refuge." Oh, that's the same Psalm I just wrote, okay.
And, my God, to my trust, okay.
Behold, I've been given, I've given you the authority to tread on serpents and scorpions
and over all the power of the enemy, nothing shall hurt you.
Deuteronomy 28-7, the Lord will cause your enemies who rise against you to be defeated before you
They shall come out against you one way and flee before you seven ways
And then it says
Put on the whole armor of God that you may be able to stand against the schemes of the devil
But we do not wrestle against flesh and blood
But rather against the rulers against the authorities against the cosmic powers over this present darkness
Against the spiritual forces of evil in the heavenly places
for the Lord God is a Son and a shield.
The Lord bestows favor and honor.
No good thing does He withhold from those
who walk uprightly.
How about this, since therefore the children share flesh and blood, he himself likewise
partook of the same things, that though death, he might destroy the one who has the power of death,
that is the devil. So that says the devil has the power of death. That's scary, huh?
How about this Psalm 118 they surrounded me like bees they went off in like a fire among thorns in the name of the Lord
I cut them off. I was pushed hard so that I was falling but the Lord helped me
How's that
Then Psalm 23,
Finally, a Psalm of David, the Lord is my shepherd. I shall not want. He makes me lie down in green pastures.
He leads me beside still waters. He restores my soul. He leads me in the past of righteousness.
For his name's sake, even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil, for you are with me, your rod and your staff, they comfort me, you prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies, you anoint my head with oil, my cup overflows."
I'll keep I'll keep saying the prayers you like that one. You love that one. Yep
I'll keep reading the prayers it looks like it's working even if even if it exercises most of the room I
Think it's exercising the right people
Footsteps for a while, look it up, hold on.
Footprints of footsteps, yeah.
He says, if you're talking about footprints in the sand,
one night I dreamed I was walking along the beach
with the Lord, scenes from my life flashed across the sky.
In each, I noticed footprints in the sand.
Sometimes there were two sets of footprints,
other times there was only one.
During the low periods of my life,
I could see only one set of footprints.
So I said, you promised me Lord,
that you would walk with me always.
Why, when I have needed you most,
have you not been there for me?
The Lord replied, the times when you have seen only one set of footprints, my child, is when I carried you."
Got the chills.
You do booty?
Well, they've been working, okay?
Just let it burn, let it burn.
It's burning away all that evil.
Which, you know, there can be attachments.
Long life we pick up we can pick up a lot of love gunk
Hey bottom man
So I did there is a really good prayer that I did find
And I read it and it was powerful and I think it needs to be read again. Well, not that's not the song
But it covers pretty much every thing
I read it once really recently. It was really good. Okay. Okay. It's a little, it's not
too long. It's not too long. Okay. It's just, yeah, just, just, just settled in guys. Let's
listen to this one. You'll like this.
As your servant, O God, I confess my continued allegiance and surrender myself completely
in every area of my life.
I cover myself and my family with the blood of Jesus for our protection, and I take a
stand against all the workings of Satan and his demons that would hinder me or any family
member.
I place upon myself, with thanksgiving, the armor you have prepared, the girdle of truth,
the breastplate of righteousness, the sandals of peace, the shield of faith, and the helmet
of salvation. And I take up the sword of the Spirit. By faith and dependence upon you, I put
off all fleshly works from the same width from the old men and stand in the victory of the cross,
where Jesus provided cleansing from the old man, and it's provided a way for me to live above sin.
Heavenly Father, I give you thanks that I am seated in the heavenlies and I
recognize by faith that all wicked demonic spirits and Satan himself are
under my feet and are subject to me in the name of Jesus. Thank You Lord.
Father, I thank you for the weapons of our warfare, are not carnal but mighty through
God for pulling down strongholds, for casting down imaginations, and every high thing that
exalts itself against the knowledge of God, and to bring every thought into obedience
to the Lord Jesus Christ.
Therefore, in my life today, I will tear down the strongholds of Satan and smash his plans
that have been formed against me, tearing down the strongholds of Satan against my mind,
and I surrender my mind to the Holy Spirit.
I affirm that my Heavenly Father did not give me a spirit of fear, but a spirit of power,
of love, and of a sound mind.
So I break and smash the strongholds of Satan formed against my emotions today.
I give my emotions to you.
Strongholds of Satan formed against my will today.
Lord, I give my will to you and choose to make the right decisions of faith and obedience.
Therefore, I smash the strongholds of Satan formed against my body and declare that no
diseases, no germ, bacteria, virus, or illness of any kind can live on or in this body.
I give my body to you, Father, recognizing that I am your temple and I rejoice in your
mercy and goodness.
I decree and declare.
All works of the enemy that are contrary to or would hinder the fulfillment of God's plan and purpose in my life are broken.
I am liberated from all generational, spoken or satanic curses.
I sever them by the sword, word of God, the spirit and the blood.
I am free from any and all demonic influences that negatively affect me, physically, emotionally,
psychologically, spiritually, or by any other means.
The wisdom of God directs my life and cannot be twisted or perverted in any way.
Neither Satan nor his fallen angels have any right to my finances, and all the wealth of
the wicked comes to me now.
I command Satan to cop it up, spit it out, and let it go.
Satan cannot cause confusion nor interfere with my hearing of the voice of God regarding
I will stand in victory against all attacks of the enemy that will destroy all attempts to deceive me,
to ambush me, or to interfere with my assigned ministry. Through prayer, worship, and obedience
to God, I will continue to defeat Satan and his unclean spirits."
Hi, Joker.
You like the prayer?
Hail to the Awakens. Hail him.
Thank you.
Hail to the Awakens.
Can I join your okay? Yeah
Destroy my hold my hand and I was gonna finish up the prayer real quick. Do we get to eat people?
We need to eat Jesus. Okay. So says in the name of Jesus I repent of bind up, rebuke, cast out, nullify and forbid off myself, my wife, my family, my friends, my church, and my community, the following demonic spirits.
Spirits of poverty, religious and fricical spirits, mindsets of lack, worry and fear, spirits of witchcraft and control, selfishness, spirits of lust and sexual immorality, pride, fear and timidity, self-righteousness, spirits of apathy and lukewarmness.
negative thoughts and ideas, rebellion, depression, compromise with the world, intimidation, discouragement,
accusation, self-gratification, spirits of death and unaliving, and all spirits associated
with a mental, emotional, or physical illness. I pull down every generational curse,
all hexes and word curses, and call all my relationships into Godly order. I decree and
declare my life is under and in the order of God Almighty.
Father, I pray that now and through the day you would strengthen and enlighten me. Go ahead. It's the Joker's feeling it
Very good. Okay. Keep going. You can scream pulling
Showed me the way stations is hindering. He left there is hindering and tempting
And lying and distorting the truth in my life enable me to be aggressive mentally, to think about and practice your word and give you your rightful place in my life.
I pray that the Holy Spirit would bring down all the works of the crucifixion, all the work of the resurrection, all the work of the glorification, and all the works of Pentecost into my life today.
In Jesus' name, that this life that you have given me is yours completely.
My God is Jehovah and He is the God who saves, heals and delivers.
Therefore, I refuse to be discouraged and to worry or speak negatively.
You are the God of hope.
Teach me to speak blessings and not curses.
You have power.
You have proven your power by resurrecting Jesus from the dead.
So I claim in every way this power and victory over all the satanic forces in my life.
I pray this prayer in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ with thanksgiving.
I seal this prayer by the blood of the Lamb.
There you go.
You're back Joker in back. I don't know if he left but
Looked like oh my gosh. I mean Joker disappeared without me. Well
Pyrrhus the other me see Pyrrhus Pyrrhus, I don't know. I don't know. It was not a not my favorite character
Some people need to work on their on their on their characters. Okay, so it's a character. I mean, it's like you're gonna be a demon like fucking
Yeah
The best demon you can it'll be like some kind of lame
No
Third circle hell demon. I'm gonna be
Yeah, Joker Joker exploded, okay. Oh by Joker, I mean Joker being cheese. I was like a two-minute poem cheese
See the guys see people to start to this like when you do these things
Things will start to happen like you know be like oh why this person is the pure why this person suddenly blow up on me
What's that happened? It's called it's a revelation. It's like the truth is being shown. Okay?
Go with me go with me
Just watch just watch
Yeah
Like you know, I was like I can tell you a story that I when I was you know
I was always into the occult, you know, right? I was into like that come on in more new age
But I was kind of into like the more a little more witchier aspects and I find I still find some of a very appealing, right?
But okay, so when I was probably 10 years old, I got I went and bought this satanic Bible from a store and they made the source
Oh my god, why are you buying this?
Hard core. I was like, I want to read it. I read it and I read it many times
I thought you know and in fact, I even joined the Church of Satan at almost 18 years old and
You feel like a hundred question question there. I think the CIA picks out the questions
I think it's basically like a psychological operation to collect information, but
Yeah, so I did that, but then, you know, I kind of grew out of it. I kind of like I did find
find Satanism to be
kind of anti-human, anti-human,
because, you know, some of these demons are anti-human because humans have power over them.
So,
We have control over them. They don't want us to know that they do want us to think that they have control over us
But that's why on the devil card. They're not even chained tightly around the next little it's all voluntary
We voluntarily chain ourselves to these lower these lower things
Sometimes it's like, you know tying a balloon to something. You know, so it's you know, it stays on the earth
and we don't want to just float away like an angel, but
You're a dianetics at 8 at 18. Yeah, I read dianetics, too. I read it when I was probably 13 or 14
It also, I just remember reading it, and then it came to a place where it's like, oh, and
Dianetics cures homosexuality, and then I was like, oh, that's bullshit.
It's causing little prisons on the wall.
Oh, this is, I have like a little hanging crystal, and so it creates these orbs.
Yeah, it's like a little, I think it's a crystal or glass, and the sun shines through, it makes
these beautiful rainbows everywhere.
So even guys and even if you are like some trolls in here and everything and whoever is remaining like obviously, you know
You didn't flee when you heard a prayer. And so, you know, obviously
There's something, you know, I
Would say some kind of morality or some kind of something doesn't mind prayers, you know
People that just hate prayers even because those prayers that are like kind of kind of
There's prayers that are kind of hardcore and stuff like that
The Bible, but people that do not like prayer at all. Like why would you afraid you're afraid to talk to God?
Yeah, it's a dianetics that's the other on her bird field the dianetics Scientology
Even going back to Mormonism they go all these
new religions basically are basically
Created by Mason's who are they're basically taught to create a religion and then they branch out and they start their own, right?
It became a little test to see if you could finish it.
Yeah, it's a little bit, I find everyone at Hubbard
just very dry and confusing.
And it's like, yeah, it does tell you in Dianetics,
he says, you have to go to the glossary
for every word you don't understand.
But then he made up a billion of words
and they're just complicated kind of words.
So you have to sit there going constantly back and forth
trying to understand everything exactly.
And that kind of programs you to take it seriously.
And it's always like a whole brainwashing process
of trying, getting you to read the book
and take it seriously.
I just, there's stuff about some of these organizations, I kind of find cultish, cultish.
And so, I'm kind of, I'm not very, a cult as a joke, it's like these cults where they
basically like, people give away all the possessions and they, or they give them all to the leader
Give their wife to the co-leader to have sex. Yeah, it's a different language, huh?
like the t-tens and the e-meter and the
SP's and the
Yeah, I
Think that there might be some good. I mean I'm sure it helps some people
But it seems like if most of the help comes through the networking of the people that are there instead of like actually
Psychological stuff, but whatever works, right?
Elrond Hubbard once said, if you want to make a lot of money, start a religion.
And Scientology was the first tax-exempt, tax-exempt church.
Or I don't know if I'm going to have to first, but it did get tax-exempt status
by calling itself the church, even though it doesn't believe in a God.
Anyway, my Scientology diatribe.
There's tons of information about by X Scientologists. You can see what exactly what they do
Yeah, even like the different like religions like Tibetan Buddhism I study and
This is and so it says word Tibetan Buddhism come from well Buddhism grew out of Hinduism of the Indian Hinduism
Oh, it's especially the
to bed in Buddhism. I think even the Buddha was born in India, I think, right?
There's other stories of where he was born, but there's a, so there's a lot of
Hindu influence on Buddhism. You're not a Scientologist. Yes, he was a prolific science fiction writer in his previous life. Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Are you Hindu now?
I
Okay, are you can do my
Bendy on my forehead as a Hindu
Well, he is my god. He blessed me. He put that red thing on my forehead. He's Hindu and these are actually
You know, it means you're from they're from India. It's like, no, it's an Indian continent. Oh, no shit Sherlock
Yeah, I mean, that's what it people think. Oh, you can convert to Hinduism. The real Hindus are like actually from India
But you know, you can study Hinduism and Buddhism. I certainly did there's no tip
There's no I just wanted to read your terror cards if it's okay
I don't think I'm interested
What a softy soft skin sorrow as bitch when people are my partners on your panel
Oh, yeah, there's your shit
I don't know, you should have been here last night.
Everyone was getting called stuff in the chat.
I mean, it's like, you know, what?
I don't know, I just think, I don't know if,
I don't know what's happened.
Like you just seem like you're a little bit strange.
I just, I just, I don't know.
I don't feel like being insulted and degraded
by you right now.
So.
Thank you for that. Thank you for the offer of reading. I don't feel like mocking tarot or what I do or
Have you pick on me anymore? So, you know
But thank you I
Mean if you were gonna do a reading I would prefer, you know, you'd actually do your you know your traditional readings that you do
in your in your tradition
Then I really enjoyed and I never I never said anything, but I enjoyed your readings
You never said anything, but you enjoyed my readings, but now of course you're
Changing your tune or be to go. He's just sitting backstage. She's decided to come insult me and like make accusations and
Talk about a bunch of dumb shit, so I
Don't know
Totally I'm provoked
Thank You Doug
Thank you for the super chat
Appreciate you. Thank you, man. Good guy
Because I beat it because I know what you're talking about your cut you're saying oh you let me be called a predator
I banned this your big pipes from the show. I asked him to apologize to you last night again, you know
Who didn't you have said last night? I don't know. I mean, it's like everybody like, you know, Alex
Alex started attacking me. Joker was making fun of me. It's your big pipes and we're bombing crystal
F a gg ot we're bombing. Yeah
Okay, well, I'm glad they had those kind of stuff and I'm glad I didn't I can't even read it. It's just it's just too much
Okay, you do your thing. Okay
Because it's just I know I don't know
Even joke. Yeah, it was the guy. It was literally everybody and it's like, you know, maybe it's like a test from the universe to see how
You know, I could take it. Okay
But love to everybody like love, you know
What great beat I hope, you know, go to go to beat and be this case tarot. Okay, please
I get free tarot readings, too.
But judging on how the last one was starting out,
it doesn't sound like they're going to be the nicest tarot readings.
We might end up getting engrossed in.
Wow, she's just going nuts in chat hall.
Whereas...
Like this chocolate
Okay, there is I got you anytime I will of course you read your readings for anybody chat
Can I beat it and maybe you're very recon style. Yeah, well, she's not backstage anymore
You let me back stage before be there
Just let it look guys. Let her get it out. No, it's a crystal. It's a crystal accusing me of calling her a crack whore and of
Crystal saying I said she looked like Kim Joe's friend. It's just ridiculous. It's like it's like not even the worst worth the
whatever you want to think you live your life I'll live mine I'm not going to bother you
it's okay Doug not
it's like it's not it's not just me it's happening too
I'm not fighting totally calm
I'm very I am sensitive and it's like I don't like being called out of my name especially since I
Probably do the right thing
Hey, Jamie
Yeah, well, I know it's not I know I know I'm not the only one
How many balls that you've got which oh edge. Oh, yeah him hi J dog
Yeah, I'm just I've got to take it. It's got a
But yeah, let me be your tourniquet take your hatred out on me
Hey nice to see some friendly faces and a little bit hectic here lately
I think it's basically, you know, it's like, you know, sometimes these revelations do bring a lot of chaos. That's why, you know, revelations
That's like the apocalypse maybe in the back of the book, right? There's a lot of chaos that comes with it because when things are revealed, wow
Nothing is as it would seem to be, right?
So guys take a deep breath, you know
You say prayers say prayers, you know, the things are ramping up and not only
And this it's everywhere, you know, it's happening everywhere. There's like all this tension
It comes out of different ways people are concerned about what they hear on the news and things
I would say try to stay off the news. It's really
Trying to get people vile of emotionally trying to you know, do some more social engineering
It's touching grass, right?
545 here
Yeah, I'm touching carpet
It looks like Indiana Jones, but how does that Joe Shipply, though? He needs to wear like a Raven's hat and like a
Full Ravens gear
So let's read about some things and
manipulation. I want you guys to be aware of these tactics that people will use.
Okay, so there's something called gaslighting, right? It says
Okay, take care of yourself and your friends by getting to know the signs of relationship red flags
That's not what happened
You're overreacting you're crazy. I would never do such a thing. It was a joke. You're so forgetful everyone agrees with me
You're being paranoid
These are catchphrases of the gaslighter, someone who is deliberately using manipulative
behavior to make you think that your memory or understanding of something is wrong, and
they are right, and that you can't trust yourself and you need to rely on them instead.
Abusers gaslight so they can gain and retain control of a relationship.
Why is gaslighting a red flag? Gaslighting is a strategy that is intended to break down the trust you have in your memory
Instincts and self-esteem
It can make you doubt yourself and depend more on the objective perspectives of your partner while in reality
They are taking care of only their best interests
Let's see if it is an abusive behavior that can be a sign of more frequent and worsening abuse to come
So what does darbo mean?
So there's a thing called darbo, okay?
Darbo stands for deny, attack, reverse victim, offender.
It's a series of actions used by a perpetrator
as a defense mechanism when their unjust,
unkind behavior is questioned or called out.
It works to confuse you and your sense of reality.
So deny.
Denying your memory or perception of an event is gaslighting.
They could be denying an agreement or a conversation
or even something physical, like hitting you.
Denying doesn't always mean outright saying
something never happened.
It can also look like creating a story
to explain their actions.
In the example of denying a physical attack,
for example, they might say something like,
of course I didn't hit you on purpose.
You were about to hit me.
So I put my hands out in defense.
But in reality, you hadn't moved at all.
Attack.
After denial comes the attack that tries to break down your credibility your credibility right the abuser might go on the offensive about your motivation for questioning them your mental health you're crazy your parenting ability your intelligence anything that fuels the voice in your head that says maybe
And then it says, reverse victim offender.
Next, here comes the blame shifting.
This is when the perpetrator manages
to make you out as the one that is at fault.
They try to make you feel bad for bringing it up
in the first place or say that it was only
because of something you did first.
Okay.
So,
That's just a little you know guys. It's a whole it's a whole lot of studying you can see the movie gaslight
It's about this opera singer that's her aunt died and leaves her with a bunch of money and she goes and
Marrys this guy and the guy starts to try to drive her crazy
So she thinks money after her money
But so she won't he wants her to think that she's crazy and starts messing with the lighting
He said gas lights in the house instead of the electric lights. He mess with the lighting
Yeah, yeah, but Jamie it is important that I let people know because some people don't realize there's manipulation being used
I mean if there's always and a lot of relationships there's
There's there's there's like a
Really bad manipulation. There's also you can manipulate things for the better, but there's also like very coercive
Trying to control somebody else. It's called gas letting yes
It's like, you know, you're crazy. You're a fault. You did this. You did that. You take, you know, it's mirror campaigns. There's a lot.
It's under, if you guys study narcissistic abuse, you'll find it very prevalent there.
Also, dark triad, Machiavellianism, and
and psychopaths. That's the triad.
I know that we should always be bad. Well, no, I mean the word there's nothing wrong with a word
The word is describing something if there's no word for it, then how are people gonna like say what's going on yet?
Then they can if they can study it
You can better better protect yourself because it is a deep programming process because some people are just our mind fuckers
They're all that you're gonna do is fuck your mind like, you know
Create problems. There's some people that try to heal everybody. So it's like constant struggle people hurting and healing
If people know people know more about it, they're able to
Just know that there's there's a reason it's not just them because they think they're crazy. They're like, oh my god
What am I? It's actually some manipulation tactic. Okay?
for different reasons
There's different types of narcissists. They want different things
Some of someone that want fuel fuel can be like a tension can be like that reaction. It can be like a
Giving them your energy and stuff you're and you be in a state of
Distress that can be fuel for them. It's like the kind of schwaiden Freud liking other stuff bring it's kind of a
It's a scary thing
Because it almost when you get into it. It's very like inhuman. It doesn't see other people as even if other people don't exist
To an artist that everybody is just them
And you know, it's just part of them. They seem just everybody is themselves. So they have no empathy. It's all them
It's worse when they do get up on it. Yes, it actually has to keep some people do have sexual responses to abusing like
You know mentally abusing people to get it. They get a high permit
Okay
So, yeah, this may be it's scary, right?
Thank you
Also, you know, it is sad like a lot of the times like these behaviors are not like they'll just come out of nowhere
And I don't know even know if they're that genetic. I think it really is to do a lot with you know
people do have trauma a lot and become that way and then they
Spread it out. It comes with a virus, right?
Thank you booty bandit. Thank you booty bandit. I won't forget that I won't forget that
You know, I do appreciate, you know, and if you if you're you know, you if you don't like me
You don't have to you don't like me, you know, it's like I don't ask that you
People help me. I ask this don't hurt me. This don't hurt me. So it's okay to hurt me
And that's with everybody
You don't have to help people if you don't want to but don't just don't hurt them
So have a truck. I don't know that's not what I'm the real Joseph. This is Nick making it. He's an outfit
Um, yeah, but it's also, you know, she said like, you know, you don't want to make, um,
I would never go make a mockery of somebody's livelihood.
Right.
I don't have the, why do I have the energy to go out, bother other people?
Well, I like really, I try to focus on myself, people that love me.
I'm going to go out and harass people.
I'm going to go out and start conflict for no reason.
No.
I like peace I like I like I like chill. I you know, I like not having to be in anxiety
Or on eggshells walking on a so what do I do? What do I do next?
They will make I can't you're damned if you do damn if you don't I did this they're gonna matter
They don't this they're gonna matter. You can't there's no it's like a no win
And so that's like a double bind like no win situation
How can you ever?
How can you ever get anywhere? It's like you'll never win. There is
Also, if you want to like say, oh, well, I'll just be as evil as them
Don't do that. Don't be as evil as them because yeah, you can be smart and like have like, you know
No, they're tactics, but do not be as evil as them because that
Then they have one because they're turning you they've turned you into that like and so
Right. So don't don't be evil
Be above it like, you know
Don't let
What people do they've done to you make you want to take it out other people let it give you empathy let it let it
Show you hey look that looks like it feels bad. I don't ever want to make anyone feel like that because I know don't make me feel bad, right?
sometimes
It's it's an it's natural to feel it and sometimes you have to
experience the
Negativity yourself to understand how other people feel because sometimes you have an experience that you can't really have empathy for
right
With or without empathy, well, yeah, but Hannah, there's also like, you know, there's a dark empaths
And so the dark empaths they have the empathy they they just they just use it to manipulate so they can see oh this person's
In a emotional distressful state. That's when people
Like say around the best time to like do a Hoover is like around holidays and birthdays and stuff
That's when they come back after having you know discarded you for a long time. They'll come back on holiday
And that's when we're kind of emotionally vulnerable. They know they just know that oh, you know
Oh, this is they're gonna be like hurting this day. And so they're they're gonna want to talk to somebody
I'll be able to you know come in and charm
Yeah, they'll just they look at people like you know little little dolls to play with
Competence artist con artist. Yes
And it's like, you know, it's good thing about con artists is a lot of them are very brilliant
They're like they can be very intelligent people a psychopath. See like, you know, there's gonna be talented. They basically
Don't need to they could actually
Not unless, you know, there's circumstances where they can't do what they want to do. They can like
Basically learn the professions and fake it as good as the real people of professions. There's actually a big con artist
He was like a he got on a military ship
He like got to the thing he was in the military or something and he was like the military doctor and he would like
Actually sew up big legs and he would learn from the medical textbooks
And he would like you know treat and save lives and stuff as a doing medicine
But he had no right to practice medicine. So it's very dangerous. You want to make sure you're
You're not dealing with somebody that's
I'm trying because you know, it can have bad consequences. We all know about think the uncertified
Botox and liposuction or not liposuction
What the if it is butt fillers then and do something to use silicone like the whole depot and like the silicone
The silicone the tubes and they put it in there and people die. It's terrible. Yeah
I'm gonna go to professionals
Or at least someone that knows what they're doing.
Either you get bitter or you want better. Yeah
Yeah
Well, yeah, and it's like yeah, I don't want to be bitter and but it's like you know the world will like a little
So a lot of disappointments that you'll be I'll throw a lot of
A lot of sadness love. Oh my god. I can't believe but it's like there's also a lot of good in the world
And there's like, you know, it's basically what you can focus on and if you can't focus on the good
Just start doing good and start doing it yourself. Just like
Stephanie was talking about earlier in the chat. She's like, you know, she just wanted to help
She wanted to do good to the world. She's she's in the medical field. She's saving cats and things like that
Doing very you know, those those two combinations are very very compassionate
Things to do good in the world. Yes, that's good. Love to the world. You're not there. There's so much hate already. There's so much
conflict so many differences the key is like
Learning working through the differences forgiveness love compromise, but don't let yourself just be
You know attacked. Yeah, that's it's abusive
Oliver, I don't know she was bringing up stuff from months to two months ago stuff from a month ago. I don't know
It just doesn't like me anymore so she can like she just she's trying to burn the relationship
She doesn't have to ever talk to me good. I guess that's fine
Yeah, I mean it's a whole because I've seen people like there's people going through some hard times in the chat
Like I talk privately to a lot of people. I know that there's
difficult things sometimes people will stay share but they're going through sometimes they're not and
So people go through a lot of stuff, right? You can rewind you just rewind all over you can see was exactly what she said
Because you can hear her telling and everything
You can see what I say
Do I know?
You know it hadn't we had no conflict the first six months we usually not what we would not we were just we just know fine
then
So sort of happening like my chest are getting bigger like stuff are happening where people were like, oh, she I'm modern
That was like the first thing she started getting mad about I was like your chat is saying that I'm kicking over your show
I'm trying to I'm not hiding anybody. I was like, I know I know it's like well
I think don't worry about it and then
Then she'd be mad of this person said this and then I was thinking about this and it was just one thing after another
She's mad at me every every other day. You don't get entertained at that stuff. Well, you asked
I don't get it, it's not supposed to be entertainment,
it's supposed to be, it's just showing you,
you ask the question, why is she mad?
If you can hear all the reasons she gives,
see if it makes any sense to you.
I'm not trying to say, go let, go have a lap.
It's not funny to me.
It was hurtful.
I was not entertained, I was horrified.
Yeah.
Like they said with the gaslighting here, it's like they try to attack you in public, so they attack your integrity, and so that's why she's saying, oh, they're crap, you know.
Okay, Oliver, Oliver, it's been going on for months, it's been going on for months.
go for a couple days later, calm down, it always be like, no, and then it's, no, it's like getting
too unpredictable. It's like, oh, what, which beta is today? Which is it going to be the nice beta?
Like, but like sweet or the mean, mean beta is a, that's all I've been seeing for the past like week.
I just, I don't get it. It's like,
Not even not even nice. It's like the kind-hearted kind-hearted like no friend rather than like this like
Person that's staying on it's this evil monster. I don't know
Yeah, it's kind of dizzy
Look because it's called cognitive dissonance. It's he has a dizzy and disonance
It's D. I. S. S. O. N. A. N. C. League. It has to do with dizzy because cause
This is dissonance is when cognitive dissonance is when oh
I love this person. I think that's one side of your brain
Oh, I love this person's person perfect
And then it's like then you see the other side personality
You're like well, that's a different person that person's the most evil person in the world
And it's like in your two hemispheres fight over
Is this person God or the devil and so I always try to say well we're both we're both, you know
We're both mixtures of good and evil, but you know some people can have one of them take over
Let's have a chill night. Maybe you can talk about later. Yeah, let's see. It seemed like she was like ready. She's like trying to
They do demolition on the relationship because it's like you okay
The real beat is the sober be that I wouldn't bother getting overworked over stuff. He says when she's drunk
I don't know about you. She doesn't sound drunk to me like
As if you get me when she likes you I'm high over there, but she's drunk a million times. She was never like this
Hi corruption, yeah
But I can't say I wasn't
Like told what would happen by like a lot of people I could think there was a ocean. No, this is what happens
So I kind of not too surprised gonna see you to corruption. I
Just would hope that
No way to happen with us, but
Yeah, but I do think that the the world's kind of getting on edge. I was gonna didn't take your wrench
He doesn't have a wrench and he's not even in the check. Yeah
Yeah, that's not cool daughter of truth, that's what I'm saying. It's like I don't that's why I don't want that stuff here
No, it's like it's like, you know, I don't want my channels to turn into that. I don't I don't I don't
I need to put my hand back on the steering wheel
It's evil dormant from birth I
Think that there are people born and then they would have been evil had not they've had certain circumstances like maybe loving family and
you know
Certain things that they can serve as an outlet for their evil
He's in a productive way or there's just people that have horrible things happen to them
And then they want to go out and do horrible things, right?
Broker the friendship. Yeah. Thank you
Yeah, I might it's like I'm totally I've already see like before I started streaming
I knew about some of the stuff that goes on because I've seen it in 90 day fiancee community
And that's like just a silly TV show and it's like they do the same thing
they have private Facebook groups all the all the
Streamers like hate each other and they they don't even allow each other to stage their name on that on that on that
That kind of commentary they don't mention their commentators because it's like you do and then all of a sudden like they
Facebook groups those talks everything and harass you they involve people's children
It's because really sick and so I really don't want to go down that road at all. I just have to dip it in the bud
So came looking for that stuff anybody. Sorry. You're not gonna find it here
People try to try to force it on but no not gonna work
Do I think that people that pass away had come back to life come back with something evil in them hmm to bring back?
I
Don't I wouldn't know like a lot of people say they've had visions of an afterlife
Some people have had visions of going to hell those visions of hell have made them change their ways after or they see no visions of heaven
Maybe they just got a confirmation that there's the afterlife or some kind of
Experience I don't think they come back with something evil in them necessarily. You know, the evil is like not some kind of like
People think it's a force. I don't think it's actually in us. It's like it's a part of our
Psychology it has to do with the duality. They'll get really creative. They'll send you a gift and obtain your address ultimately your full. Yeah
Yeah, I know I know I know
Know but they got I talked to Lisa Jordana about this. I asked her about doxing
I asked her about what do you monetize? She's you know, she's a very successful streamer
She's like over 20,000 subscribers
and she gave me some really really good advice about doxing and
and
I'm running my channel you're in limbo Leah
Yeah, so
Lisa really gave me great advice. She knew exactly what I was asking and actually I went to her and asked her and she answered
Nicely would look for your nearest
Yeah, I know it's I mean, it's just it gets it gets sick
Yeah, easy camera took off for a little while
I don't know. I don't know what you're doing. It is busy
Yeah, I know daughter. I've been I've been I've been doxxed. Okay. I've been doxxed and I've seen people be doxxed and you know
You know, it can be dangerous like you know, because we've either that recent situation with that that know that streamer that the streamer and
That poble thing that happened the tragedy that can happen if you're doxxed because they can find your address if they're a match
Maybe they'll go that far
99.9% of the time they will
Send a piece of your house not paid for just try to annoy you. Hello
Hey, Saki, how's everything? How are you? Okay?
Well, I mean there's just there's a lot of stuff going on right now, it's like
We're talking about people doxing first of all. We're talking about doxing like just why
but like some of their tactics and you know
So it's good. Yeah, so I yeah, I just you know, just I had this is no doxing this channel
That's I'm gonna be really strong in that rule
So it's not the place like I don't want it to just degenerate into like a place
So people are feeling like unsafe and if there's doxing going on the chat already
I could kind of handle it more in the panel
But I just need mods of those mod if there's any stuff you doxing
Just leave the comment and warn the person if they continue just you know, maybe we have to hide those people
I've noticed it's like a whole different group of chat is in there, you know
Yeah, I mean it's like but that's I mean that's to be expected. I mean it is kind of like, you know
There's not many people in the chat right now first of all and could probably like, you know, they're all these
You know, we were like, you know rated but it's like I guess the rate is still going on or we'll continue to go on
I'm not sure but
You know, that's why I have to be stronger with the
You know blocking people hiding people watching the chat better watching the panel because we're gonna have new people coming in too
So it's gonna be a year from now. There's gonna be a whole different
Crowd here, you know, but I didn't expect it to be like overnight. It'll be a whole different crowd
But yeah a year from now it will be hold different people
But they're gonna be people that are I meet over the year and there's gonna be the third be real ones
Not gonna be a bunch of just random brand new people trying to cause problems in the chat
I'm not saying that's anybody in particular in the chat. There's a lot of really nice people today, but
Yeah, it's just like and I know it's just fishy and so I don't feel like it's anything
Anything like oh, oh, we shared your channel, you know, I tried to do friendly raise like they surely rated me for sure
This is my Howard Stern rated me
one day
And it was just that that was great. Yeah, I remember that and I'm glad I was on
That's like that's like that's what a rate. That's what a rate is supposed to be
It's like it's like it's a raid, but it's not like oh, let's go
It was happening that moment because I had hopped up on piano and like it was
It was blind to me right when I got up in I would just saw him up there
I didn't see like what led up to him coming up
Yeah
He just showed you know what you just showed up in the chat, but like if you watch his show from that day
He's sitting there. There's they're finding different
Channels is the guy in the studio is like, hey, well we found this one guy. He does he like taros and crystals and cats and stuff
He's like, yeah, let's go over there. I watch that too. I don't think it was random though. I think I think he's watched before
I think we all I don't know into the same kind of stuff
They were looking at you mean there are like kind of very few open panels like during sometimes
And I don't think maybe that maybe there's like in all the open panels that were open or something
But yeah, I mean that was kind of and also I remember I was just talking to Jerry that day and Jerry works for the Howard Stern show
he's like, you know the producer of the the e-show and stuff and
And so I mentioned I was talking about Howard Stern and the producer and then so in the algorithm
I think picked that up and made it put that in their algorithm. I'm not sure I've very willing to suffer one
I don't think we suffered it. I remember after that I started getting the three memberships from to the Shoei Network again
mm-hmm
Yeah, so, you know, I've just been there a few times that he's a cool guy, and you know, I
Just haven't I'm not able to go in other chats anymore. I like I'm not I can't go to Lisa's chat anymore
I can't go into even even other streamers chest. It's like stuff to like say hi in the chat
like I
drama that's going through now in the double verse there the stuttering John and
Sent them some happening served them with some papers. Oh
and hear about that but yeah I know that there's a little bit of drama between like
Stettering John and Lisa and
I once told Lisa like she was talking about Shulie and I had just done the tan mom thing where I sent them a question to answer about
tan mom or tan mom a question on Shulie show and I
Were you around when she was on like the Stettering John show and stuff?
I just seen clips of that and I wasn't around I just I've been I've been watching here for like six months
Let's see a closer way. Oh, yeah, Wendy's been on the show daughter of truth. Yeah, when you
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean I I remember watching her on Howard Stern like in like you know 2010 or whatever like but
And as you remember her this Howard Stern and stuff like that and she was just very memorable
So I saw her again. I was like, oh my god
I know her
Freeman because she she used to not do IRL. She had a show come in friends. Yeah, come in friends
We do a panel show like this
Yeah
Little bit less chaotic. She was like, you know, she was scheduled interviews like people interesting people and then she would just do one-on-ones
And so it was like probably like a little less hectic than my show can get because I don't know. She's a big open
She sometimes put three people on the panel. I never saw them more than that really
But yeah, I mean she had interesting people and she had that guy
Christian during the Christian on she had him on she didn't have many Manson on I've seen her every Wendy and Andy Dick and
A lot of other people a lot of people
Unision there's a lot of people that are really recognized but
Yep
The day she went IRL with many that that was hilarious dream and with Billy
Billy John trying to mediate
Oh, it was, it was hilarious.
Well, yeah, I mean I wouldn't I mean I went through the I went through this
You know with many many Manson got mad at me last week or two weeks ago
That was wow like many Manson like went to my discord like posted all this crazy shit
Posted me all these messages in this work, and then we were fine like then we're like he said oh he said oh well
I saw you I saw you apologize on your show, so I you know I accept your apology
Let's can we be friends again, and I was like yeah, so many man a mini man has been on the show since then
No, it wasn't really falling out, but just one night we had a kind of a I brought somebody on the panel when he asked me
that he wouldn't be on loan on the panel and he got pretty upset, but
It's all it's all good. It's all good. We're all good now
Yeah, and I'm a fan of Marilyn Manson's you know, I like a lot of music, but
He's listened to whole Marilyn Manson that was my thing in the 90s for you most
Okay, how we all doing in chat might go grab some food soon though. Oh, okay. We have uh, hold on. Who's this?
Who is this?
Who are
Is that Nick?
That's Nick. Yeah. Hey person in the back. Can you like first in the back? Who are you?
Can you type in the chat first in the back? Can you type in the chat or something?
Let me know who you are or cam up for a second. I won't put you on screen
I just want to see that you're for a person. I have no idea who you are. You have a very suspicious name
Yeah, unless you cam up or comment in the chat. I'm I can't help you. I'm sorry not today Satan
Not today
Okay, we're all good. Okay, they left okay
So, yeah, guys, I just, and I can, right now,
now I can smell, I can smell the porn bombers.
I can just smell them, it's like,
I just got an extra sense.
It's like a sixth sense called no PB, no porn bombers.
Yeah.
Yeah, but if you guys know anything,
just think that.
Oh, yeah, it's probably probably um, you know having a slander fest about me. It's so funny
She was so mad about you know, Kate, you know talking about her and then she's probably like
All this shit about me over there. Who knows? I mean, it's like, I
Hope she doesn't take it. I was listening for a while. She didn't ever she never brought you up. What you two were fighting
She's been here twice today, and she was just really cool both times and
Was like just yelling at me calling pussy that she got she posted in the chat f-a-g-o-t several times and
So yeah, I'm blocked in that chat. I don't know who did it probably one of the most
Beat is
Beat is saying she made me and the same to Birdo
Babel and yeah, so I met I met I met beta I say probably like I
had already been doing my show for a few months and like
She really didn't inspire me to do surgery panels.
Actually, Tyrone, I did.
Marty kind of found you and brought everyone over here.
No, no, no, no, he didn't find me.
First of all, Marty didn't find me.
Well, he might have, but.
That's the wrong word.
I shouldn't have said found you, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no, no, Marty just showed, like he showed up.
I don't know if he was through beta or,
but I just know Jamie, Jamie Rose and him
just showed up one day, right?
Yeah.
I remember I was in chat that time.
I forget how I in love there, but.
But I remember I was in chat with that.
I just hope that's not a doc with BB in that by the first I don't know if it's
Anyway, yeah, I mean no guys
Bida Bida is her show. It's like, you know, it's well, but we kind of have different styles
I mean, you have a lot of um, mutual friends, but
Um, it's just the same I don't I don't want to talk too much about it
But it's just the unfortunate thing is I had a lot of people that are like really really sweet good people, right?
and
you know, they know that I know that are during my chat and stuff and
I've seen
Them get pretty
I don't know. I've just I all of a sudden like
They're on the out and it's this it's not it just seems like it's weird. It's just weird. I don't know
But the coordinate they're half half as illustrations. Yeah, I mean, it's like it's definitely it's like I mean, I'm I'm learning really fast
I'm not gonna put up with it
Really confusing when one night someone screaming cussing at you then the next day acting like nothing happened
Hmm and I
Someone if I get a fight with somebody and then the next day they come to me calm
I'll be calm and it's like we can get along
I'm willing to say I'm willing to not even bring it up
Right spiritual discernment, right?
Yeah, because I just read the spiritual warfare prayers daughter of truth
I felt I felt the spiritual war. I felt like it was something beyond
It's like it's like a demon and you notice that Ziggy has a demon on his avatar. He has a demon, okay?
These avatars a demon from the Goetia the King Solomon's Goetia. It's a magical
text probably 15 16th century with has 72
Yes
It's IPOS the guy's name is I post or they sometimes say anubis or you know, there's different known as different words different names and
It's a pattern some people are asked has like a tiger kids can't change the stripe
Think I think there are there are like
Well, yeah, and you knew this is another name for IPOS. Yeah, but it's like I think a new bus is more of like
You know calling a new bus a demon. I would like I would they come I don't agree with every like every
Because a new bus was the one who brought you
Yeah
He was an underworld
Yeah, a psychopomp but also and also like we know when you have your your your heart wave with this on the scale of
Against the feather of truth to see if your heart lighter than a feather
If you were a friend of the newbis, sometimes he would put his foot on the scale a little bit to even it out and help you out a little bit, you know, because dogs, dogs...
It would measure your deeds in life.
Yeah, but if you look at some of the... Well, it said, is your heart like light, like a feather?
The way to get ma'at has the feather of truth and they put on a scale.
Is your heart lighter than a feather?
Or do you have...
Yeah, do you have guilt you have all this guilt and regret and shame and and stuff and so but but even if people did they have
Tapestries with a new bus and he has like his little his foot like or he's like pulling the scale down a little bit to cheat a little bit because
you know
He's a he's a loyal loyal
friend, okay, when did you find this about out about Ziggy's avatar? Did you ask him to change?
No, I know it's I recognize it because I've studied the Goetia. So I do instantly what it's they're very they're very recognizable, but
That's gonna change it. No, you know, am I afraid of sigils? No
Can it represent something or cannot kind of bring that energy here? Yeah, maybe
but
No, I
You said a lot more like of these really good wishes in the chat
I mean there might be some of you I haven't revealed yourself, but we had a few that could they could do so
We had the same kind of problems before and they would do a return to sender in the chat
Instantly the chat would just be like a bomb and it's like the chat which is like
Everything would like go silent and then I would just be back to normal
But it's like it would be like crazy like this and we and so I had a few return
You acknowledge it
Well, no, no, I mean, it's like, okay, so here's magic. Okay, so you, so you, so you can ask somebody, you believe in magic, you believe, and they're like, I don't believe in magic.
Okay, so if you put a picture of their loved one, you know, or their child or something, put a picture in front of them and give them a knife and say, okay, you don't believe in magic, just stab this picture a hundred times.
most people will not do that because it's like there's a sympathetic there's
something that says that that is a representation of my loved one and so I
would not okay you come on panel come up and so people do believe in magic but
there is like there's this thing where it's like we understand the understanding
of these representations that have hold on hold on hold on oh shit
hold on oh it's black okay okay I got you I got you home
Hello
Yeah, anyway, those are stupid people, but so guys
I'm gonna go ahead and research the stream. I
Was gonna have a